Here's the problem with magnesium
这就是镁的问题所在。
supplementation [music]
补充[音乐]
when it comes to sleep. The first thing
说到睡眠。第一件事
to note is that most forms of magnesium
需要注意的是，大多数形式的镁
don't cross the brain barrier and
不要穿过脑屏障，
[music] sleep is produced by your brain.
[音乐] 睡眠是由你的大脑产生的。
So, how can something that doesn't get
那么，一件无法得到的东西，怎么可能得到呢？
into your brain affect brain process?
进入你的大脑会影响大脑处理过程吗？
All you're doing is creating probably
你所做的只是在制造……
expensive urine.
昂贵的尿液。
However, there is one form of magnesium
然而，镁只有一种形式。
that seems to have some evidence in
这似乎有一些证据
favor of [music] it which we can speak
音乐的魅力，我们可以谈论它。
about. But it doesn't stop there.
关于。但这还没完。
There's so much new evidence that we
有大量新证据表明我们
have including this myth of 8 [music]
包括这个关于 8 的神话 [音乐]
hours. my fear about giving melatonin to
小时。我担心给孩子服用褪黑素
kids. Why you keep waking up in the
孩子们。你为什么总是醒来？
middle of the night and the invention of
半夜和发明
the first new class of [music] sleeping
第一类新的[音乐]睡眠
medication that I actually favor and
我真正喜欢的药物
most people are not aware of it.
大多数人对此并不知情。
&gt;&gt; Okay, let me write this down.
好的，我把它写下来。
&gt;&gt; Matthew Walker [music]
马修·沃克 [音乐]
is back and the worldrenowned sleep
它回来了，而且是世界闻名的睡眠
expert and neuroscience professor
专家和神经科学教授
&gt;&gt; is sharing brand new research to combat
正在分享对抗疾病的最新研究成果
[music] the sleep loss epidemic and help
[音乐] 失眠流行及帮助
you get the perfect night's sleep. So
你会睡个好觉。所以
society, we have struggles with sleep at
社会上，我们都有睡眠问题。
night due to many reasons, but no one
夜晚由于诸多原因，但无人
teaches us this stuff. And it's things
它教给我们这些东西。而且是这些东西
like say you go to bed at 11:00 one
比如说你晚上11点睡觉
night, 1:00 a.m. the next night, then
晚上，然后是第二天凌晨1点。
10:30 p.m. the next night. And it's
晚上10:30第二天晚上。而且是
remarkable how many people do this, but
令人惊讶的是，竟然有这么多人这样做，但是
studies have shown that you are
研究表明你是
statistically 49% more likely to
统计上，可能性高出 49%
prematurely die versus those people who
过早死亡的人与那些
were most regular in terms of going to
就去哪里而言，他们是最常去的
bed and waking up at the same time. And
睡觉和起床的时间一样。和
worse, they had a 57% cardioabolic
更糟糕的是，他们的心血管疾病发病率高达57%。
disease [music] risk increase.
疾病（音乐）风险增加。
&gt;&gt; What the
什么？
&gt;&gt; science really teaches us that there are
科学确实告诉我们，存在着
four pillars of good sleep. [music] And
良好睡眠的四大支柱。 [音乐] 和
then there's this incredible new study
然后还有这项令人难以置信的新研究
looking at sleep banking. And this is
探讨睡眠银行。这就是
remarkable for people who are facing a
对于那些面临困境的人来说，这意义非凡
sprint at work or a medical doctor about
工作中冲刺或咨询医生
to go on call for the next 40 hours, new
接下来40小时需待命，新的
parent. And we can go through all of
父母。我们可以把所有内容都过一遍。
that. But if you were to push me to say
那。但如果你非要我说的话
the three [music] most impactful things
音乐中最有影响力的三件事
that you can start doing tonight to
你今晚就可以开始做这件事
start sleeping better, it would be
开始改善睡眠质量，那将会……
I see messages all the time in the
我经常在……中看到消息
comments section that some of you didn't
评论区里有些人没看到。
realize you didn't subscribe. So,
意识到你没有订阅。所以，
[snorts] if you could do me a favor and
[嗤笑] 如果你能帮我个忙的话，
double check if you're a subscriber to
请再次确认您是否是订阅用户
this channel, that would be tremendously
这个频道，那将会非常棒。
appreciated. It's the simple, it's the
谢谢。很简单，就是这样
free thing that anybody that watches
免费的东西，任何观看的人都可以获得
this show frequently can do to help us
这个节目经常能帮到我们
here to keep everything going in this
来这里是为了维持一切正常运转。
show in the trajectory it's on. So,
按照它所处的轨迹显示出来。所以，
please do double check if you've
请仔细检查您是否已经
subscribed and uh thank you so much
已订阅，非常感谢！
because in a strange way, you are you're
因为从某种意义上说，你就是你。
part of our history and you're on this
这是我们历史的一部分，而你也身处其中。
journey with us and I appreciate you for
与我们同行，我非常感谢您。
that. So yeah, thank you
那。是的，谢谢。
[music]
[音乐]
[singing]
[歌唱]
Dr. Matthew Walker. Here in front of me,
马修·沃克博士。就在我眼前，
I have these cards which I'm going to
我有一些卡片，我打算……
reveal a bit later, but these kind of
稍后会揭晓，但这类
hold what you consider to be the four
持有你认为的四个
pillars of great sleep. But you also
优质睡眠的支柱。但你也
spend much of your professional career
在你的职业生涯中花费大部分时间
just studying the brain generally to
仅仅是研究大脑的一般情况
understand human performance and how we
了解人类表现以及我们如何
can change our lifestyles and also
可以改变我们的生活方式，而且
introduce some of these new sort of
介绍其中一些新型的
treatments to improve how our brain
改善我们大脑功能的治疗方法
performs. And I want to talk about all
表演。我想谈谈所有的一切
of that as well, but to start for anyone
这一点也很重要，但对任何人来说，这都是一个开始。
that is unfamiliar with you and has been
你不熟悉的，而且一直是
hiding under a rock,
躲在石头底下，
how do you summarize who you are
你如何概括自己？
professionally,
专业上，
the sort of academic references you're
你提供的学术参考文献类型
drawing on, and the experiences and
借鉴经验和
research you've done so that the viewer
你所做的研究，以便观众
listening at home understands the full
在家听能完全理解。
world that you operate in, study, and
你所处、所研究和所处的世界
have experienced.
经历过。
&gt;&gt; I am a neuroscientist by trade, but my
我是一名神经科学家，但我
specialty is sleep. the effects of sleep
专业领域是睡眠。睡眠的影响
on the brain and the body. And I've
对大脑和身体的影响。而且我已经
probably spent about the past two
可能在过去的两年里花了大约两个小时
decades trying to understand exactly why
几十年来，人们一直在试图弄明白究竟为什么。
do we sleep? Because 50 years ago, the
我们睡觉吗？因为50年前，
crass answer to the question, why do you
对“为什么”这个问题的粗鲁回答
sleep was the following? You sleep to
睡眠情况如下？你睡着了
cure sleepiness,
治疗嗜睡症
which is the factous equivalent of
这是事实上的等价物
saying, well, you eat to cure hunger.
他说，人吃饭是为了消除饥饿。
No, you don't eat to cure cure hunger.
不，你吃饭不是为了消除饥饿。
you eat to support all sorts of
你吃东西是为了维持各种需求
physiological and biological benefits.
生理和生物学益处。
But now, and this is not due to my
但现在，这并非由于我的
research, is this all of the incredible
研究，这就是全部的不可思议之处吗？
colleagues whose sort of shoulders that
那些肩膀像肩膀一样的同事们
I stand on, we've now had to upend the
我坚持认为，我们现在不得不彻底颠覆……
question. We now have to ask, is there
问题。现在我们必须问，是否存在
any major physiological system in your
你体内任何主要的生理系统
body or is there any operation of your
身体方面，或者你做过任何手术吗？
mind that isn't wonderfully enhanced by
思维并没有因此而得到极大的提升。
sleep when you get it or demonstrabably
得到或明显地睡觉
impaired when you don't get enough? And
摄入不足时会感到不适吗？和
the answer now seems to be no. There is
现在看来答案是否定的。有
no such system. Even down to the level
没有这样的系统。甚至细化到这个层面
of your DNA,
你的DNA，
your sleep and how you are sleeping or
你的睡眠状况和你的睡眠方式
not sleeping will change the very DNA
睡眠不足会改变DNA。
nucleic alphabet that spells out your
核酸字母表拼写出你的
daily health narrative. And we can see
每日健康小贴士。我们可以看到
it all the way up to society. Sleep can
一直到整个社会。睡眠可以
change the fabric of society, can change
改变社会结构，可以改变
how we interact with other people. It
我们如何与他人互动。它
can change our belief systems. can
可以改变我们的信仰体系。能
change how lonely or sort of hypersocial
改变孤独感或某种程度上的过度社交
we are. So to your question, I'm a sleep
我们是。所以回答你的问题，我正在睡觉
scientist by trade and I suppose my
我是一名科学家，我想我的
mission has been trying to reunite
该任务一直试图让家人团聚。
humanity with the sleep that it seems to
人类似乎在沉睡
be so bereft of.
如此缺乏。
&gt;&gt; We had a fantastic conversation last
我们上周进行了一次非常棒的谈话。
time and my audience valued it
时间和我的听众都很珍惜它。
tremendously. I know that cuz we we
非常大。我知道，因为我们
often survey our audience and we we get
我们经常对受众进行调查，并从中获取信息。
to see some of the the backend stats and
查看一些后端统计数据和
this conversation about sleep is
这场关于睡眠的对话是
particularly personal to everybody
对每个人来说都特别私人
listening because when we surveyed our
倾听是因为当我们调查我们的
audience ahead of this conversation
本次对话前的观众
today about 75 or 80% of the direio
今天大约有75%或80%的董事
audience struggle with sleep for a
观众饱受睡眠困扰
variety of different reasons. So we
原因多种多样。所以，我们
actually asked them a thousand of them
实际上问了他们上千人。
their questions to ask you today. But
他们今天想问你的问题。但
also the other reason I really wanted to
这也是我非常想做的另一个原因
chat to you is the science of sleep I
跟你聊天就是关于睡眠科学的。
mean as is the way of science is always
科学的方式总是意味着
evolving. We're learning new things and
正在发展。我们正在学习新事物，
even since we spoke last time, there is
自从我们上次谈话以来，已经发生了很多事。
new sleep science which we're going to
我们将要介绍的最新睡眠科学
talk about today and one of those
谈谈今天以及其中之一
particular things we're going to talk
我们将要讨论的具体内容
about is going to be demonstrated using
关于这一点将通过以下方式进行演示：
this jar [laughter] because I always
这个罐子[笑声]因为我总是
want to know what the updated sleep
想知道最新的睡眠情况
science is so that I can be a better
科学让我能够成为更好的人。
sleeper because I agree with everything
因为我完全同意，所以就当个睡美人吧
you've said about how foundational sleep
你曾说过睡眠的基础性作用
is in my life.
在我的生活中。
&gt;&gt; And um I didn't know this at the start
嗯，我一开始并不知道这一点。
of my career. I didn't know this even a
我职业生涯中的一部分。我甚至不知道这件事
couple of years ago, five years ago. I
几年前，五年前。我
didn't know. I thought sleep was one of
不知道。我以为睡眠是其中之一
those things you could just take it all
那些东西你完全可以全部拿走。
or leave.
或者离开。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. I mean, and it's not your fault in
是的。我的意思是，这并非你的错。
so many ways because if you didn't know
有很多方法，因为如果你不知道的话
what I know, you would just think, well,
据我所知，你会想，嗯，
when I sleep, my body is dormant and my
当我睡觉时，我的身体处于休眠状态，我的
mind for the most part is blank. So, is
大部分时间脑子一片空白。所以，是
it so catastrophic to lose, you know, an
失去一个……真是太可怕了，你知道吗？
hour or two of sleep? And you know, you
睡一两个小时？你知道，你
have to then think about from an
然后必须从以下角度考虑：
evolutionary perspective, it is such an
从进化论的角度来看，这真是……
idiotic idea to sleep because when
睡觉是个愚蠢的想法，因为当
you're sleeping, you're not finding a
你睡着了，你找不到
mate, you're not reproducing, you're not
伙计，你没在繁衍后代，你没在繁衍后代
caring for your young, you're not
照顾你的孩子，你不是
foraging for food, and worst of all,
四处觅食，而最糟糕的是，
you're vulnerable to predation.
你很容易成为捕食者的目标。
&gt;&gt; So on any one of those grounds, and
所以，基于上述任何一项理由，以及
especially all of them as a collective,
尤其是他们作为一个整体而言，
sleep should have been strongly selected
睡眠应该经过严格筛选
against in the course of evolution.
在进化过程中与之相反。
And my point is that, and it's often
我的意思是，而且这种情况经常发生。
been said that if sleep doesn't serve an
有人说过，如果睡眠不能起到作用……
absolutely vital set of functions
绝对至关重要的功能集
plural, then it's the biggest mistake
如果是复数形式，那就是最大的错误。
the evolutionary process has ever made.
进化过程所创造的一切。
And we now realize it didn't make a
我们现在意识到它并没有造成什么影响。
spectacular blunder. But really, I guess
惊人的失误。但说真的，我想
to the point of it is sleep is not a
关键在于睡眠并非……
passive state. It's an incredibly active
被动状态。这是一个极其活跃的地区。
state both in the terms of the brain and
无论是从大脑的角度来看，还是从其他方面来看，都处于这种状态
the body. And so you should not feel
身体。所以你不应该感到
sort of you know remiss or ashamed that
有点你知道的，有点疏忽或者羞愧。
you didn't value the importance of sleep
你没有意识到睡眠的重要性
because firstly as a subjective sense
首先，从主观角度来说
you just think well my mind was offline
你就会想，好吧，我当时脑子一片空白。
for a while. Second we also know that we
一阵子。其次，我们也知道我们
don't teach the importance of sleep in
不要在课堂上教授睡眠的重要性
education and doctors themselves you
教育和医生本身
know there's a great study and they what
我知道有一项很棒的研究，他们是什么
they found was that medical doctors
他们发现的是，医生
across I think it was about 11 different
我觉得大概有11种不同的
curricula around the world they will
世界各地的课程设置将
only receive about 1.2 two hours of
仅接收约 1.2 个小时的
education on sleep, but it's a third of
睡眠教育，但只有三分之一
their patients lives. So there's a
他们守护着病人的生命。所以，这里有一个
collection of sort of almost perfect
近乎完美的收藏
storms that have happened to keep
发生的风暴一直
society ignorant of the importance and
社会对重要性缺乏了解，并且
the value of sleep. I think that's why
睡眠的价值。我想这就是原因
we often so short change it together
我们经常一起偷工减料。
with also something terrible which is
还有一件可怕的事情是
stigma.
柱头。
that people are so proud to say, well,
人们非常自豪地说，嗯，
I've been eating really healthy the past
我过去一直吃得很健康。
couple of months, or, you know, I've
几个月，或者，你知道，我已经
been going to the gym, you know, three
你知道，我一直在去健身房，三个月
times a week consistently for the past
过去每周几次
year. No one is ever going out into
年。没有人会出去
society and saying, you know, I I've
社会上有人说，你知道，我，我
been getting 8 and 1/2 hours of sleep
每天睡8个半小时
consistently every night. Because if you
每晚都如此。因为如果你
did, people would say, really? And
人们会问，真的吗？和
there's a there's a slight edge to the
略微有些……
really which is that if you have time to
实际上，如果你有时间的话
sleep then you must not be busy and if
睡觉的话，你肯定不忙，而且如果
you're not busy you must not be
你不忙，你肯定不忙。
important.
重要的。
So can you do me a favor and for the
所以你能帮我个忙吗？
listener at home can you tell me what
家里的听众朋友们，你们能告诉我什么吗？
the different groups of people that are
不同人群
listening to this conversation right now
我正在听这段对话
are seeking from the extreme end being
正在寻求从极端走向极端
sleep apnnea. I get no sleep. I'm an
睡眠呼吸暂停。我彻夜难眠。我是一名
insomniac to the other end where maybe
失眠症患者到另一端，也许
they're looking for marginal performance
他们追求的是勉强及格的成绩。
gains. Like what are the what are the
收益。比如，什么是？什么是？
cohorts of people you see and the
你看到的人群以及
reasons why they're so interested in
他们如此感兴趣的原因
your work? They listen to your podcast,
你的工作？他们会听你的播客，
they read your books. What are the
他们会读你的书。什么是
cohorts?
群体？
&gt;&gt; Firstly, we have the collection of
首先，我们有以下集合：
people who have insomnia. Those people
患有失眠症的人。那些人
who have other sleep disorders like
患有其他睡眠障碍的人，例如
sleep apnoa which we can speak about.
我们可以谈谈睡眠呼吸暂停症。
There's another disorder called restless
还有一种叫做躁动症的疾病
leg syndrome. It's a terrible disorder
腿部综合征。这是一种可怕的疾病
where your legs start to feel as though
当你的腿开始感觉好像
they've got this sort of creepy crawly
它们有这种令人毛骨悚然的爬虫
feeling and you've constantly got to
感觉，而且你必须不断地
massage them and move them. It's a
按摩并移动它们。这是一个
terrible disruptor of your sleep. All of
严重干扰睡眠。全部
these disorders are marketkedly
这些疾病是市场化的
undiagnosed, by the way. And then you've
顺便说一句，我还没确诊。然后你就……
got another collection of individuals
又收集了一批人
who they don't have any sleep disorders,
他们没有任何睡眠障碍，
but they are either doing things that
但他们要么在做这样的事
will dismantle their sleep. So, either
将会扰乱他们的睡眠。所以，要么
they're taking on things into themselves
他们把事情都揽到自己身上了。
like alcohol, caffeine, THC that aren't
比如酒精、咖啡因、THC 等，它们并非如此。
the sleep helpers, even though sometimes
助眠剂，即使有时
they think they are. And then you've got
他们自认为如此。然后你就有了
perhaps the internal things that will
或许是内部的事情
prevent you from sleeping well. Things
妨碍你睡个好觉。事物
like stress and anxiety. And then you've
例如压力和焦虑。然后你就……
also just got life itself that can get
也刚刚经历了人生本身，而人生本身就可能……
in the way. And then moving from the
挡路。然后从
sleep disorders realm to the I don't
睡眠障碍领域，我不这么认为
have a sleep disorder, but I'm probably
我有睡眠障碍，但我可能
not doing it right quote unquote when it
做事不正确，就是说它
comes to sleep. Then you've got the
睡着了。然后你就有了
people who are obsessed about getting it
那些痴迷于得到它的人
right and they are the bio optimizers.
没错，它们就是生物优化器。
this sort of the you know the biohackers
这种生物黑客，你知道的。
and then you've also got I work with a
然后你还有我与一个
lot of high performance individuals who
许多高绩效人士
are really trying to just scratch out
他们真的只是想勉强应付一下。
those last couple of percentages either
最后那几个百分点要么
if it's in business or often we're
如果是在商业领域，或者我们经常……
working with professional athletes.
与职业运动员合作。
These are the people for whom two or
对于这些人，两个人或
three percentage point changes can be
三个百分点的变化可能会
tens of millions of dollars or they can
数千万美元，或者他们可以
be the difference between standing on a
这可能决定你站在……
podium at the Olympics or not. And so
无论是否登上奥运会领奖台。所以
there's there's a broad collection of
这里有种类繁多的
wonderful characters.
精彩的人物角色。
&gt;&gt; And since we last spoke, is there now a
自从我们上次谈话以来，现在是否……
lot of new sleep science and
许多新的睡眠科学和
understanding as it relates to sleep
理解睡眠的相关知识
performance and these three categories
表现和这三个类别
of sleep deficient sleep disorders,
睡眠不足引起的睡眠障碍
lifestyle factors and then the
生活方式因素，然后是
optimizers.
优化器。
&gt;&gt; Yeah, I think there's there's a broad
是的，我认为存在一个广泛的问题。
collection of new evidence that we have.
我们收集到的新证据。
But maybe let me come on to the middle
但或许我可以转到中间部分。
group. You know, I used to say that for
团体。你知道，我以前常这么说。
people who were deficient in their
那些在以下方面存在缺陷的人
sleep, that sleep wasn't like the bank,
睡眠，那种睡眠不像银行的睡眠，
that you can't accumulate a debt. Oh,
你不能累积债务。哦，
here we go. Okay. So, what we can see
开始了。好的。所以，我们可以看到
here is that the jar used to be full,
这里的情况是，罐子以前是满的。
full of sleep credit when you're
当你睡眠充足时
sleeping well. And then during the week,
睡得很好。然后，在一周内，
I'm short sleeping. So, maybe I'm only
我睡眠不足。所以，也许我只是
getting five hours a night. So, I'm
每晚睡五个小时。所以，我是
constantly going into debt. So, I'm
不断负债。所以，我是
losing all of this wonderful sleep
失去了所有这些美好的睡眠
credit and my system is building up this
信用和我的系统正在建立这一点
collateral debt. And then we used to
抵押债务。然后我们过去常常
think that sleep was not like the bank.
想想看，睡眠和银行不一样。
That once you've gone into debt,
一旦你背负了债务，
unfortunately,
很遗憾，
the lid is closed and even at the
盖子盖上了，即使在……
weekend, if you try to pay it back, you
周末，如果你试图还钱，你
can't put back credit into the system.
无法将信用额度重新注入系统。
However, there was a study published
然而，有一项研究发表出来。
from what's called the UK Bioank, which
来自所谓的英国生物资源中心，
is this incredible data set. It's
这是一个令人难以置信的数据集。它是
revolutionary. And they studied in this
革命性的。他们在这里学习。
particular research uh paper over 90,000
特定研究论文超过90,000
individuals. And what they did was they
个人。他们所做的就是
essentially split them down into those
基本上将它们分成这些
individuals who were short sleeping
睡眠时间短的人
during the week and then short sleeping
工作日睡眠时间短，然后晚上睡觉时间短。
at the weekend. And they compared them
周末。他们将它们进行了比较。
to those individuals who were short
对于那些缺货的人来说
sleeping during the week, but then long
工作日睡觉，但之后很长一段时间
sleeping at the weekend. They were doing
周末睡觉。他们当时正在做
catch-up sleep.
补觉。
&gt;&gt; That's me.
这就是我。
&gt;&gt; And that's so many individuals. It turns
那可是很多人啊。原来如此
out if you look at the data, it's it's
如果你查看数据，就会发现……
remarkable how many people do this this
令人惊讶的是，竟然有这么多人这样做。
catch-up sleep behavior. But what was
补觉行为。但是，那又是什么呢？
amazing is that in the people who were
令人惊讶的是，在那些人中
short sleeping during the week but long
工作日睡眠时间短，但长期睡眠时间长
sleeping at the weekend, they had a 20%
周末睡觉，他们有20%
reduced cardiovascular disease risk
降低心血管疾病风险
relative to the people who were short
相对于那些身高较矮的人来说
sleeping during the week but also short
工作日睡觉，但也很短
sleeping at the weekend. Now, to be
周末睡觉。现在，要成为
clear, both of those groups had a higher
很明显，这两个群体都具有更高的……
cardiovascular disease risk than people
比其他人更容易患心血管疾病的人
who were sleeping sufficiently during
睡眠充足的人
the week and sleeping sufficiently
一周的安排和充足的睡眠
during the weekend. So, I'm not saying
周末期间。所以，我不是说
that it's a completely free lunch. But
这是一顿​​完全免费的午餐。但
for the first time, we realized that at
我们第一次意识到，
least one system, major organ system in
至少一个系统，主要器官系统
your body is like the bank, which is
你的身体就像银行，而银行就是
that if your heart at the weekend
如果你周末的心跳加速
you can
你可以
just keep putting credit back and your
只要不断充值，你的
system doesn't suffer as much
系统受到的影响并不大。
&gt;&gt; for your heart.
为了你的心。
&gt;&gt; Okay.
好的。
&gt;&gt; But again, many of the other major
但同样，其他许多主要
physiological systems don't show that.
生理系统不会表现出这种现象。
So work by people like Kenneth Wright at
所以，像肯尼斯·赖特这样的人的作品
the University of Boulder, Colorado,
科罗拉多州博尔德大学
he's shown that your immune system
他已经证明你的免疫系统
doesn't rebound after long sleep at the
长时间睡眠后不会恢复正常
weekend, your regulation of blood sugar,
周末，你的血糖调节情况，
your cognitive ability. So that's one
你的认知能力。所以，这是其中之一。
way in which I've changed my mind
我改变主意的方式
regarding sleep in the bank. But there's
关于在银行睡觉。但是还有
a very different new set of data that
一组截然不同的新数据，
has changed my mind completely about
彻底改变了我对……的看法
this idea of sleep and the bank. Now
睡眠和银行的这种想法。现在
what we've just discussed here is to say
我们刚才讨论的就是：
I went into debt and then I was hoping
我负债累累，然后我抱着一丝希望。
to try and pay it off with credit at the
尝试用信用卡偿还。
weekend.
周末。
&gt;&gt; So the jar represents the debt that you
所以这个罐子代表了你所欠的债务。
have the sleep.
好好睡一觉。
&gt;&gt; Correct. Yeah. And what I'm trying to do
正确的。是的。而我正在努力做的
is force more coinage
强制发行更多硬币
in at the weekend to see if I can offset
周末去看看能不能抵消
the debt that I created and get back to
我所欠的债务，以及我最终的偿还。
net net neutral by the end of the
到年底，净值将达到净中性。
weekend. Now, it turns out you can't do
周末。现在看来，你做不到这一点。
that even if you sleep for as long as
即使你睡了很久很久
you want. But here's this new remarkable
你想要。但这里有一个令人瞩目的新发现。
data. It came from um Walter Reed
数据。它来自沃尔特·里德
Medical Army Institute, a researcher
陆军医学研究所，一名研究人员
called Thomas Balkan. And what he was
名叫托马斯·巴尔干。而他究竟是什么样的人
interested in was flipping the direction
感兴趣的是改变方向
of the question. Not if I go into debt,
这个问题。如果我因此负债，那就不行了。
can I pay back with credit, but what if
我可以用信用卡还款吗？但是如果
I know in future I'm going to face a
我知道将来我会面临……
debt, an upcoming debt, can I do sleep
债务，即将到来的债务，我能睡着吗
banking?
银行业？
&gt;&gt; Oh, so if I've got a big thing coming up
哦，所以如果我接下来有件大事发生的话
where I'm traveling across the world and
我正在环游世界，
I know I'm going to be sleep deficient,
我知道我会睡眠不足。
can I sleep a lot before it to create a
我可以在它之前睡很多觉来创造一个
What would the financial analogy be? The
如果用金融术语来类比，会是什么呢？这
financial analogy would be, let's say
用金融术语来说，比如说……
that we're coming up to Christmas.
圣诞节快到了。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; And you're going to spend lots on, you
而且你会在……上花很多钱
know, presents and all sorts of stuff.
知道，礼物和各种各样的东西。
So, I know that in October and November,
所以，我知道在十月和十一月，
I'm going to tighten my financial belt.
我要勒紧裤腰带过日子了。
&gt;&gt; I see.
我懂了。
&gt;&gt; So that when I go into the sort of
所以当我进入那种状态时
Christmas period and I'm spending a lot
圣诞节期间，我花了很多钱。
more money, my bank account isn't hit as
钱多了，我的银行账户却没受影响。
hard. I don't go into as much of a sort
难的。我不太喜欢这类事情。
of a debt situation because I've built
因为我建立了自己的债务体系，所以我陷入了债务困境。
up credit. So you can create sleep
充值。所以你可以创造睡眠
savings.
节省。
&gt;&gt; Correct. It's a sleepsaving system. So
正确的。这是一个能节省睡眠的系统。所以
essentially, you know, what he was able
基本上，你知道，他能够做到的
to do, not just put the jar to full, but
要做的，不仅仅是把罐子装满，而是
he was actually packing in even more
他实际上还打包了更多东西。
so that you almost got this wonderful
所以你几乎就得到了这个美好的结果。
overflow of sleep.
睡眠过多。
&gt;&gt; How did he know?
他是怎么知道的？
&gt;&gt; He didn't. It was the experimental
他没有。这是一项实验
hypothesis.
假设。
&gt;&gt; And but how did they prove it?
但他们是如何证明的呢？
&gt;&gt; So what they did is that they woke you
所以他们所做的就是叫醒你。
up to a period when you're going to have
直到你将要经历的那段时间
two or three nights of either no sleep
两三个晚上没睡着
or marketked sleep reduction. And in the
或减少睡眠。而且在
week beforehand with these army
提前一周与这些军队
cadetses, instead of being limited to 8
学员人数不应仅限于 8 人
hours of time in bed, they were able to
卧床数小时后，他们能够
get 10 hours of time in bed and they
他们每天在床上待10个小时。
could sleep all that they want. And so
他们可以睡到自然醒。所以
they went from probably an average of
他们的平均水平大概是
about 7 7 and 1/2 hours of sleep to
大约7个半小时的睡眠
about 8 and 1/2 almost 9 hours of sleep.
大约睡了 8 个半小时，接近 9 个小时。
So they were extending their sleep
所以他们延长了睡眠时间。
duration
期间
and so that they had built up this
因此，他们才建立了这种体系。
buffer. It's almost like a sort of a a
缓冲。这几乎就像一种……
sleep safety net that's in place so that
睡眠安全网已经到位，以便
when you go into the tumble of sleep
当你进入梦乡时
deprivation,
剥夺，
you're sort of almost bolstered and
你几乎得到了某种程度的加强，
you're lifted higher and therefore your
你被抬得更高，因此你的
degree of impermanment that you suffer
你所遭受的无常程度
under conditions of sleep deprivation is
在睡眠不足的情况下是
significantly less if you banked sleep
如果你把睡眠时间存起来，睡眠时间就会显著减少。
beforehand versus those people who were
事先与那些……的人相比
just sleeping normally and then faced
正常睡觉，然后面对
the deprivation. they went down much
匮乏。他们跌了很多。
further in terms of their cognitive and
进一步来说，就他们的认知和
mental performance.
心理表现。
&gt;&gt; So he gave them challenges and tasks to
所以他给他们布置了挑战和任务。
do correct in two different groups. One
请在两个不同的组中进行更正。一
group had sleep savings saved up from
该团体节省了睡眠开支。
sleeping well the previous week. One
上周睡眠质量很好。一
group didn't.
该团体没有。
&gt;&gt; That's right.
这是正确的。
&gt;&gt; And they performed remarkably different.
他们的表现截然不同。
&gt;&gt; So both of them were impaired relative
所以他们俩都是残疾亲属
to a sleep rested person. However, the
对一个睡眠充足、休息充分的人来说。然而，
people it's sort of you know how how
人们就是这样，你知道的，怎么会这样
much of a drop
大幅下降
&gt;&gt; in your cognitive performance do you
在你的认知能力方面，你是否
suffer? And what he found was that
遭受？他发现的是……
people who had built up this credit,
那些积累了这种信用的人，
this savings account of sleep in the
睡眠储蓄账户
days, in the week beforehand, they
在前一周的几天里，他们
suffered about 40% less of an impairment
受损程度减轻了约 40%。
relative to the people who had not
相对于那些没有……的人来说
created any savings plan. Now, they
创建任何储蓄计划。现在，他们
weren't in debt. They were just net
没有负债。它们只是网
neutral.
中性的。
&gt;&gt; But boy, did they drop quickly. Whereas
但是，它们下降得真快。然而
those people who'd had some cash in the
那些手头有一些现金的人
sleep credit system, they didn't fall
睡眠积分制度，他们没有倒下
anywhere near as far. But this is
几乎到不了那么远。但这是
remarkable for people like you were
对于像你这样的人来说，这真是太了不起了。
saying who are facing, let's say, if
比如说，谁面临这样的情况？
I've got a sprint at work or I'm a
我工作上有个冲刺任务，或者我是一个
medical doctor, I know I'm about to go
医生，我知道我即将离世
on call for the next 40 hours. You're a
接下来40小时待命。你是
military, aviation, all of the new
军事、航空，所有新的
parents. All of these circumstances are
父母。所有这些情况都是
places where now we know athletes is a
现在我们知道运动员是某些地方的
great example. When we work with a
很好的例子。当我们与……合作时
athletes, people like Michael Grner have
像迈克尔·格纳这样的运动员有
demonstrated that athletes sleep
研究表明运动员睡眠
terribly typically the night before a
非常通常是前一天晚上
huge performance. No matter, you know,
表现非常出色。没关系，你知道的。
of course, they're nerves.
当然，那是紧张情绪。
&gt;&gt; But what you can do is you can have them
但你可以做的就是拥有它们。
bank sleep in the days before when
银行睡眠在过去的日子里
they're not as nervous and therefore
他们没那么紧张，因此
their performance doesn't suffer as much
他们的表现并没有受到太大影响。
even though they know they're going to
即使他们知道自己会……
be deprived.
被剥夺。
&gt;&gt; Sleep is so important, isn't it? And I
睡眠真的非常重要，不是吗？我
think everybody now knows that because
我觉得现在大家都知道了，因为
of people like yourself or really, you
像你这样的人，或者说，你
know, you were the real pioneer in
你知道吗，你才是真正的先驱
pushing the subject into the world. I
将主题推向世界。我
remember when you first went on Joe
还记得你第一次上乔节目的时候吗？
Rogan's show, the amount of my friends
罗根的节目，我的朋友数量
that sent me that episode and then sent
他们给我发了那一集，然后又发了
me your book was just staggering. It was
你的书简直让我叹为观止。那是
like that was the catalyst moment, I
感觉那就是转折点，我
think, in society for the mainstream to
想想，在主流社会中
really start talking and caring about
真正开始谈论和关心
sleep. However, there's still so many
睡觉。然而，仍然有很多。
people struggling um because of all the
人们因为所有这些而苦苦挣扎
factors that you talked about when we're
你之前谈到的那些因素
talking about group two who have those
谈到第二组那些人
lifestyle factors, the stress, the
生活方式因素、压力、
psychological factors, the trauma, etc.,
心理因素、创伤等等。
etc.
ETC。
What can we give them, those people, the
我们能给他们什么？那些人？
people that really really struggle,
那些真正挣扎的人，
maybe they haven't got a disorder. We'll
也许他们根本没有患病。出色地
come to the people with sort of sleep
来到那些有某种睡眠状态的人们身边
disorders later and we'll talk about
稍后我们会讨论疾病问题。
optimizers. But what what is the new
优化器。但新的是什么呢？
information or advice that we can give
我们可以提供的信息或建议
them that will help them once and for
那些能帮助他们一次又一次的人
all sleep 8 hours a night and get their
他们每晚睡8小时，并且……
life back?
生活恢复正常了吗？
&gt;&gt; If you were to push me to say what are
如果你逼我说出来，
the three most
前三名
impactful things that you can start
你可以开始做一些有影响力的事情
doing tonight to start sleeping better,
今晚开始努力改善睡眠质量。
it would be the following.
内容如下。
Digital detox.
数码戒断。
&gt;&gt; Okay, let me write this down. Digital
好的，我把它写下来。数字的
detox. Okay, what does that mean?
排毒。好的，那是什么意思？
&gt;&gt; 1 hour before bed,
睡前1小时
try to limit
尽量限制
activating social media engagement,
激活社交媒体互动，
email, and text messages that are going
电子邮件和短信正在发送
to trigger you.
激怒你。
&gt;&gt; It's fine to listen to a podcast, you
听播客没问题，你
know.
知道。
&gt;&gt; Thank God for that. [laughter]
感谢上帝。 [笑声]
&gt;&gt; You heard it here, folks.
各位，你们都听到了。
&gt;&gt; Right from that book.
就出自那本书。
&gt;&gt; But it's also good to like and
但喜欢也是好事，
subscribe, would you say? I would say
你会订阅吗？我会说
that you know like and subscribe and
你知道的，点赞、订阅和
then just click here so that you get the
然后点击这里即可获取
latest notification you get that bell
你会收到最新的通知铃声。
just click on the bell icon so that you
只需点击铃铛图标即可。
[laughter]
[笑声]
&gt;&gt; so it's not a problem of blue light a
所以这不是蓝光的问题。
quick aside we've been taught this myth
先插一句，我们从小就被灌输了这个谬论。
of the blue light effect
蓝光效应
&gt;&gt; from devices and it really is a myth
来自设备，这其实是个神话
because an incredible Australian
因为一位了不起的澳大利亚人
researcher a guy called Michael Gradazar
一位名叫迈克尔·格拉达扎尔的研究员
has almost singlehandedly
几乎凭借一己之力
changed the the what I think of as being
改变了我对“存在”的看法
the zeitgeist for a while after a very
在经历了一段非常时期之后，时代精神一度成为主流。
influential paper which is a great paper
一篇很有影响力的优秀论文
and what they showed was that 1 hour of
他们展示的是那1个小时的
iPad reading before bed ended up
睡前用iPad阅读的结局
impairing your melatonin it disrupted
它会干扰你的褪黑激素分泌。
sleep it reduced the amount of dream
睡眠减少了梦境的数量
sleep and even after they stopped
睡眠，甚至在他们停止之后也是如此
reading the iPad the blast radius impact
在 iPad 上阅读爆炸半径的影响
on your dream sleep lasted a week it's
你的梦境睡眠持续了一周，是
almost like the drug needed to get
几乎就像需要服用药物才能达到目的一样
washed out the system that even when you
即使你
you'd stop using technology for an hour
你会停止使用科技产品一个小时。
before bed the impact of that technology
睡前思考这项技术的影响
ology even though you'd stopped using it
即使你已经停止使用它，它仍然有效。
could still be seen in the echo of sleep
睡眠的回声中依然可见。
disruption for a week later. It was a
中断持续了一周。那是一个
very influential study in a very
一项极具影响力的研究
prestigious channel.
知名频道。
&gt;&gt; When was that a while ago?
那是多久以前的事了？
&gt;&gt; That was probably about 10 years ago.
那大概是十年前的事了。
But then Michael Gretazar, this
但后来，迈克尔·格雷塔扎尔，
incredible Australian researcher started
一位杰出的澳大利亚研究员开始了
to say, well, I can't replicate these
也就是说，我无法复制这些
findings.
发现。
And what he was discovering is that it's
他发现的是，
not the blue light that's the problem.
问题不在于蓝光。
Now, the blue light will change aspects
现在，蓝光将改变某些方面。
of your melatonin. And melatonin is a
你的褪黑激素。褪黑素是一种
hormone. It simply tells your brain and
激素。它只是告诉你的大脑和
your body when it's nighttime, when it's
你的身体在夜晚，在……
time to fall asleep. It doesn't
该睡觉了。它不
participate in the generation of sleep.
参与睡眠的生成。
Melatonin is like the starting official
褪黑素就像是发令枪手。
at the 100 meter race. It brings all of
在100米赛跑中。它带来了一切。
the races to the line and it begins the
冲向终点线，比赛开始了
timing of the race, but it doesn't
比赛时间安排，但并非如此
participate in the creation of the race
参与创建比赛
itself. That's a different set of
本身。那是另一套……
chemicals.
化学品。
&gt;&gt; It doesn't make you go to sleep. It
它不会让你入睡。它
doesn't make you and if you look at what
这并不能决定你，如果你看看什么
we call meta analyses where we gather
我们称之为荟萃分析，其中我们收集
together all of the individual studies
综合所有单独的研究
on a topic and we put them in a big
我们围绕某个主题，把它们放在一个大……
statistical bucket. What they found is
统计桶。他们发现的是
that melatonin will only improve the
褪黑素只会改善……
speed with which you fall asleep by
你入睡的速度
about um 3.4 minutes and it will only
大约需要3.4分钟，而且只会……
increase the efficiency of your sleep by
通过以下方式提高睡眠效率
about 2.2%. So not much more than
约2.2%。所以也就仅此而已。
placebo. Um, so melatonin is it it's now
安慰剂。嗯，所以褪黑素就是它，现在
the placebo effect is the most reliable
安慰剂效应是最可靠的。
effect in all of pharmarmacology. So you
对所有药理学领域均有影响。所以你
know maybe no harm no foul I would say
我知道也许没什么大碍，我这么说吧。
and don't forget I will come back to the
别忘了，我还会回来的。
three but when it comes to melatonin be
三，但说到褪黑素……
careful more isn't always better and you
注意，并非越多越好，而且你
run the risk of confusing your morning
冒着弄乱你早晨的风险。
brain into a dense nighttime fog. And
大脑仿佛陷入了浓重的夜雾之中。和
what I mean by that is
我的意思是……
10 milligrams or 20 milligrams of
10毫克或20毫克的
melatonin is what we call a supra
褪黑素就是我们所说的超物质
physiological dose, which again is just
生理剂量，也就是……
a fancy medical term to say it's a size
一个听起来很专业的医学术语，其实就是说它的大小。
of magnitude of melatonin that your body
你体内褪黑激素的含量
would never naturally release. It's far
永远不会自然释放。很远
greater. So melatonin is the signal of
更大。所以褪黑激素是……的信号
darkness. And normally by the morning
黑暗。通常到了早上
hours, our natural release of melatonin
小时，我们体内褪黑激素的自​​然释放
has stopped and you're down to zero
已经停止，你的余额降至零。
levels again
水平再次提升
&gt;&gt; in the morning.
在早晨。
&gt;&gt; In the morning. So, [clears throat] you
在早晨。所以，[清嗓子]你
wake up and your body no longer has the
醒来后，你的身体不再拥有……
signal of melatonin saying it's night,
褪黑激素发出夜晚来临的信号
it's night, it's night. But if you've
夜幕降临，夜幕降临。但是如果你有
dosed yourself with 10 milligs or 20
你给自己服用了10毫克或20毫克
milligs of melatonin, you run the risk
服用毫克褪黑素，你就有风险
of saying, well, yes, I know it quote
说，“嗯，是的，我知道”
unquote knocks me out. But the problem
让我晕倒了。但问题是
is in the first, you know, 3 or 4 hours
是在最初的3到4个小时里。
of the waking morning, you're struggling
清晨醒来，你感到很挣扎。
because you're in this fog of a hormonal
因为你正处于荷尔蒙波动带来的迷雾之中
melatonin, a hormonal signal saying it's
褪黑激素，一种表明身体处于什么状态的激素信号
still pitch black. No, it's not. It's
依然一片漆黑。不，不是。它是
bright light outside, but your body is
外面阳光明媚，但你的身体却
fooled into thinking it's pitch black
被误导，以为外面漆黑一片。
because you've dosed yourself too high.
因为你服用的剂量过高了。
And no wonder you're reaching for two or
难怪你会伸手去拿两把或两把。
three cups of coffee in the morning. So,
早上三杯咖啡。所以，
what what dose of melatonin should I be
我应该服用多少剂量的褪黑素？
taking?
服用？
&gt;&gt; Somewhere between probably about 0.1 to
大概在 0.1 到 之间
3 millig.
3 毫克。
&gt;&gt; And do you advise melatonin for people?
您会建议人们服用褪黑素吗？
&gt;&gt; Yes, in two conditions. The first or
是的，但有两个条件。第一个或
circumstances I should say. The first is
应该说，是在这样的情况下。第一个是
when you're going through jet lag.
当你经历时差反应时。
Wonderfully helpful. But timing is
非常有帮助。但时机很重要
critical. You need to create that sort
批判的。你需要创建那个排序
of that artificial signal of night
那夜里的人造信号
because let's say that you and I here in
因为假设你和我在这里
Los Angeles, we're both going to fly
洛杉矶，我们俩都要飞。
back to London tomorrow and London is 8
明天返回伦敦，伦敦现在是8点。
hours ahead. So, we fly overnight. We
几个小时后。所以，我们乘坐夜间航班。我们
arrive in London and then that first
抵达伦敦后，首先
night, let's say we decide to go to bed
晚上，假设我们决定睡觉
uh or I decide to go to bed in the hotel
或者我决定回酒店睡觉。
at midnight. The problem is here in Los
午夜时分。问题出在洛杉矶这里。
Angeles and my body clock, it's still
安吉利斯和我的生物钟，它仍然
400 p.m. because London's 8 hours ahead.
下午 4 点因为伦敦比这里早8个小时。
So, my melatonin is not going to rise
所以，我的褪黑激素水平不会上升。
for probably another 6 or 7 hours. So, I
可能还要再过六七个小时。所以，我
need to artificially hijack my melatonin
需要人为地劫持我的褪黑激素
system and tell my brain, "Oh, no, it's
系统告诉我的大脑，“哦，不，是……”
not 400 p.m. It's instead it's
不是下午 4 点。而是……
midnight." And so, there under
午夜。”于是，就在那里
conditions of jet lag, very helpful. The
缓解时差反应非常有帮助。这
second is if you have a circadian rhythm
第二点是，如果你有昼夜节律的话
disorder. Let's say that you're someone
紊乱。假设你是某人
who has a an advanced circadian phase.
昼夜节律相位提前的人。
What that means is you're someone who
这意味着你是这样的人
really can't get sleepy until 3 or 4 in
直到凌晨三四点才能真正睡着。
the morning and you would prefer to be
早上，你更愿意……
sleeping throughout most of the day. So
一天大部分时间都在睡觉。所以
you you're almost nocturnal.
你几乎是夜行动物。
&gt;&gt; Is that a genetic disorder?
那是一种遗传性疾病吗？
&gt;&gt; And yes, it's a genetic disorder in
是的，这是一种遗传性疾病。
part.
部分。
&gt;&gt; How many people have that? probably one
有多少人拥有那种东西？可能一个
to two% of the population have a very
约有百分之二的人口患有非常严重的疾病。
severe adv what we call an advanced
严重的疾病，我们称之为高级疾病
circadian phase disorder but their
昼夜节律紊乱，但他们
melatonin can also be helpful because
褪黑素也可能有所帮助，因为
once again their melatonin part of their
再次，褪黑激素成为他们的一部分
problem is that their melatonin is very
问题是他们的褪黑素含量非常高。
delayed so they don't get the signal of
延迟，所以他们收不到信号
oh it's night until maybe 4:00 in the
哦，现在大概要到凌晨四点才亮灯。
morning you and I we start to get our
早上好，你和我，我们开始……
signal of melatonin depending on our
褪黑激素信号取决于我们的
chronotype by somewhere between about 9
生物钟类型大约在9岁左右
10 or 11 p.m. they may be delayed by 5
晚上10点或11点他们可能会延迟5天。
hours. So if we can give them melatonin,
小时。所以如果我们能给他们服用褪黑素，
we can artificially try to fool their
我们可以人为地尝试欺骗他们
brain into thinking it's actually
让大脑认为它实际上是
earlier in their biological rhythm. So
在生物节律的早期阶段。所以
they sleep earlier and they're more in
他们睡得早，而且更投入
sync with the rest of society.
与社会其他成员保持同步。
&gt;&gt; How does someone know if they're that
一个人怎么知道自己是不是那样的人呢？
type of person if they have that
如果他们有那种特质的话，那就是那种人。
disorder? Is there there's not a way to
紊乱？难道没有办法吗？
test, is there?
有测试吗？
&gt;&gt; Well, what we typically do is we will
嗯，我们通常的做法是……
bring you into a laboratory and we will
带你到实验室，我们将
measure your innate level. So we will
衡量你的先天水平。所以我们会
shut out sort of all windows. All clock
几乎把所有窗户都关上了。所有时钟
faces are gone and we just let you run
面孔已然消失，我们只好放你逃走。
your natural rhythm.
你自然的节奏。
&gt;&gt; And they have the same rise and fall in
它们的涨落规律相同
melatonin just like you and I do. Except
就像你我一样，体内也需要褪黑素。除了
where it's doing that rise and fall of
它在那里经历着兴衰
melatonin on the 24-hour clock face is
24小时制时钟上的褪黑素是
radically different.
截然不同。
&gt;&gt; Okay?
好的？
&gt;&gt; For you and I, it's, you know, 910 p.m.
对你我而言，现在是晚上9点10分。
11:00 p.m. at night when we're starting
晚上11点晚上我们开始的时候
that melatonin crescendo.
褪黑激素分泌达到顶峰。
&gt;&gt; For them, it's 4:00 in the morning. So,
对他们来说，现在是凌晨4点。所以，
we can measure it. It's not in their
我们可以测量它。不在他们的计划之内
minds. It's not their choice. It's a
思想。这不是他们能选择的。这是一个
biological edict.
生物学法则。
&gt;&gt; Are you concerned that melatonin is
您是否担心褪黑素？
becoming more and more popular as a way
越来越受欢迎
to solve lifestyle issues that have
解决生活方式方面的问题
caused sleep impairment? Because I'm
是否导致睡眠障碍？因为我
seeing loads of, you know, I'm an
看到很多，你知道，我是一个
investor, so I see lots of companies now
投资者，所以我现在看到很多公司
pitching me different products that have
他们向我推销各种不同的产品，这些产品……
melatonin in them as a sort of
它们体内的褪黑素就像一种
day-to-day sleeping supplement.
日常睡眠补充剂。
&gt;&gt; I think I'm really torn. I've been on
我感觉自己非常纠结。我一直在……
both sides of this argument and I'm
双方都同意这种观点，我
cautious about it for two reasons. The
出于两个原因，我对此持谨慎态度。这
first is in pediatric populations here
首先是儿科人群。
in the United States.
在美国。
&gt;&gt; Pediatric
儿科
&gt;&gt; Yeah. So the people's use of melatonin
是的。所以人们对褪黑素的使用
in kids is increasing. So in pediatric
儿童患病率正在上升。所以在儿科
populations it's increasing
人口正在增加
exponentially. And in fact, if you go
呈指数级增长。事实上，如果你去
down the sort of the supermarket aisles
沿着超市的过道
here in America, often if you go into
在美国，通常如果你进入
sort of the the health sort of food
某种健康食品
section, there's this big purple
区域内有一大片紫色区域
section. That's the melatonin section.
部分。这是褪黑素部分。
And a large proportion of that is there
其中很大一部分就在那里。
dedicated to gummies for your children
专为您的孩子打造的软糖
with melatonin.
含褪黑素。
And there was a study that was published
而且还有一项研究发表出来。
about three years ago that showed here
大约三年前，这里就出现过这种情况。
in America over the past 10 years there
过去十年间，美国……
has been a 53% [clears throat]
已经达到 53% [清嗓子]
increase in poisonous overdose
中毒过量病例增加
admissions to hospitals of melatonin in
因服用褪黑素而入院的人数
the past 10 years. 503%
过去十年。 503%
increase. So firstly, we've got to be a
增加。所以首先，我们必须成为
bit careful. The second reason is that
小心点。第二个原因是：
melatonin is a bioactive hormone and
褪黑激素是一种生物活性激素，
it's also involved in reproductive
它也与生殖有关
development. And there studies done back
发展。而且之前也有相关的研究。
in the 1970s I think where they were
我认为他们在20世纪70年代的地方
looking at juvenile male rats which is
观察幼年雄性大鼠，即
to say male rats who are going through
也就是说，正在经历的雄性老鼠
adolescence
青春期
and they were dosing them with high
他们给他们服用了高剂量的药物。
amounts of melatonin and what they found
褪黑激素的含量以及他们的发现
is that that stunted the development of
正是这一点阻碍了……的发展
the testes of the testicles and it
睾丸的睾丸和它
caused testicular atrophy. Now, these
导致睾丸萎缩。现在，这些
were very high doses, but we've got to
剂量非常高，但我们必须
be a little bit careful. We think we
稍微小心点。我们认为我们
say, "Well, melatonin is a natural
比如说，“褪黑素是一种天然的……”
hormone, so anything natural is safe."
“激素，所以任何天然的东西都是安全的。”
Melatonin overall in terms of its safety
总体而言，褪黑素的安全性
profile is very safe. It's actually a
个人资料非常安全。实际上，这是一个
very good antioxidant.
非常好的抗氧化剂。
But you've got to be careful because
但你必须小心，因为
things like for example testosterone
例如睾酮之类的东西
supplementation in males what we know is
男性补充剂方面，我们目前所知的是
that if you're injecting testosterone
如果你正在注射睾酮
after a while after maybe 18 months or
过了一段时间，大概18个月后，或者
so the testicles themselves will stop
所以睾丸本身就会停止跳动。
producing their own testosterone and
它们自身会产生睾酮，
even if you stop the administration of
即使你停止管理
the exogenous testosterone the injection
注射外源性睾酮
the testes never return their function
睾丸的功能永远无法恢复。
of producing testosterone.
产生睾酮。
Now, we don't have any evidence yet that
目前，我们还没有任何证据表明
that's the case that if you keep taking
如果你继续服用，情况就是这样。
melatonin at high dose, your body, the
高剂量褪黑素对你的身体有何影响？
fear would be shuts down its own natural
恐惧会使其自身的自然状态关闭。
production of melatonin. I've seen no
褪黑激素的产生。我没见过
evidence of that. In fact, I've seen
有证据支持这一点。事实上，我见过
evidence the contrary that even after
有相反的证据表明，即使在……之后
about 6 months or even 12 months in
大约6个月甚至12个月
certain small cities, when you stop
某些小城市，当你停下来的时候
melatonin, the production starts again
褪黑激素的分泌又开始了。
naturally. It seems fine. Problem is,
自然。看起来没问题。问题是，
people haven't been taking melatonin for
人们服用褪黑素的时间并不长
just 12 months. They've been taking it
仅仅12个月。他们一直在服用它
for years.
多年来。
We've got no idea what happens after
我们完全不知道之后会发生什么。
years.
年。
&gt;&gt; That was my hesitation when the first
这就是我第一次犹豫的原因。
time someone offered me melatonin is
有人给我提供褪黑素的那次是
from doing this podcast and speaking to
通过制作这个播客和与……交谈
smart people like yourself, I've come to
像你这样聪明的人，我来这里是为了……
learn this sort of principle that if you
学习这种原则，如果你
start making something for your body in
开始为你的身体制作一些东西
terms of a hormone, if you start sort of
从激素的角度来看，如果你开始……
um consuming something externally like
嗯，比如从外部消费一些东西
testosterone, your body will say fine, I
睾酮水平正常的话，你的身体会告诉你没问题。
don't need to do this. It will try and
不需要这样做。它会尝试……
return to that level of balance where
回到那种平衡状态
the quantities in your system are
你系统中的数量是
maintained, which means it kind of
保持，这意味着它有点
learns to shut down. And I always think
学会关闭。我总是觉得
about the case of testosterone because
关于睾酮的案例，因为
men know that if we start injecting
男人们都知道，如果我们开始注射
testosterone then we're going to have to
如果睾酮水平高，我们就不得不……
pretty much do it forever.
几乎会一直这样做下去。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; Um if we want those levels to be the
嗯，如果我们想让这些级别达到……
same.
相同的。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. That's the worry is that there are
是的。令人担忧的是，有……
no free lunches in biology and usually
生物学领域没有免费的午餐，而且通常
if you fight biology you typically lose.
如果你与生物本能作斗争，通常都会失败。
&gt;&gt; There's always a tradeoff and some of my
凡事都有利弊，而我的一些……
friends often like talk to me about like
朋友们经常喜欢和我谈论类似的事情
these miracle things or this thing or
这些奇迹般的事物，或者这个事物，或者
take medafanol and everything will be
服用美达凡诺，一切都会好起来的。
fine and da but what's the trade-off?
很好，但是有什么权衡取舍呢？
And I get most concerned when they say
而当他们说……时，我最担心。
there isn't one
没有一个
&gt;&gt; cuz then I go we don't know it.
因为然后我就想，糟了，我们都不知道。
[laughter]
[笑声]
&gt;&gt; Yeah, you've got to be careful because
是的，你得小心点，因为
absence of evidence is not evidence of
缺乏证据并不等于没有证据
absence.
缺席。
&gt;&gt; Be very careful when you're doing that
做这件事的时候一定要非常小心。
deal with with your physiology. So to
处理好你的生理问题。所以
come back to sort of the three things,
回到这三件事上来，
the first thing we were mentioning is
我们首先提到的是
digital detox and don't worry about the
进行数码戒断，别担心
blue light. Worry about light in
蓝光。担心光线问题
general. I'll come on to that because
一般的。我稍后会谈到这一点，因为
that's the second. But Michael Gratazar
这是第二个。但迈克尔·格拉塔扎尔
as I was saying what he found is that
正如我刚才所说，他发现的是……
the blue light doesn't really disrupt
蓝光并不会真正干扰生活。
your sleep. It's a combination of first
你的睡眠。这是第一点的组合
these devices that we use are attention
我们使用这些设备是为了吸引注意力。
capture devices and they are designed to
采集设备，它们的设计目的是为了
fleece you of your attention economy and
榨干你的注意力经济
they do it ruthlessly well. They've
他们做得非常出色，而且毫不留情。他们有
spent tens of millions of dollars
花费了数千万美元
designing these products to do that. So
设计这些产品就是为了实现这一目标。所以
what happens is that these devices
这些设备发生的情况是……
become hugely activating and as a result
变得极具激活性，结果
they essentially will be a mute button
它们本质上就是一个静音按钮
on your sleepiness. So you could be
关于你的困倦。所以你可能是
there, you get into bed, it's 11 p.m.
就这样，你躺到床上，已经是晚上11点了。
You think, I am so tired. I was falling
你心想，我好累啊。我正在坠落
asleep on the the the couch watching
睡在沙发上看着
television and then you get into bed,
看完电视就上床睡觉了。
you start going onto social media and
你开始使用社交媒体，
then you start doom scrolling and then
然后你就开始刷末日滚动条，然后
you get into this what we call bed
你进入我们称之为床的这种地方
rotting where you just sit there and now
你坐在那里，看着它腐烂，现在
you look at the clock and it's no longer
你看了一眼钟，时间已经过去了。
11 p.m. It's 1:00 a.m. and you've just
晚上11点现在是凌晨1点，你刚刚
done sleep procrastination. Now it turns
不再拖延睡眠了。现在轮到我了
out that it's yes that that these are
结果表明，这些都是……
attentiongrabbing devices that will mute
引人注目的设备会静音
your sleepiness, but you have to be of a
你的困倦，但你必须是……
certain personality type. He found not
某种特定性格类型。他没有找到
all of us are vulnerable to this sleep
我们所有人都容易受到这种睡眠的影响
disruption of devices. You have to be
设备故障。你必须是
someone who is perhaps neurotic, someone
一个可能有点神经质的人，一个
who has high impulsivity or someone who
冲动性强的人，或者
is perhaps high anxious. If you are of
可能焦虑程度较高。如果您是
any of those kinds, you should be really
任何一种类型，你都应该非常注意。
careful about your use of technology in
谨慎使用科技产品
the bedroom. Now, for me to, you know,
卧室。现在，对我来说，你知道，
sit here and say, look, put your phone
坐在这里说，看，把你的手机放在这里
in the car, in the garage, and that way,
在车里，在车库里，就是这样，
you know, that's what I would love
你知道，那正是我想要的。
because what we've learned to do in this
因为我们在这其中学到了什么
modern era is the first thing when you
现代是当你……时首先要考虑的。
wake up, what is it that you do?
醒醒吧，你平时都做些什么？
&gt;&gt; No, no comment. [laughter]
无可奉告。 [笑声]
&gt;&gt; Lots of you.
你们当中很多人都这样。
&gt;&gt; You,
你，
&gt;&gt; it's just you and I, Stephen. Um,
斯蒂芬，只有你和我。嗯，
&gt;&gt; I grab my phone before my eyes are even
我还没睁开眼就抓起了手机。
open. And what happens is this sort of
打开。然后就会出现这种情况
small tsunami of anxiety washes over you
一股小小的焦虑浪潮席卷而来。
because as soon as you unlock the phone,
因为一旦你解锁手机，
it's everyone else's agenda for your day
这是其他人对你一天的安排。
but your own. And it's a terrible way to
但你自己的。这是一种糟糕的方式
wake up. Have you ever had the
醒醒。你有没有过这样的经历？
experience where you've got to wake up
体验那种你必须醒来的感觉
for an early morning flight? And it's a
赶早班飞机吗？而且它
critical flight. You know that that
关键航班。你知道那
night is not going to be a good night of
今晚不会是个好夜晚。
sleep. It's going to be a shallow kind
睡觉。这将是一种肤浅的……
of sleep. It's what we call anticipatory
睡眠。这就是我们所说的预期
anxiety. You are anticipating an anxious
焦虑。你正期待着一场焦虑的
event in the morning. And studies have
上午的活动。研究表明
shown that when we create this
这表明，当我们创建这个时
anticipatory anxiety, the amount of deep
预期性焦虑，即深度焦虑的程度。
sleep that you have drops significantly.
你的睡眠时间明显减少。
You don't sleep as well. And therefore,
你睡眠质量不好。因此，
if we just do this little sort of
如果我们做这种小事的话
version, this lit version of the morning
版本，这个轻柔版的早晨
flight, which is we know that when we go
飞行，也就是说，我们知道当我们去
to bed and we put our phone down, we
我们上床睡觉，放下手机，我们
know that when we wake up every morning,
要知道，当我们每天早上醒来时，
we're just going to open it up to that
我们打算就此开放。
hit of anxiety every morning. No wonder
每天早上都会感到焦虑。怪不得
our sleep can start to get shallow. Now,
我们的睡眠可能会开始变浅。现在，
I'm not going to sit here and say,
我不会坐在这里说，
"Well, don't take your phone into the
“嗯，别把手机带进去。”
bedroom because the genie is out the
因为精灵被赶出了卧室
bottle and no matter what I say, it's
瓶子，不管我说什么，它都是
not going back in anytime soon." And a
近期内不会再回去了。”而且
friend of mine, Michael Brander, has got
我的朋友迈克尔·布兰德有
this beautiful uh framework where he
这个美丽的框架，他
says you can take your phone into your
他说你可以把手机带进你的
bedroom. It's fine.
卧室。没关系。
But you can only use your phone
但你只能使用你的手机
standing up.
站起来。
[laughter]
[笑声]
&gt;&gt; What's his name?
他叫什么名字？
&gt;&gt; Michael Grande. He's brilliant.
迈克尔·格兰德。他才华横溢。
&gt;&gt; Mind his own business.
管好你自己的事。
&gt;&gt; And and what happens is that you you're
然后发生的事情是，你……
there and you think after about seven or
在那里，你觉得大约七点或之后……
eight minutes, I'm just I'm just going
八分钟，我这就走
to have a bit of a sit down here. as
想在这里坐下来休息一会儿。作为
soon as that phone goes away. So I would
手机一离开。所以我会
say that digital detox is the first
据说，数字排毒是第一个
friend that will really help your sleep.
一位能真正帮助你入睡的朋友。
The the second is regularity. And we'll
第二点是规律性。我们将
come on to regularity when we speak
我们说话时要讲究规律。
about you know what really makes for
你知道真正构成……的是什么吗？
good sleep. If you were to only do one
睡个好觉。如果你只能做一件事
thing, not three things, but just one
一件事，不是三件事，而是一件。
thing. Go to bed and wake up at the same
事物。每天按时睡觉，按时起床
time. No matter whether it's the weekday
时间。无论是不是工作日
or the weekend, regularity is king.
或者说，对于周末来说，规律性才是王道。
&gt;&gt; Okay. So that's the third pillar. That's
好的。这是第三个支柱。那是
correct. Regularity.
正确的。规律性。
&gt;&gt; Okay. And then I have
好的。然后我还有
the T for timing.
T 代表时间。
&gt;&gt; Correct.
正确的。
&gt;&gt; Which we'll go through these. Um
我们将逐一介绍这些内容。嗯
quantity, which we've talked a little
数量，我们之前也稍微谈过。
bit about already, and quality.
已经有一些内容了，而且质量也不错。
&gt;&gt; Correct. So when I looked at the
正确的。所以当我查看……
science, for me, I created this
对我而言，科学是我创造的。
framework of the four macros of good
良好四大宏观框架
sleep. You've heard of the three macros
睡觉。你听说过三大宏吗？
of food, macronutrients, fat, protein,
食物、宏量营养素、脂肪、蛋白质
carbohydrate. To me, there are four
糖类。在我看来，有四个
macros of good sleep. And it's QQQRT.
良好睡眠的要素。是 QQQRT。
QQRT and it stands for quantity,
QQRT，它代表数量（quantity）。
quality,
质量，
regularity,
规律性，
and timing. And think of it less like
以及时机。别太在意这些
pillars, but the four legs of a chair.
柱子，但椅子的四条腿。
And if any one of these becomes
如果其中任何一个变成
unstable, the chair will topple over.
椅子不稳，会翻倒。
So, I'll probably start with the one
所以，我大概会从第一个开始。
that people have heard me bang on about,
人们都听我唠叨过这件事，
which is quantity. 7 to 9 hours. This
即数量。 7至9小时。这
myth of 8 hours is nonsense. It's a
八小时工作制的说法纯属无稽之谈。这是一个
wonderful range. 7 to 9 hours. And what
种类繁多。 7至9小时。还有什么
we know is that using that sweet spot of
我们知道的是，利用那个最佳平衡点
7 to 9 hours, when you get less than
7到9小时，当你睡眠时间少于
that, the shorter your sleep, the
也就是说，睡眠时间越短，
shorter your life.
缩短你的寿命。他妈的。
&gt;&gt; Short sleep predicts all cause
睡眠不足预示着所有原因
mortality. Now, we say that there's the
死亡。现在，我们说这里有……
minimum of 7 hours of sleep. And some
至少7小时睡眠。还有一些
people have argued perhaps correctly
人们的论点或许是正确的。
that look, if you look at these
那种眼神，如果你看看这些
mortality curves, there's not much of a
死亡率曲线，并没有太多的
percentage difference between sleeping
睡眠百分比差异
six hours versus the seven that you're
六小时对比七小时
telling me is minimum. So 6 hours is
告诉我一声是最低限度。所以6小时是
just fine. So all of this nonsense and
很好。所以，所有这些胡说八道……
rhetoric is is is silly from you. And I
你的这种修辞手法很愚蠢。我
think they've made a conflation
认为他们混淆了
because
因为
7 hours is the minimum amount of sleep
7 小时是最低睡眠时间。
that you need to survive. Because the
你需要生存下去。因为
way that we quantify what minimum is is
我们量化最小值的方法是
based on whether you die or you don't
取决于你是否死亡
prematurely,
过早地，
the amount of sleep that you need to
你需要多少睡眠
survive is different than the amount of
生存与数量是不同的。
sleep that you need to thrive. And
充足的睡眠，让你活力充沛。和
people will conflate the former with the
人们会将前者与后者混淆
latter. So you've got to be careful when
后者。所以你得小心点
people are sort of touting on social
人们在社交媒体上有点炫耀的意味
media saying, "Well, no, but look, you
媒体说，“好吧，不，但是你看，你
there's not much difference between my
我的和我的之间没有太大区别。
sort of survival rate on 6 hours versus
6 小时生存率与
7 hours." You may have a just as much of
7 小时。”你可能也有同样多的时间
a long life, but the quality of your
寿命长短，但你的生活质量如何？
life will be very different. So that's
生活将截然不同。就是这样。
quantity 7 to n hours. And is that does
数量 7 到 n 小时。确实如此
it change for parents, by the way?
顺便问一下，这对父母来说会有什么变化吗？
Because I've met so many parents that
因为我见过太多这样的父母了
seem to be functioning better than me
他们似乎比我更胜任。
and they've got four they're having like
他们有四个孩子，他们正在筹备。
four or five hours sleep. Did evolution
睡眠四到五个小时。进化论
not give parents any leeway or anything
不要给父母任何回旋余地或任何机会
when they have kids that suddenly their
当他们有了孩子，突然间他们的
brain changes and now they can survive
大脑发生变化，现在它们可以存活下来了
with less sleep? The evidence doesn't
睡眠不足？证据并不充分。
suggest that once you go through
建议你一旦完成
parenthood, you get some magic sort of,
为人父母，你会感受到某种神奇的力量。
you know, immunity shot that makes you,
你知道，那种能让你获得免疫力的注射剂，
you know, resilient and not vulnerable
你知道，坚韧不拔，不易受伤
to a lack of sleep. And in some ways you
睡眠不足导致的。在某些方面，你
could argue because we used to, you
可以争辩，因为我们以前是这样，你
know, live as a collective tribe and we
知道，像一个集体部落一样生活，我们
would share duties at that point, you
届时你们将分担职责。
know, mother nature doesn't really worry
你知道，大自然母亲其实并不担心。
too much about you now because you've
现在关于你的事太多了，因为你已经
already procreated and you've passed on
你已经生育子女，并且去世了。
your genetic code. So you are now the
你的基因密码。所以你现在是
the sort of the you know the not
你知道的那种不
particularly well you know cured for
尤其清楚，已经治愈了
individual through evolution. It's your
个体通过进化而来。这是你的
offspring gets
后代获得
&gt;&gt; so it sacrifices you in a way. I mean
所以从某种意义上说，它是在牺牲你。我是说
that's what we see in the animal
这就是我们在动物身上看到的。
kingdom. Did you see that documentary
王国。你看过那部纪录片吗？
about the octopus?
关于章鱼？
&gt;&gt; Yeah, it it was just I mean I thought it
是啊，我的意思是，我当时就是这么想的。
was beautiful documentary but um
纪录片拍得很好，但是……
&gt;&gt; the TLDDR for anyone that hasn't seen it
给还没看过的人的简要总结
is once the octop and I'm going to
曾经是章鱼，而我要去
completely butcher this so please ignore
请忽略这段文字，它完全被毁坏了。
um once the octopus has given birth it
嗯，章鱼产仔后……
dies. Basically it doesn't move out of
死亡。基本上它不会移出
that hole and it dies. Is that a rough?
它钻进那个洞里就死了。这是草稿吗？
&gt;&gt; Well, I don't know if if it dies, but
我不知道它会不会死，但是
its level of of active life.
它的活跃生活水平。
&gt;&gt; I searched, does the octopus die after
我搜索了一下，章鱼死后会怎么样？
reproduction, and it says yes. Female
繁殖，答案是肯定的。女性
octopuses die after their eggs hatch.
章鱼卵孵化后，它们就会死亡。
After laying eggs, a female stops eating
雌性产卵后便停止进食。
and devotes all of her energy to
并将她所有的精力都投入到
protecting and oxygenating them until
保护和供氧直至
they hatch. Once they do, she dies
它们孵化了。一旦他们这么做了，她就死了。
shortly after, a process called semiol
不久之后，一种称为半醇的过程
parity, meaning they reproduce only
奇偶性，意味着它们只会繁殖
once. This death is triggered by hormone
一次。这种死亡是由激素引发的。
changes from the optic gland similar to
视腺的变化类似于
mamalian proterty glands. And males die
哺乳动物前体腺。男性死亡
shortly after mating as well, usually
通常也是在交配后不久。
within a few months.
几个月之内。
That is wild
真是太疯狂了
&gt;&gt; in some ways. It's, you know, it's it's
在某些方面。你知道，就是，就是
tragic and it reminds me I'm so glad
真是悲剧，这让我更加庆幸
that I'm not an octopus. But [laughter]
我不是章鱼。但是[笑声]
but but coming back to it, so for there
但是，回到正题，所以，就那里而言
doesn't seem to be some you know magic
似乎不是什么魔法。
cloak of invincibility that you put on
你穿上的那件无敌斗篷
when you go through parenthood.
当你经历为人父母的过程。
Certainly what we know is that the
我们确切知道的是，
number of individuals who can survive on
能够生存下来的个体数量
6 hours of sleep or less and show no
睡眠时间少于6小时且未表现出任何症状
impairment in either their brain or
大脑或
their body rounded to a whole number and
他们的身体四舍五入到整数，
expressed as a percent of the population
以占总人口的百分比表示
is zero.
为零。
So quantity matters but it turns out
所以数量固然重要，但结果却并非如此
that we got it wrong in thinking that
我们之前的想法是错误的。
was the only thing because then came
那是唯一的事，因为后来就发生了
quality. So QQRT quality is defined in
质量。因此，QQRT质量的定义如下：
sleep science as two things. The first
睡眠科学包含两方面。第一个
is something that your sleep tracker
这是你的睡眠追踪器所包含的内容
will measure which is the continuity of
将测量哪个是连续性
your sleep. Meaning do you sleep in one
你的睡眠。意思是说，你睡在一间房里吗？
or two nice long bouts throughout the
或者在比赛中打出两场精彩的长回合
night? That's good quality of sleep,
夜晚？这是良好的睡眠质量。
nice continuous bouts versus your sort
精彩的连续战斗，对抗你这种类型的对手。
of sleep is very fragmented by all of
睡眠非常零碎，这都是各种因素造成的。
these awakenings. That's very poor
这些觉醒。那太差了
quality of sleep. And the way that you
睡眠质量。以及你的方式
can measure it in your sleep tracker is
可以在你的睡眠追踪器中测量。
just by looking at the app. And there'll
仅仅通过查看应用程序。而且还会有
be something called sleep efficiency.
可以称之为睡眠效率。
Sleep efficiency is defined as the
睡眠效率定义为
following. Of the time that you're in
下列的。在你所在的这段时间里
bed, what percent of that time is spent
床上，其中有多少百分比的时间是用来睡觉的
asleep? And what we like to see is you
睡着了吗？我们想看到的是你
north of 85% or above. So, this is kind
高于 85% 或以上。所以，这是一种
of like the users's guide to sleep
就像睡眠用户指南一样
trackers. What I want to see is 85% or
追踪器。我希望看到的是85%或
more. If you're less than that, we need
更多的。如果你的分数低于这个标准，我们需要
to have a conversation. That's number
进行一次对话。那是数字
one, good quality of sleep. The second,
第一，良好的睡眠质量。第二，
which is what sort of what these
这就是这些的什么类型
trackers can't really do, but I can do
追踪器做不到这一点，但我可以做到。
in the sleep laboratory when you look
在睡眠实验室里，当你观察
like a spaghetti monster cuz I put
就像意大利面条怪兽一样，因为我放了
electrodes all over your head. [snorts]
头部遍布电极。 [嗤笑]
I can measure the quality of your big,
我可以衡量你大的质量，
deep, slow brain waves of deep non-REM
深度非快速眼动睡眠的深层、缓慢的脑电波
sleep. And that is a second measure. The
睡觉。这是第二项措施。这
power of those big slow brain waves.
那些缓慢而强大的脑电波的力量。
That's a second measure. And quality
这是第二项措施。质量
seems to be as predictive as quantity in
似乎与数量一样具有预测性
making a difference not just to your all
不仅对你所有人，更要有所作为
cause mortality but quality even more
导致死亡，但生活质量更高
than quantity when it comes to mental
精神层面，数量比数量更重要。
health has been showing the bigger
健康状况已显示出更大的变化。
signal. So again it's not that quantity
信号。所以，问题不在于数量。
doesn't matter. You do have to get
没关系。你确实需要得到
sufficient amounts of sleep but quality
充足的睡眠和高质量的睡眠。
as much as quantity should be paid
应按数量支付相应款项
attention to and I haven't said that
注意，我还没说过
enough.
足够的。
&gt;&gt; Mhm.
嗯。
&gt;&gt; The next is where we came to in our sort
接下来是我们分类过程中遇到的情况。
of three things that I was saying. The
我当时说的三件事。这
first is digital detox. Then next thing
首先是数码戒断。然后是下一件事
I said is regularity.
我说的是规律性。
This is somewhere where I've also
这也是我曾经去过的地方。
changed my mind on. I've doubled down on
我改变了主意。我加倍投入
regularity. There was a study that also
规律性。还有一项研究也
came out of that same data set that I
这些数据都来自我使用的同一个数据集。
described. It's called the UK Bioank
已描述。它被称为英国生物银行
data. And now they didn't look at 90,000
数据。现在他们没看90000美元。
individuals, but they looked at 60,000
但他们研究了60000人。
individuals. And they decided that they
个人。他们决定
were going to compare and split them
我们将对它们进行比较和拆分。
into quartiles. So the most regular to
分成四分位数。所以最常规的
the second most regular to then sort of
第二常见的情况是……
the third most regular and then the
第三大最常规的，然后是
final quartile was those who were the
最后四分之一的人是那些
least regular.
最不规律。
&gt;&gt; And what does regular mean in this
那么，这里的“常规”是什么意思呢？
context?
语境？
&gt;&gt; Good question. highly regular
问得好。高度规律
individuals plus or minus 15 minutes in
个人误差在正负 15 分钟以内
terms of going to bed and waking up at
就寝和起床的条件
the same time. In other words, a total
同时。换句话说，总共
wiggle room of 30 minutes.
有30分钟的缓冲时间。
&gt;&gt; Oh, okay. So, if I'm always going to bed
哦好的。所以，如果我总是上床睡觉
at 9:00 p.m. and I do that 5 days in a
晚上9点我这样做5天
row, I'm regular timing really.
划船，我的时间安排很规律。
&gt;&gt; So, so it's it's regularity in terms of
所以，这就是它的规律性所在
when you're going to bed and waking up.
当你准备睡觉和起床的时候。
&gt;&gt; So, it you're right, it's timing in a
所以，如果你是对的，关键在于时机。
way, but I'll come on to why there is a
一种方法，但我稍后会解释为什么会有这种方法。
separate t for timing in just a second.
单独计时只需一秒钟。
But regularity here was okay, plus or
但这里的规律性还可以接受，或者
minus. So, let's say you go to bed at
减。假设你晚上几点睡觉
8:45 p.m. one night and then 9 and then
晚上8:45一晚，然后是9晚，然后
9:10 p.m. and then you're back to 8.
晚上9点10分然后你就回到了 8。
That's beautiful tight timing. I like
时机把握得真好。我喜欢
that. Whereas the those people who were
那。而那些人
least regular, they were 90 to 120
最不规律的时候，他们有90到120人。
minutes desperate. They were going to
绝望的时刻。他们打算
bed, let's say, at 11 one night, then 1
比如说，某天晚上11点上床睡觉，然后1
a.m. the next night, then they were
第二天凌晨，他们……
going to bed at 10:30 p.m. and then they
晚上10点30分上床睡觉然后他们
were going to bed at 12:30. They were
我们12点半就准备睡觉了。他们是
all over the map. So what they found was
遍布各地。他们发现的是……
that those people who were most regular
那些最常来的人
versus least regular, so they compared
与最不规律的相比，他们进行了比较。
the extremes of these two, those people
这两个极端，这些人
who were most regular had a 49%
最常光顾的人群占49%
relative decrease in all cause
所有原因的相对减少
mortality. So they were 49% less likely
死亡。因此，他们的可能性降低了49%。
to prematurely die than those people who
比那些人更容易过早死亡
were least likely to die. They had a 39%
最不可能死亡。他们占39%
cancer mortality risk reduction. Great.
降低癌症死亡风险。伟大的。
they had a 57%
他们有57%
cardioabolic
心血管代谢
disease risk reduction. So that was
降低疾病风险。就是这样。
stunning. That regularity was incredibly
令人惊叹的。这种规律性令人难以置信
powerful as a predictive signal of your
可以作为预测您未来走势的有力信号。
different forms of mortality. That
不同形式的死亡。那
wasn't the best part of the paper
这不是论文中最好的部分。
though. They had also measured quantity
尽管。他们还测量了数量
as well as regularity in these same
以及这些方面的规律性
individuals. So then they decided to
个人。于是他们决定
say, well, I'm going to take our measure
好吧，我来衡量一下我们之间的关系。
of quantity and regularity and we're
数量和规律性，我们
going to put them both in the same
准备把它们两个放在一起
statistical bucket and do a Coke Pepsi
统计分类，然后进行可口可乐百事
challenge to see which one wins out in
挑战，看看谁能胜出
terms of predicting all cause mortality.
预测全因死亡率的指标。
We all bet in the sleep field, at least
至少在睡眠领域，我们都在下注。
I did, it was going to be quantity. I
没错，我打算追求数量。我
was wrong. Regularity beat out quantity
错了。规律性胜过数量
in predicting all cause mortality and by
在预测全因死亡率方面，
quite some margin. Now that doesn't mean
余地相当大。但这并不意味着
that you can now go away and say, "I'm
现在你可以离开并说：“我是
going to start sleeping 4 hours." but
我打算开始每天睡4个小时。”但是
incredibly consistent 4 hours. You need
非常稳定，持续了4个小时。你需要
both quantity and quality. But goodness
数量和质量都很重要。但天哪
does regularity seem to carry a massive
规律性似乎蕴含着巨大的意义
signal. So coming back to those three
信号。所以，让我们回到这三个问题上来。
things, I would say digital detox, just
我觉得应该提一下数码排毒之类的。
go to bed and wake up at the same time.
每天同一时间睡觉，同一时间起床。
And the final thing is light. In this
最后一点就是光。在此
modern world, we are a dark deprived
现代世界，我们生活在黑暗与匮乏之中。
society.
社会。
We get what I call junk light at night.
晚上我们这里会发出我称之为杂乱灯光的光。
So you've heard of junk DNA. Well, we
所以你听说过垃圾DNA吧。嗯，我们
get junk light at night.
晚上会发出杂乱的光。
We don't need all of this light and it
我们不需要这么多光，而且
fools our brain into thinking it's still
它欺骗我们的大脑，让我们以为它仍然
daytime outside. So no wonder as a
白天在户外。所以，难怪……
society we have some struggles with
我们这个社会面临着一些挑战
sleep at night. Now that's due to many
晚上睡觉。这主要是由于许多原因造成的。
reasons. Stress, too much caffeine,
原因。压力过大，咖啡因摄入过量
alcohol, THC. But excessive light is one
酒精，THC。但光照过强也是一个问题。
of the easiest things that you can do.
你能做的最简单的事情之一。
So for the next 7 days, just do me this
所以接下来的7天，你就帮我做这件事。
experiment. If you can set an alarm 1
实验。如果你能设置一个闹钟 1
hour before your normal bedtime. When
比平时就寝时间提前一小时。什么时候
that alarm goes off, turn off, and I I
警报响了，关掉了，然后我
do this myself, turn off almost all of
我自己动手，把几乎所有东西都关掉。
the lights in your house.
你家里的灯。
&gt;&gt; When you say all of the lights, do you
你说所有的灯，是指……
mean the little red light on my smoke
指的是我烟灰缸上的小红灯
alarm or
警报或
&gt;&gt; No, that's fine. But, you know, so my
不，没关系。但是，你知道，所以我的
wife and I, 1 hour before bed, almost
我和妻子，睡前一小时，几乎
all the lights, we've got sort of this
所有的灯，我们大概就是这样
little set of this sort of light that
一小套这种类型的灯
goes around the television, the back of
绕着电视机，在背面
the television, so it kind of looks like
电视机，所以看起来有点像
the television's cool and illuminated. I
电视机很凉爽，而且灯光很亮。我
will set that down to about 5% of
将其降低到大约5%
brightness and all of the rest of the
亮度以及其他所有
lights out so you can kind of just still
关灯后，你就可以继续待下去了。
see some illumination so I'm not sort
看到一些光线，所以我并不太在意
of, you know, looking desperately uncool
你知道，就是那种看起来极其不酷的感觉。
uh in in front of her when I'm tripping
呃，在我嗑药的时候，就在她面前
over things cuz it's complete black, you
因为一片漆黑，所以对一切都感到厌倦，你
know. Then start cooling the house or
知道。然后开始给房子降温或
the room as best you can to around about
尽可能把房间布置得井井有条。
67 68 Fahrenheit or about 18C. We can
华氏67-68度，约合摄氏18度。我们可以
speak about temperature, but just do
谈论温度，但只是做
this experiment for the next 7 days. 1
接下来的7天将进行这项实验。 1
hour before bed, the alarm goes off. You
睡前一小时，闹钟响了。你
switch off all of the lights and ask the
关掉所有的灯，然后问
following question. Do you feel
接下来的问题。你感觉如何？
sleepier? Is it soporific? Does it make
更困了吗？它有催眠作用吗？它会制造吗？
you feel more sleepy as a result? But
因此你感觉更困了吗？但
don't stop there. What you've gone and
不要就此止步。你已经走了
done is the first positive experiment
第一个积极的实验已经完成。
which is you've gone from the no
也就是说，你已经从“否”变成了“否”。
intervention lights are on to then the
干预灯亮起，然后
Matt's intervention which is now the
马特的介入现在是
lights are off for 1 hour before bed.
睡前关灯一小时。
Don't just ask is my sleep better when
不要只问我“我什么时候睡得更好？”
the lights were out for 1 hour before
停电一小时后
bed. Once that 7-day period has
床。一旦这7天期限结束
finished, go back to doing what you were
搞定了，回去继续做你之前在做的事吧。
doing before, which is keep all of the
之前所做的，就是保留所有的
lights on and ask yourself, did my sleep
开着灯，问问自己，我睡得好吗？
get better when I did the intervention
当我进行干预后情况有所好转。
and did my sleep go back to being worse
我的睡眠状况又变差了吗？
when I stopped? Because I'm trying to
我什么时候停下来的？因为我正试图
teach you birectionality in the
教你双向性
experiment. Does that make some sense?
实验。这样说得通吗？
&gt;&gt; Yeah. So, you get to you get to
是的。所以，你就能……
basically do an AB test.
简单来说就是做个AB测试。
&gt;&gt; Correct. You get to see both sides of
正确的。你可以看到事情的两面。
the equation. And with that, it's more
该方程式。因此，它就更……
proof positive than just one direction
比单向传播更有力的证据
alone. because who knows it could just
独自的。谁知道呢，说不定就这么发生了。
be a placebo effect. So regularity
可能是安慰剂效应。所以规律性
coming back to it is critical. So we've
重新审视这个问题至关重要。所以我们已经
spoken about QQR quantity quality
谈到QQR数量质量
regularity
规律性
&gt;&gt; on the um regular
嗯，定期
&gt;&gt; regularity point. Why what's going on in
规律点。为什么？到底发生了什么？
our brain that's making it from a
我们的大脑正在从……中制造它
hormonal perspective or other that's
从激素角度或其他角度来看
making it important for us to sleep at
因此，对我们来说，睡眠至关重要。
the same time?
同时？
&gt;&gt; It's a bloody great question. People
这真是个绝妙的问题。人们
don't respond to rules. They respond to
不要遵守规则。他们会回应
reasons not rules. So let me try and
理由而非规则。那我就试试吧
explain the reason behind the sort of
解释这种现象背后的原因
the rule. When it comes to regularity,
规则。就规律性而言，
we have something called a circadian
我们有一种叫做昼夜节律的东西
rhythm that we've spoken about. And
我们之前讨论过的节奏。和
there's a clock that sits inside of your
你的身体内部有一个钟。
brain deep in the middle of the brain.
大脑深处，位于大脑中央。
So we have it just turns out a brain
所以，我们发现它原来是一个大脑
here.
这里。
Lovely. Okay. So we've got one of these
迷人的。好的。所以我们有一个这样的
hemispheres here. And then I'm just
这里是半球。然后我就……
going to take out what we call the
我们要取出我们称之为
subcortical sections. So these are the
皮层下切片。所以这些就是
areas that are below the subcortex. So
皮层下区域以下的区域。所以
here is the brain. So this is the front
这就是大脑。这是正面
of the brain, the back of the brain, top
大脑，大脑后部，顶部
of the brain, and here's the brain stem.
这是大脑的一部分，这里是脑干。
And it turns out that right in the
结果发现，就在
middle of the brain, right here, there's
大脑中央，就在这里，有
an area called the hypothalamus.
一个叫做下丘脑的区域。
Now here, this structure here, this is
现在这里，这个结构，这是
the phalamus. This is the sensory gate
阴茎。这是感觉门
of your brain. So all of your five
你的大脑。所以你们五个人
senses, sound, touch, taste, smell, they
感官，听觉、触觉、味觉、嗅觉，它们
all flood into this gate called the
所有东西都涌入这个叫做
phalamus. And then the phalamus will
阴茎。然后，阴茎将
decide whether it sends those sensory
决定是否发送这些感觉信息
signals up to your cortex. And when it
信号传递至大脑皮层。当它
sends the signals up to your cortex, you
它会将信号发送到你的大脑皮层，你
start processing them and you become
开始处理它们，你就会变成
consciously aware of the external world.
对外部世界有意识的感知。
Now, as we're falling asleep, just as an
现在，当我们即将入睡时，就像……
aside, what's interesting is that this
除此之外，有趣的是……
gate, the sensory gate, the phalamus,
门，感觉门，柄状突，
once we start to fall asleep, the gate
一旦我们开始入睡，大门就开了。
will close shut. Now your eyes are
即将关门。现在你的眼睛是
technically still seeing, your ears are
严格来说，你的耳朵仍然能看到东西。
still hearing, your tongue is still
仍然能听到，你的舌头仍然
tasting, but because the gate of the
品尝，但因为大门
phalamus, the sensory gate closes shut,
阴茎，感觉闸门关闭，
those signals that are coming into your
那些进入你体内的信号
brain are no longer sent up to your
大脑不再向你发送信息
cortex. So you stop perceiving the
皮层。所以你不再感知……
outside world, which is just simply a
外部世界，其实就是一个
different way of saying you've fallen
另一种表达你已跌倒的方式
asleep. Now the hypothalamus, you've
睡着了。现在说说下丘脑，你已经……
heard of hypo sort of hypertension or
听说过低血压之类的高血压吗？
sort of you know hypothermia or that
你知道，就是那种体温过低之类的。
means lower. So here's the phalamus.
意味着更低。这就是阴茎。
This area here is called the
这里这片区域被称为
hypothalamus. And it's a tiny structure
下丘脑。而且它还是个很小的结构。
but within that structure contains a
但在该结构内部包含一个
nucleus. And that group of cells the
核。而那群细胞
nucleus has a fancy term and it's called
细胞核有个很专业的术语，叫做
the supraismatic nucleus. But the
上扣带核。但是
superismatic nucleus is your master
上肌核是你的主人
24-hour clock. Every cell in your body
24小时制。你身体里的每一个细胞
has a clock inside of it. But this is
里面有个钟。但这是
the master clock. It's like Lord of the
主时钟。它就像《指环王》
Rings. There's one ring to rule them
戒指。只有一个戒指统治它们
all. Well, there's one clock to rule
全部。嗯，现在只有一个时钟可以统治。
them all. And here in the super
商场。而在这里，超级
chaismatic nucleus, you get the 24-hour
混乱的核心，你将获得24小时
rhythm of being awake and being asleep,
清醒和睡眠的节奏
being awake and being asleep. How does
清醒和睡眠。如何
your brain keep quartzlike precision
你的大脑保持着石英般的精准度
24-hour clock time? How does it do that?
24小时制？它是如何做到的？
The way it does that is that it uses
它实现这一点的方式是利用
signals such as light and dark
诸如光线和黑暗之类的信号
&gt;&gt; from your eyes
从你的眼中
&gt;&gt; from your eye. And so when light comes
来自你的眼睛。所以当光明来临的时候
through the retina, it tells the
它通过视网膜传递信息
hypothalamus it's daytime and therefore
下丘脑现在是白天，因此
you should be awake. And its rhythm
你应该保持清醒。以及它的节奏
starts its awesome sort of upswing. And
开始迎来令人惊叹的上升期。和
temperature can do this and feeding can
温度和喂食都会造成这种影响。
do this all sorts of different things.
做各种各样的事情。
But for the most part, light is the
但大多数情况下，光线是
principal governor that essentially acts
主要治理者，实质上是……
like electrical, I should say, photon
就像电，或者更确切地说，光子
fingers that pops the wristwatch dial
手指戳破腕表表盘
out and resets it precisely. So, 24
将其取出并精确重置。所以，24
hours every single day. Because if
每天都要花好几个小时。因为如果
you're left in the dark with no signals
你被蒙在鼓里，没有任何信号。
of light, your clock isn't precise. It
光线不足，你的时钟就不准了。它
drifts to about 24 hours and 15 minutes.
漂移至约 24 小时 15 分钟。
So, you start going forward a little bit
所以，你开始向前走一点。
every single day if you go into a cave.
每天都要去山洞。
And people have done this experiment.
人们已经做过这个实验了。
The thing that keeps it precise is
保持其精确性的因素是
light. So, you need light to keep a
光。所以，你需要光照来保持……
beautiful 24-hour rhythm. One of those
美丽的24小时节奏。其中之一
things that's under the control of your
那些在你掌控之中的事情
24-hour rhythm is your sleep wake cycle.
24小时节律就是你的睡眠觉醒周期。
&gt;&gt; What if I'm doing exercise?
如果我在锻炼呢？
&gt;&gt; Exercise is a wonderful entrainer of
运动是极好的训练方法
your circadian rhythm as long as you're
只要你保持昼夜节律，你的昼夜节律就会受到影响。
doing it at the right time. So, if
在合适的时机做这件事。所以，如果
you're starting to exercise at 3:00 or 4
你下午3点或4点开始锻炼。
in the morning, that's not good because
早上那样做不好，因为
that's an activity signal that's going
这是一个正在进行的活动信号
to confuse the brain into thinking it's
使大脑误以为它是
the active period, which is normally
活跃期，通常是
because we're a dional species, the day.
因为我们是多面体物种，每一天。
And it's the same thing coming back to
而回到原点也是如此。
my point of regularity.
我的规律点。
Using light as the best way to help with
利用光是最好的辅助方式
that regularity because light if it's
那种规律性是因为光线（如果它是）
artificial at night fools your brain
夜间的人工效果会欺骗你的大脑
into thinking that it's daytime still
误以为还是白天。
outside.
外部。
&gt;&gt; I mean is there any such thing as
我的意思是，是否存在这样一种情况？
non-artificial light? I mean I mean I
非人工光源？我的意思是，我的意思是，我
guess with the sun but I mean is there a
猜猜太阳怎么样，但我的意思是，有没有……
type of light that I could use at night
我晚上可以用的那种灯
like candles or something or
比如蜡烛之类的东西
&gt;&gt; Yes. below 30 lux,
是的。低于30勒克斯，
&gt;&gt; right,
正确的，
&gt;&gt; is not going to necessarily do you a
未必会对你有帮助
disservice. Probably below 50 lux. Now,
失职。可能低于50勒克斯。现在，
lux lux is just a measure of light
勒克斯（lux）只是光强度的计量单位。
intensity. And you can download on the
强度。您可以在以下位置下载：
app store a free looks meter. And if
应用商店里有一款免费的颜值测量工具。如果
you're an idiot nerd like me, you're
你跟我一样是个笨蛋书呆子，你
going all over the house at night and
晚上在房子里到处乱跑
you're sort of putting it in different
你把它放得有点不一样了。
location, you're seeing any kind of
位置，你看到的任何类型的
white spots here where you know the
这里有一些白点，你知道的
looks is too high, but you need to drop
外貌特征太高了，但你需要降低标准。
that that looks. By the way, it's a
看起来是这样。顺便说一句，这是一个
great way if people want to say, "Look,
如果人们想说“看，
my REM sleep is deficient. How can I get
我的快速眼动睡眠不足。我如何才能获得
more REM sleep?" There's a great study
更多快速眼动睡眠？”有一项很棒的研究
where they did something similar to what
他们做了类似的事情
I'm telling you now. 90 minutes before
我现在就告诉你。 90分钟前
bed, they turned down the lights to
上床后，他们关掉了灯。
below 30 lux, and they pulled out all of
低于30勒克斯，他们把所有的……
the blue light. And just that trick of
蓝光。而这招……
dropping the lights down 90 minutes
灯光调暗90分钟
before bed, below 30 lux, making it warm
睡前，照度低于30勒克斯，感觉很暖和。
yellow light, increased their REM sleep
黄光照射增加了他们的快速眼动睡眠
by 18%. Wow,
增长18%。哇，
&gt;&gt; it's a huge margin. So, no need for
差距巨大。所以，无需
pharmarmacology. But to your question,
药理学。但回到你的问题，
why is regularity
为什么是规律性
important? Well, I told you that light
重要的？我跟你说过那盏灯
is one of the signals that can create
这是能够产生信号的信号之一。
regularity. It turns out that your
规律性。原来你的
behavior is another thing that will tell
行为是另一个可以说明问题的因素。
your brain. So, meaning when you go to
你的大脑。所以，意思是当你去
bed and wake up at the same time, it
同时入睡和起床，
acts like an anchor. It anchors your
起到锚的作用。它锚定了你的
circadian rhythm and it tells you almost
昼夜节律几乎可以告诉你
like a scene in a movie. This scene is
就像电影里的场景一样。这一幕是
now complete. A new scene starts. This
已完成。新的一幕开始了。这
scene is complete. A new scene starts.
场景完成。新的一幕开始了。
So every time that you're going to bed
所以每次你准备睡觉的时候
at the same time and waking up at the
同时，在……醒来
same time, you are feeding the super
与此同时，你正在喂养超级
chaismatic nucleus, the master 24-hour
混沌核心，24小时大师
clock in your brain, you're feeding it
你大脑中的时钟，你正在给它提供信息。
signals of regularity.
规律性的信号。
And when it feeds on signals of
而当它以信号为食时
regularity, it improves the quantity and
规律性可以提高数量和
the quality of your sleep. Your
你的睡眠质量。你的
circadian rhythm likes consistency. It
生物钟喜欢规律性。它
likes regular signals. When you feed it
喜欢规律的信号。当你喂它的时候
signals of light, of activity, of waking
光线、活动和醒来的信号
up, going to bed, you improve the
起床、睡觉，你改善了
quantity and the quality of your sleep.
睡眠的数量和质量。
That's the reason behind the underlying
这就是其根本原因。
rule. So having a TV in your bedroom is
规则。所以，在卧室里放一台电视是
a terrible idea then because if on that
那真是个糟糕的主意，因为如果那样做的话……
behavioral point if I'm getting in bed
如果我上床睡觉，行为上就会出现问题。
but then I'm staying up for 3 hours
但我之后要熬夜3个小时。
watching Netflix my brain is going to be
看Netflix的时候，我的大脑会……
quite confused about like the behavioral
我对行为方面的事情感到很困惑。
pattern of what what I'm doing in my
我正在做的事情的模式
life. It's not going to associate the
生活。它不会与
bed with sleep. It's going to associate
躺在床上睡觉。它将关联
the bed with movies.
床上放着电影。
&gt;&gt; That's one of the problems that we call
这就是我们所说的问题之一。
con it's called conditioned arousal
它被称为条件性唤起
which sounds a lot more salacious than
听起来比这更淫秽。
it actually is. It's a term that we use
确实如此。这是我们使用的术语
in sleep medicine which may explain
在睡眠医学领域，这或许可以解释
insomnia. So with insomnia, let's say
失眠。所以，以失眠为例……
that the first time you go to this thing
你第一次去这个地方的时候
called a dentist and you get in the
给牙医打电话，然后你就进去了。
chair and it's kind of cool. You're
椅子，还挺酷的。你是
reclined back and you know you think
向后靠去，你知道你在想什么
this is fine. But then after about 14 or
这样可以。但大约14岁或之后
15 visits when you get into that chair
当你坐上那张椅子时，需要去15次。
you are no longer looking forward to
你不再期待
getting into that chair, are you? Why?
你要坐到那把椅子上吗？为什么？
because you've learned the association
因为你已经了解了这种关联
that being in that chair typically leads
坐在那把椅子上通常会导致
to a bad outcome. [laughter]
结果很糟糕。 [笑声]
Now, the same thing is true with the
现在，同样的情况也适用于……
bed. If you start associating the bed
床。如果你开始把床与床联系起来
with anything other than sleep, and we
除了睡眠之外的任何事情，我们
give you a pass in terms of sex, but
在性方面我会放过你，但是……
sleep and sex, anything other than that,
除了睡眠和性之外，其他任何事情
you start to learn that this thing
你开始明白这件事
called my bed is this place where I'm
我称之为床的地方就是我所在的地方
awake, where I work, where I eat, where
醒来，我工作的地方，我吃饭的地方，哪里
we have conversations, where I watch
我们进行对话，我观看
television. And so, you know, if I were
电视。所以，你知道，如果我是
to, and again, I'm stealing Michael
还有，我又在偷迈克尔了
Grand's point, but if I were to say to
格兰德的观点，但如果我说……
you, bed sleep, bed sleep, bed sleep,
你，睡觉，睡觉，睡觉，
bed sleep, bed sleep.
上床睡觉，上床睡觉。
&gt;&gt; Okay. If I were to say bed, scroll, bed,
好的。如果我说床，滚动，床，
eat, bed, work, bed, sleep, bed, TV,
吃饭，睡觉，工作，睡觉，看电视，
bed,
床，
&gt;&gt; you
你
&gt;&gt; confused.
使困惑。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; Because there's no predictive signal.
因为没有预测信号。
You've never bound an association. Now
你从未建立过任何协会。现在
the way this works to your disadvantage
这样做对你不利。
in insomnia is the following. The
以下是失眠症的症状。这
insomnia event that begins the insomnia
引发失眠的失眠事件
is typically not the thing that
通常不是这样的
maintains the insomnia. So let's say
加剧失眠。比如说
that I um had I experienced a really
我，嗯，我经历了一件非常
difficult bereavement and that triggered
艰难的丧亲之痛引发了
a form of insomnia where I couldn't
一种我无法入睡的失眠症
sleep because of the bereavement.
因丧亲之痛而失眠。
Gradually the bereavement is not the
渐渐地，丧亲之痛不再是……
thing that's going to maintain my
能维持我的东西
insomnia. It's because every time I have
失眠。这是因为每次我都有
been going to bed over the past month, I
过去一个月，我一直晚上睡觉，
have not been sleeping. I've been wide
我一直没睡着。我一直很宽广
awake in my bed. So now, because your
我醒来时发现自己躺在床上。所以现在，因为你
brain is such an incredibly associative
大脑是一个极其复杂的联想器官。
device, it learns the association that
该设备会学习这种关联，即
my bed is the place where I'm always
我的床是我一直待的地方
awake. And what do we then do? We need
醒。那么我们接下来该怎么办？我们需要
to break that association in insomnia.
打破失眠中的这种关联。
So what we do is we say the 20-minut
所以我们所做的就是说20分钟
rule. If you've been in bed for about 20
规则。如果你已经卧床大约20分钟
minutes and it's just not happening for
几分钟过去了，事情还是没有发生。
you, don't worry. Don't listen to idiots
你不用担心。别听傻瓜的话
like me that doom and gloom and disease
就像我一样，充满厄运、悲观和疾病
and sickness and one bad night is not
生病和一次糟糕的夜晚并非如此。
going to be a problem. It's just not. So
这将是个问题。事实并非如此。所以
just say look tonight is not my night. I
你就说，今晚不适合我。我
am not however going to lie in bed awake
但我不会躺在床上醒着。
because very quickly my brain starts to
因为我的大脑很快就开始
learn the association that my bed is the
了解我的床是
place where I'm wide awake. And you need
我完全清醒的地方。你需要
to break that association. So go to a
打破这种联系。所以去……
different room in dim light. Just read a
光线昏暗的另一个房间。刚读完一篇
book, listen to a podcast, whatever it
看书、听播客，或者做任何事。
is. And the rule of thumb is the
是。而经验法则是：
following. only return to bed when you
下列的。只有当你……的时候才回到床上。
are sleepy and so there's no time limit
他们很困，所以没有时间限制。
and that way you gradually relearn the
这样你就能逐渐重新学习……
association that my bed is the place
联想到我的床就是那个地方
where I always get consistent sleep
在那里我总是能睡个好觉
because otherwise it's the dentist chair
因为不然的话，它就变成牙医椅了。
you walk into your bedroom and you look
你走进卧室，环顾四周
at your bed and it's your nemesis and
它就在你的床上，而它正是你的宿敌。
you convinced yourself even before you
你甚至在你之前就已经说服了自己
get into bed I'm not going to sleep
上床睡觉吧，我不想睡。
because that's the place where I always
因为那是我总是去的地方
don't sleep and by the way if you suffer
不要睡觉，顺便说一句，如果你感到痛苦
from the 3M awakenings my first question
从3M觉醒开始，我的第一个问题
is how do you know It's 3:00 a.m.
你怎么知道现在是凌晨3点？
And that's your first problem. Looking
这就是你的第一个问题。寻找
at the clock does two things. It makes
时钟有两个作用。它制造
you more anxious.
你更焦虑了。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; And second, because your brain is such
其次，因为你的大脑是如此
an incredibly associative device, you
你，一个极具联想性的设备。
start to then decide that 3:00 a.m. is
然后开始决定凌晨3点是
the time when I need to wake up. If you
我需要起床的时间。如果你
keep looking at the clock, you keep
你不停地看表，不停地
reinforcing that it's 3:00 or 4. And
再次强调现在是三点或四点。
sleep at 3:00 in the morning is like
凌晨三点睡觉就像
trying to remember someone's name. The
努力回忆某人的名字。这
harder you try, the further you push
你越努力，就越能越深入。
sleep away. Sleep is something that
睡去吧。睡眠是……
happens to you. It's not something that
发生在你身上的事。这不是什么……
you make happen. And so at that moment,
你让这一切成为现实。于是，就在那一刻，
the best advice if you don't want to get
如果你不想得到……，最好的建议是……
out of bed is do any one of the
起床是指做以下任何一件事
following. Meditation. Just do a guided
下列的。冥想。只需按照指导进行操作即可。
meditation. You can download apps. Next,
冥想。你可以下载应用程序。下一个，
if that's not your thing, that's okay.
如果你不喜欢那样，也没关系。
Do box breathing. You know, you can sort
做箱式呼吸法。你知道，你可以排序
of inhale for five, hold for six, exhale
吸气五秒，屏气六秒，呼气
for seven. There's all sorts of
七个。有各种各样的
different numbers, but you can do
数字不同，但你可以这样做
breathing exercises. The third, if you
呼吸练习。第三，如果你
don't like that, is a body scan. So,
我不喜欢那样，那是全身扫描。所以，
close your eyes, start at the top of
闭上眼睛，从顶部开始
your head, feel as you know, do I have
你的头，感觉就像你知道的那样，我是否有
tension in my forehead? Do I need to
我额头感觉很紧绷？我需要吗？
relax it? What about my neck? Do I need
放松点？我的脖子怎么样了？我需要
to move through your body and gradually
在你的身体里慢慢地移动
go down? How are my shoulder blades
下去？我的肩胛骨感觉如何？
feeling? I just relax down into the bed
感觉？我放松地躺到床上。
and gradually down into the chest, into
并逐渐向下进入胸腔，进入
the move through just relax. If none of
整个过程只需放松即可。如果没有
those things feel fun, the next thing
那些事情感觉很有趣，接下来呢？
you can do is take yourself on a mental
你可以做的就是让自己进入一种心理状态
walk. There's a great study from my
走。我做过一项很棒的研究。
university, uh, the University of
大学，呃，大学
Berkeley, California,
加利福尼亚州伯克利
and we didn't do the study. Allison
而我们并没有进行这项研究。艾莉森
Harvey did it. By the way, counting
是哈维干的。顺便说一下，计数
sheep, bad idea. Makes your sleep worse,
养羊？不好的主意。会让你的睡眠更糟。
it turns out. Why is that? Because,
原来如此。这是为什么？因为，
well, with every kind of little bleeting
嗯，伴随着各种各样的小咩咩声
cotton wool ball with a strange look on
一个看起来很奇怪的棉球
its face that leaps over the fence that
它那跃过栅栏的脸
you're counting, you're reinforcing
你在计数，你在强化
every minute of sleep that you're not
你睡眠的每一分钟都虚度光阴
getting, and it seems to make matters
得到，而且似乎让事情变得更糟。
worse. But what she found was that
更糟。但她发现的是……
there's an alternative. If you think
还有另一种选择。如果你觉得
about a walk that you know in great
关于你熟悉的一次散步
vivid detail. So for me, it's going to
细节生动。所以对我来说，这将是
be walking the dog. So I go over to the
正在遛狗。于是我走到
shelf. I open the door. Is it the red
架子。我打开门。是红色吗？
lead or the I'm going to go with the
领导或者我打算选择
blue lead today. So I clip the dog in
今天蓝铅。所以我把狗夹子夹了起来。
with my right hand. I open the door with
用我的右手。我打开门
my left hand. I take a left down the
我的左手。我左转驶入
stairs. I look. It's that level of I
楼梯。我看了看。就是那种程度的我
want you 4K detail in terms of
想要你提供 4K 细节方面的信息
granularity.
粒度。
And what's common about every method
每种方法的共同点是什么？
I've just described, meditation, box
我刚才描述的，冥想，盒子
breathing, sort of uh body scan, going
呼吸，某种身体扫描，开始
on a mental walk, all of these things
在脑海中漫步，所有这些事情
have in common that you get your mind
共同点是，你要学会控制自己的思想
off itself.
自行脱落。
&gt;&gt; In that particular example where she
在她出场的那个例子中
asks you to vividly think about a
要求你生动地思考……
journey that you know, what did she find
那段旅程，你知道的，她发现了什么
in the study? What she found is that
在研究中？她发现的是……
that increases the speed with which you
这会加快你的速度
fall back asleep
再次入睡
&gt;&gt; significantly
显著地
because as I said it it's so you know
因为正如我所说，你知道的
her work to me demonstrated that it it
她的作品向我证明了这一点。
is so like that name because the moment
就像这个名字一样，因为那一刻
I stop trying to remember someone's name
我不再试图记住别人的名字。
what happens
会发生什么
&gt;&gt; you remember it
你还记得吗？
&gt;&gt; I remember it and so when you do these
我记得这件事，所以当你做这些事的时候
types of exercises where you're getting
练习类型，从中获得
the mind off itself the next thing that
接下来发生的事情是，思绪完全转移到了自己身上。
you typically remember is your alarm
你通常记得的就是闹钟
clock going off in the morning.
早晨的钟声响起。
&gt;&gt; Is this why people listen to very vivid
这就是人们喜欢听非常生动的音乐的原因吗？
sleep stories and why I listen to serial
睡眠故事以及我为什么听连续剧
killer documentaries?
精彩的纪录片？
&gt;&gt; Serial killer documentaries,
连环杀手纪录片
&gt;&gt; true crime documentaries, I should say.
应该说，是真实犯罪纪录片。
That's a bit more uh nice to pallet.
这样看起来更……嗯，更适合摆盘。
&gt;&gt; I don't know of them. My suspicion is
我不认识他们。我的怀疑是
that they may be doing your deep sleep a
它们可能会影响你的深度睡眠。
disservice. anything
失职。任何事物
&gt;&gt; stick up for me in the comments.
请在评论区为我说话。
[laughter] If you if you listen to true
[笑声] 如果你听从真话
crime to fall asleep, please write it
犯罪行为导致入睡，请写下来
below in the comment section.
请在下方评论区留言。
&gt;&gt; If you find it subjectively wonderfully
如果你觉得它主观上非常棒
pacifying and calming and there is not
具有安抚和镇静作用，而且没有
death, naming, blood, and limbs being
死亡、命名、血液和肢体
distributed at high velocity all over
高速分布于各处
the scene, I would say it's great. But
我觉得这场景很棒。但
if it looks like a Quentyn Tarantino
如果它看起来像昆汀·塔伦蒂诺
movie or sounds like one, maybe harm and
电影或听起来像电影，可能会造成伤害。
foul rather than
比……更糟糕
&gt;&gt; I mean just in my ears
我的意思是，就在我的耳朵里
&gt;&gt; but yes. So you know we forget that to
是的。所以你知道我们常常忘记这一点。
the best of my knowledge the meditation
据我所知，冥想
company called calm now I have no
公司叫 Calm Now，我没有
affiliation with them they were doing
他们与他们有联系，他们正在这样做
somewhat well but what they realized is
情况还算不错，但他们意识到的是
that they wanted people to sort of
他们希望人们能这样想。
meditate in the morning and when they
早上冥想，以及当他们
used looked at their usage statistics
他们查看了他们的使用统计数据
people were meditating in the morning
早上有人在冥想。
but then there was a huge swath of usage
但随后出现了大范围的使用。
right before bed people were
就在睡觉前，人们
self-medicating their state of insomnia
他们通过自我用药来治疗失眠症
and then through a stroke of genius they
然后，他们灵光一闪，想到了一个绝妙的主意。
realized when we were young we used to
我们年轻的时候就意识到我们曾经
love falling asleep to our parents
我们喜欢伴着父母的哭声入睡
reading us a story.
给我们讲个故事。
Why is that any different when we become
为什么当我们成为……时情况会有所不同呢？
adults? So they created sleep stories
成年人？于是他们创作了睡前故事。
and they went from struggling as a
他们从苦苦挣扎到
company I think to becoming the first or
我认为公司要成为第一家或
one of the first billion dollar
首批十亿美元级公司之一
valuation health companies out there.
对医疗保健公司进行估值。
they became a unicorn and now they can
它们变成了独角兽，现在它们可以
they've got you know people like you
他们那里有像你这样的人。
know Matthew McConnA they've got Harry
认识马修·麦康纳，他们有哈里
Styles and then occasionally they've got
风格，偶尔他们也会有
a a you know an unfortunate British
你知道，一个不幸的英国人
sleep scientist um with a bad voice but
睡眠科学家，嗯，声音不太好，但是
you can listen to these sleep stories
你可以听听这些睡前故事
and they are wonderfully soporific. Why?
它们具有极佳的催眠作用。为什么？
Because they get your mind off itself.
因为它们能让你暂时忘记烦恼。
&gt;&gt; We we talked um earlier on about
我们之前谈到过……
melatonin and uh there are other
褪黑素，还有其他一些。
supplements which people talk a lot
人们经常谈论的保健品
about. One of the ones that's become
关于。其中一个已经成为
really popular is magnesium. I've heard
镁非常受欢迎。我听说
ashwagandha and I've heard magnesium a
我还听说过南非醉茄和镁
lot.
很多。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; Is there any efficacy to these? Are
这些方法有效吗？是
these are these useful?
这些有用吗？
&gt;&gt; The first thing I would say is that if
我首先要说的是，如果
you're suffering from sleep problems and
你正遭受睡眠问题的困扰，
you're looking to supplements, you're
你正在寻找补充剂，你是
stepping over dollars to pick up
跨过一美元去捡东西
pennies.
便士。
&gt;&gt; Okay.
好的。
&gt;&gt; What you need to do is think about the
你需要做的就是思考……
fundamentals.
基本原理。
Regularity.
规律性。
Watch your caffeine intake. Make sure
注意控制咖啡因摄入量。确保
you're not drinking too much alcohol.
你并没有饮酒过量。
Get regular. Dim down half of the
养成规律的作息习惯。将一半亮度调低
lights. Digital detox. Any one of those,
灯。数码戒断。以上任何一种，
but especially all of them combined are
但尤其是它们结合起来的时候
going to get you log orders of better
将会给你更好的日志订单
sleep than reaching for the latest
与其伸手去拿最新的
supplement bottle of whatever it is. The
一瓶不知名的补充剂。这
second thing to say is think about it
第二点是，好好想想。
from a logical standpoint. If there were
从逻辑角度来看。如果存在的话
really some supplement that promises to
确实有一些声称可以……的补充剂
be the Shangrilar of all respplendant
成为所有辉煌的香格里拉
sleep at night, the drug companies would
晚上睡得着觉，制药公司就会……
have been all over it decades ago. To
几十年前我就完全了解它了。到
put it in context, it took George Lucas,
放在当时的背景下，这要归功于乔治·卢卡斯。
I think, about 30 years to amass
我认为，大约需要30年才能积累起来。
something like 4 billion in revenue from
大约40亿美元的收入
the Star Wars franchise. It took Ambient
《星球大战》系列。它需要环境
22 months.
22个月。
That's how big a business sleep farmer
这就是睡眠农场主的生意规模。
is.
是。
&gt;&gt; Ambience is what a sleep pill.
氛围就像安眠药一样。
&gt;&gt; Ambient is a sleep pill. Magnesium, if
Ambient 是一种安眠药。镁，如果
you dig into it, and I I did a deep dive
你深入研究一下，我也做了一次深入调查。
about three years ago because I I kept
大约三年前，因为我一直
hearing it too. This magnesium,
我也听到了。这种镁，
magnesium. The first thing to note is
镁。首先需要注意的是：
that most forms of magnesium, magnesium
大多数形式的镁，镁
oxide
氧化物
or magnesium citrate, most of these
或柠檬酸镁，大多数
forms of magnesium
镁的各种形式
don't cross the brain barrier and sleep
不要穿过脑屏障和睡眠
is produced by your brain. So, how can
由你的大脑产生。那么，如何才能……
something that doesn't get into your
一些不会进入你脑海的东西
brain affect
大脑影响
brain process? Number one, there is one
大脑活动过程？第一，只有一个
form of magnesium that seems to have
似乎具有某种形式的镁
some evidence in favor of it. It's
有一些证据支持这一观点。它是
called magnesium L308.
称为镁 L308。
But if you look at the literature, where
但如果你查阅文献，就会发现
did this story come from? It turns out
这个故事出自哪里？事实证明
that about 30 years ago, they started
大约30年前，他们开始
looking at people who had disrupted
看看那些扰乱秩序的人。
sleep and they would assess their blood
他们会睡觉，然后评估他们的血液
work. And what they found is that some
工作。他们发现，有些
of those people were magnesium
这些人体内含有镁。
deficient. And when they supplemented
不足。当他们补充时
them with magnesium and they became
它们与镁混合后就变成了
magnesium normative, their sleep got
镁含量正常，他们的睡眠得到了改善
better.
更好的。
But that's very different than saying,
但这与以下说法截然不同：
"Look, you and I, we're currently
“你看，你和我，我们目前
magnesium normative and then dosing
镁的正常值，然后进行剂量调整
myself with high volumes of magnesium.
我自己补充了大量的镁。
Am I imagining that that's going to make
我是不是想多了？那样做会……
my sleep better?" The the analogy would
我的睡眠质量会更好吗？”这个比喻
be, let's say I develop this incredible
比如说，我开发出了这种不可思议的东西
new oxygen saturation machine, and you
新的血氧饱和度仪，还有你
say to me, "Well, but Matt, my blood
跟我说，“好吧，但是马特，我的血
oxygen saturation right now, looking at
目前的血氧饱和度，正在观察
my device, tells me it's 98.6%."
我的设备显示电量为98.6%。
It doesn't matter how fancy or good my
我的手机有多花哨或多好都无关紧要。
machine is. I'm not going to get you
机器是。我抓不到你
past 100%. You're already at ceiling
超过100%。你已经达到天花板了
level.
等级。
&gt;&gt; And that's the problem with magnesium
这就是镁的问题所在。
supplementation. If you're magnesium
补充。如果你体内镁含量高，那就说明你体内镁含量高。
normative, all you're doing is creating
规范化的，你所做的只是创造
probably expensive urine at at at that
可能尿液价格昂贵
moment in time. Now, there may be an
那一刻。现在可能存在
indirect benefit of magnesium in that it
镁的间接益处在于它
does seem to relax muscles. And when the
似乎确实能放松肌肉。当
body is in a state of relaxation, it
身体处于放松状态，它
sends a signal of relaxation back up a
向上发出放松信号
branch of nerves called the vagus nerve
迷走神经是神经的一个分支。
that goes up to the brain and signals to
信号会传递到大脑并发出信号
your brain you're starting to relax down
你的大脑开始放松下来
and you get this state of quiescence and
于是你就进入了这种静止状态。
that's very helpful for sleep. So
这对睡眠非常有帮助。所以
magnesium may still have an indirect
镁可能仍然具有间接作用。
benefit on sleep through its relaxation
通过放松作用改善睡眠。
kind of policy that it instantiates in
它所体现的那种政策
the body. But overall, magnesium is not
身体。但总的来说，镁并非
really moving the needle if you look at
如果你仔细观察，就会发现这确实带来了显著的改变。
the studies. Ashwagandha
这些研究。南非醉茄
is different. Ashwagandha and another
情况有所不同。南非醉茄和另一种
compound called phospatitile serarene.
一种名为磷脂酰丝氨酸的化合物。
Phospatidile sererearine and ashwagandha
磷脂丝雷瑞林和南非醉茄
both of these supplements seem to help
这两种补充剂似乎都有帮助。
do one of two things. They either
做以下两件事之一。他们要么
ratchet down the fightor-flight branch
逐步减少战斗飞行分支
of your nervous system and they can also
你的神经系统，它们也可以
reduce the amount of cortisol that the
减少皮质醇的含量
body is releasing. That's important
身体正在释放。这很重要
because I see a lot of people coming to
因为我看到很多人来这里
the sleep center where I'm at and they
我所在的睡眠中心，他们
have what I call the tired but wired
我称之为“疲惫但精神亢奋”。
phenomenon where they come to me and
他们来找我的这种现象
they say, "I am so tired. I am so so
他们说：“我好累。我好累好累。”
tired but I'm just so wired emotionally
很累，但我情绪非常激动。
and from a nervous perspective that I
从神经质的角度来看，我
can't fall asleep." And let's say that
无法入睡。”假设
you've done, let's say, you know, um, an
你已经做过，比如说，你知道，嗯，一个
onstage event and it's incredible.
舞台活动非常精彩。
You've got that onstage buzz. You come
你已经有了那种舞台上的兴奋感。你来了
off stage at 11 p.m. And normally you'd
晚上11点下台通常情况下你会
be fast asleep, but you know, you are so
你睡得很沉，但你知道，你是如此的
wired. It doesn't matter. You are tired,
有线。没关系。你累了。
as tired as can be, but you're so wired
虽然疲惫不堪，但你却精神抖擞。
you can't fall asleep. That's the fight
你睡不着。这就是战斗
orflight branch being switched on and
或飞行分支被开启
you just can't fall asleep. You need to
你就是睡不着。你需要
push it back off. Phosphatidal sererine
把它推回去。磷脂酰丝氨酸
and ashwagandha will both push you back
南非醉茄和阿什瓦甘达都会让你退缩
over into the more quuscent what we call
进入更浓郁的我们称之为
parasympathetic nervous system branch.
副交感神经系统分支。
That's good. However, they also will
那挺好的。然而，他们也会
reduce cortisol and cortisol is a
降低皮质醇水平，而皮质醇是一种
wakeromoting hormone. Cortisol is fine.
促醒激素。皮质醇水平正常。
We It gets a bad rap. You need to have
它名声很差。你需要拥有
your cortisol start to spike a few hours
你的皮质醇水平会在几个小时后开始飙升。
before bed and it helps with the waking
睡前服用，有助于醒来
up process. It's wonderful. Every day we
向上过程。太棒了。我们每天
have a cortisol spike that starts
皮质醇水平出现峰值，随后开始
happening before we wake up. It's one of
发生在我们醒来之前。这是其中之一
the things that helps us wake up and
那些帮助我们醒来的事物
then it builds us to this beautiful
然后它引领我们走向这美好的未来。
crescendo midm morning where you should
上午中段渐强，你应该在哪里？
be awake and not needing caffeine
保持清醒且不需要咖啡因
&gt;&gt; and it drops before bed
睡前会下降。
&gt;&gt; and then it starts to peak in the sort
然后它开始在排序中达到顶峰。
of middle early afternoon and in fact
下午早些时候，事实上
usually peaks at the late morning hours
通常在上午晚些时候达到高峰
I should say and then it will start its
我应该说，然后它就会开始……
awesome sort of downswing and what you
很棒的下坡路，还有你
see is that right before you go to bed
你看，就是在你睡觉前。
cortisol should hit its lowest point
皮质醇水平应该达到最低点
what we call its nadia its lowest
我们称之为它的纳迪亚，它的最低
trough.
槽。
&gt;&gt; Mhm.
嗯。
&gt;&gt; What's [clears throat] interesting, by
什么有趣呢？（清嗓子）
the way, just as an aside, is that
顺便提一下，方法是这样的：
insomnia we can classify usually as at
我们通常可以将失眠归类为……
least one of two different types.
至少是两种不同类型中的一种。
There's actually multiple, but let's
实际上有好几个，但我们先来说说……
just say there are of those multiple,
就说有多个这样的
there are two types. One is called sleep
有两种类型。其中一个叫做睡眠
onset insomnia. I can't fall asleep. The
发作性失眠。我睡不着。这
other is sleep maintenance insomnia. I
另一种是睡眠维持性失眠。我
can't stay asleep. when they've looked
睡不着。当他们看过之后
at people's cortisol on a 30 minute by
30分钟内人们的皮质醇水平
30 minute basis on the 24-hour clock
以24小时制为基础，每30分钟为一个周期。
face, we go through just what we
面对这一切，我们经历的正是我们所经历的。
described. Just before we wake up, we
已描述。就在我们醒来之前，我们
get this rise in cortisol. It peaks late
导致皮质醇水平升高。它的巅峰期来得晚。
morning and then it drops down and right
早上，然后它下降，向右。
before bed, our cortisol is almost at
睡前，我们的皮质醇水平几乎达到……
its lowest point. With insomnia
它的最低点。失眠
patients, they show exactly the same
患者们，他们表现出完全相同的症状。
thing. A beautiful rise in the late
事物。晚年的一次美丽崛起
morning hours. It starts to come down,
上午时分。它开始下降，
but then you see two anomalies. Right
但随后你会发现两个异常情况。正确的
before bed, it goes back up.
睡前，它又会回升。
And then in the middle of the night,
然后，在半夜，
even when it's starting to rise, it will
即使它开始上升，它也会
have this abnormal spike right in the
出现这种异常峰值。
middle of the night, too. And what we
也是在半夜。而我们
believe is that that may in part explain
我认为这或许可以部分解释……
sleep onset insomnia. Cortisol should be
入睡困难型失眠。皮质醇应该
coming down and it should stay low right
正在下降，应该会保持低位，对吧？
before we go to bed. But then it jumps
在我们睡觉之前。但随后它跳了起来。
back up in insomnia patients. I can't
帮助失眠患者恢复健康。我不能
fall asleep. And then it continues to
睡着。然后它继续
stay low throughout the first half of
前半段保持低调
the night, but then it also spikes in
夜间，但随后也会急剧上升
insomnia patients. I can't stay asleep.
失眠患者。我睡不着。
&gt;&gt; I've had so many founders speak to me
很多创始人跟我交流过。
and say, "Why didn't this particular ad
然后问：“为什么这个广告没有成功？”
that I ran on this platform work for me?
我在这个平台上运行的程序对我有用吗？
Maybe the copy wasn't good. The creative
或许是文案写得不好。创意
wasn't strong." But usually the problem
不够强壮。”但通常问题在于
is they're not having the right
他们没有权利
conversation because that ad never
因为那则广告从未引发过对话
reached the right person. And if you're
联系对了人。如果你是
in B2B marketing, that is much of the
在B2B营销中，这占据了很大一部分。
game. And this is where LinkedIn ads
游戏。这就是LinkedIn广告的投放位置。
solves that problem for you. Their
帮你解决这个问题。他们的
targeting is ridiculously specific. You
目标定位精准得离谱。你
can target by job title, seniority,
可以按职位、资历进行筛选
company size, industry, and even
公司规模、行业，甚至
someone's skill set. And their network
某人的技能组合。以及他们的网络
includes over a billion professionals.
其中包括超过十亿专业人士。
About 130 million of them are decision
其中约有1.3亿人正在做决定
makers. So when you use LinkedIn ads,
制造商。所以，当你使用LinkedIn广告时，
you're putting your brand in front of
你正在将你的品牌置于……之前
the right people. And LinkedIn ads also
合适的人选。 LinkedIn广告也
drive the highest B2B return on ad spend
实现最高的 B2B 广告支出回报率
across all ad networks in my experience.
就我的经验而言，在所有广告网络中都是如此。
If you want to give them a try, head
如果你想尝试一下，请前往
over to linkedin.com/diary.
转到 linkedin.com/diary。
And when you spend $250 on your first
当你第一次消费满 250 美元时
LinkedIn ads campaign, you'll get an
LinkedIn广告活动，您将获得
extra $250 credit from me for the next
我额外提供 250 美元信用额度，供下次使用。
one. That's linkedin.com/diary.
一。那是 linkedin.com/diary。
Terms and conditions apply. We were
须遵守相关条款和条件。我们曾
talking about regularity, timing, and
谈论规律性、时间安排和
all these things and quality and
所有这些以及质量和
quantity. But one of the things I
数量。但其中一件事
learned from your work is that that last
从你的工作中我学到的是，最后
hour is potentially the most important
一小时可能是最重要的
hour of me being in bed. And I I say
我躺在床上一个小时。我说
this in part because my my girlfriend,
部分原因是因为我的女朋友，
she would wake, she'd have about six six
她会醒来，大概六点钟左右。
hours, six and a half hours sleep. She
六个半小时的睡眠。她
sleeps very very well. Perfect sleeper,
睡得非常好。睡眠质量极佳，
but she'd always get up really really
但她总是会非常非常努力地起床。
really early. And in part that was
很早。部分原因在于……
because of the guilt that I talked
因为我的愧疚，我才说了这些话。
about. But I had a conversation with her
关于。但我跟她谈过了。
about the guilt. And I said, "Just stay
关于内疚感。我说：“你就待着吧。”
in bed as long as you need to stay in
你需要卧床休息多久就卧床多久。
bed. Like just have that extra eighth
床。就像多出那八分之一盎司一样
hour." And in part that's because I
一小时。”部分原因是因为我
learned that the further we go in sleep,
了解到，我们睡得越深，
the more REM we're getting.
我们获得的快速眼动睡眠越多。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; Okay. Can you explain that to me with
好的。你能给我解释一下吗？
these four blocks? Why that last hour is
这四个方块？为什么是最后一个小时？
particularly important and why we
尤其重要，以及为什么我们
shouldn't be jumping out of bed or why
不应该从床上跳起来，或者为什么
we should be using certain sleep devices
我们应该使用某些睡眠设备
to wake us up when we're at the end of
在我们走到尽头时叫醒我们
that last hour of REM.
快速眼动睡眠的最后一个小时。
&gt;&gt; Absolutely. So here we have the four
绝对地。所以这里我们有四位。
blocks of sleep. So when we first fall
睡眠断断续续。所以当我们第一次跌倒时
asleep, we go into light non rapid eye
睡着后，我们进入浅非快速眼动睡眠状态
movement sleep. Stage one. This is the
动觉睡眠。第一阶段。这是
stage of sleep that if I wake you up out
睡眠阶段，如果我把你叫醒
of it, you say, "I wasn't sleeping." Now
对此，你会说：“我当时没睡着。”现在
you it's just that you're just in that
你只是身处其中而已。
transitional phase, this beautiful
过渡阶段，这美丽的
liinal state between the windows of
窗口之间的线性状态
wakefulness and true sleep. So this is
清醒与真正的睡眠。所以这是
your bridge between the waking world and
你连接清醒世界和现实世界的桥梁
the sleep world. And it doesn't last for
睡眠的世界。而且这种情况不会持续太久
very long. Maybe just 10 or 15 minutes
很长。可能只需要10到15分钟
at tops. Then you get into the workhorse
顶部。然后你就坐上那辆干活的车了。
of sleep. This is stage two nonREM
睡眠。这是第二阶段非快速眼动睡眠
sleep. 50% of your night is spent in
睡觉。你晚上50%的时间都花在了……
stage two nonREM sleep. I don't like the
第二阶段非快速眼动睡眠。我不喜欢
word light nonREM sleep. I've often used
浅睡眠（非快速眼动睡眠）。我经常使用
it, but it's not really it's we do a lot
确实如此，但其实并非如此，我们做了很多事。
of cognitive processing in stage two
第二阶段认知加工
nonREM sleep. It's good stuff. It's not
非快速眼动睡眠。这是好东西。它不是
just the stage that you have to go
这只是你必须经历的阶段。
through from sort of, you know, deep
从某种意义上说，你知道，是从深处。
non-REM sleep to go back to stage two in
非快速眼动睡眠将回到第二阶段
order for you to get to REM, but I'll
为了让你能到达 REM，但我会
come to that. So, we have fallen asleep
确实如此。所以，我们都睡着了。
10 minutes.
10分钟。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; Now, we're in stage two nonREM sleep.
现在，我们处于第二阶段非快速眼动睡眠。
We'll stay there for about 15 or 20
我们将在那里待大约15到20分钟。
minutes. Then if it's [clears throat] in
分钟。然后如果它是[清嗓子]
the first couple of hours of the night,
夜幕降临后的头几个小时，
we go down into the very deepest stages
我们深入到最深处。
of deep non-REM sleep. This is where the
深度非快速眼动睡眠。这就是……
brain wave patterns slow down. But the
脑电波模式减慢。但是
brain waves become incredibly big, huge,
脑电波变得异常强烈、巨大，
big, powerful, slow brain waves. This is
大而强劲的缓慢脑电波。这是
where you get an enormous amount of
在那里你可以获得大量的
restoration, recovery of many of your
修复，恢复你的许多
major physiological systems.
主要生理系统。
&gt;&gt; So physical recovery,
所以，身体恢复，
&gt;&gt; physical recovery, but mental too. Yeah,
身体恢复，心理恢复也很重要。是的，
&gt;&gt; it's during deep sleep that you take
你是在深度睡眠期间服用的。
newly minted memories that you've
你已经拥有的全新回忆
learned and you hit the save button on
学会后，你点击了保存按钮。
those memories so that you don't forget.
那些记忆，让你永生难忘。
&gt;&gt; Deep sleep essentially is going to
深度睡眠本质上会
futureproof the information that you
确保您的信息具有前瞻性
just learned today. It transfers
今天刚学会的。它转移
information from a short-term storage
来自短期存储的信息
vulnerable reservoir to a more permanent
脆弱的蓄水池更容易受到永久性破坏
long-term storage site. It's during deep
长期存储场所。这是在深海期间
non-REM sleep when we have this
当我们处于非快速眼动睡眠状态时，就会出现这种情况
communication. So think of those deep
沟通。所以想想那些深层的
powerful slow brain waves like longwave
强大的慢脑电波，例如长波
radio station when you used to tune into
你以前常收听的那个广播电台
a radio station in a car. You get huge
车里的广播电台。你会变得非常大
ability for information transfer across
跨渠道信息传递能力
long distances across huge paths in the
跨越漫长道路的漫长距离
brain. It's amazing. So we've gone from
脑。太神奇了。所以我们已经从
light non-REM, then we go down into deep
然后我们进入深度睡眠阶段。
nonrem. We'll stay there for about 15 or
非放射性。我们将在那里待大约15分钟或更长时间。
20 minutes. Then we'll start to rise
20分钟。然后我们就会开始崛起
back up again. We'll go back into stage
又恢复正常了。我们将重返舞台
two nonREM sleep.
两次非快速眼动睡眠。
&gt;&gt; Wait, we've gone from 1 2 3 to two. Yes.
等等，我们已经从 1 2 3 变成 2 了。是的。
So, we've gone, think about it more
所以，我们已经……再仔细想想。
almost like a roller coaster, right? So,
就像坐过山车一样，对吧？所以，
we go from light nonrem and then we go
我们从轻度非物质层面开始，然后我们……
down into stage two nonREM. Then, we go
进入第二阶段非快速眼动睡眠。然后，我们去
down into deep sleep and then we're
进入深度睡眠，然后我们就……
going to rise back up into light stage
即将重返光明舞台
two nonREM sleep. We're going to stay
两次非快速眼动睡眠。我们会留下来
there and after about 70 80 minutes,
在那里，大约过了70到80分钟，
you're going to pop up and you'll have a
你将会突然出现，并且你会有一个
short REM sleep period.
快速眼动睡眠期较短。
&gt;&gt; Oh, okay. Like this.
哦好的。像这样。
&gt;&gt; And this is beautiful. So this is what
这真美。所以这就是……
we call a hypnogog.
我们称之为催眠术。
&gt;&gt; I'll put this on the screen for anyone.
我会把这个显示在屏幕上，任何人都能看到。
&gt;&gt; Lovely. So what I'm describing here is
迷人的。所以我在这里描述的是……
this roller coaster ride. So we've
这趟过山车之旅。所以我们已经
fallen asleep light stage one nonREM go
进入浅睡眠阶段（第一阶段非快速眼动睡眠）
down into stage two. Then you go down
进入第二阶段。然后你就下去了
and you have a heavy period of deep
你经历了一段深度睡眠的时期。
nonREM slowwave sleep. Stage three. And
非快速眼动慢波睡眠。第三阶段。和
then and that's what you see on your
然后，这就是你在你的屏幕上看到的。
sleep tracker is deep sleep. This is
睡眠追踪器显示的是深度睡眠。这是
light sleep. This is deep sleep. Stage
浅睡眠。这是深度睡眠。阶段
two nonREM sleep. Light sleep. Stage
两次非快速眼动睡眠。浅睡眠。阶段
three nonREM sleep. Deep sleep. But then
三次非快速眼动睡眠。深度睡眠。但是后来
you'll start to climb back up and
你会开始重新向上攀登，
[clears throat] then you may pop up and
[清嗓子] 然后你可能会突然出现
you'll have a short REM sleep period
你的快速眼动睡眠期会很短。
here after about 70 or 80 minutes. So
大约70或80分钟后到达这里。所以
you'll have about 10 minutes of REM
你大约会有10分钟的快速眼动睡眠期。
sleep and then back down you go again.
睡一觉，然后又睡着了。
You go down into non-REM sleep and then
你进入非快速眼动睡眠状态，然后
up into REM. Down into nonREM sleep and
进入快速眼动睡眠期。进入非快速眼动睡眠状态
you'll go up into REM. Down into nonREM
你会进入快速眼动睡眠期。进入非快速眼动睡眠阶段
sleep and up into REM.
睡眠并进入快速眼动睡眠阶段。
So what's interesting however is that
然而，有趣的是……
the ratio of nonREM to REM changes. Now,
非快速眼动睡眠与快速眼动睡眠的比例发生变化。现在，
there's a myth out there and it's a bit
坊间流传着一种说法，而且有点……
of a problem. We humans have a 90inute
一个问题。我们人类有90分钟的寿命
average nonREM to REM cycle. So, we go
平均非快速眼动睡眠到快速眼动睡眠周期。所以，我们出发
down into nonREM sleep and then up into
进入非快速眼动睡眠，然后进入……
REM sleep every 90 minutes. Then, we go
每90分钟进入快速眼动睡眠期。然后，我们去
back down into nonREM sleep and then up
再次进入非快速眼动睡眠，然后醒来
into REM sleep. So, we go down into
进入快速眼动睡眠期。所以，我们继续深入
nonREM sleep and then up into REM in
在非快速眼动睡眠阶段，然后进入快速眼动睡眠阶段。
this 90minut cycle.
这个90分钟的周期。
The problem is that it's on average 90
问题是，平均下来是90。
minutes. It ranges from 70 minutes to to
分钟。时长从70分钟到……不等
120 minutes from one individual to the
从一个人到……需要120分钟
next. So you know these devices that you
下一个。所以你知道这些设备
may have seen tried to sort of you know
可能见过有人尝试过，你知道的。
entrepreneurship they say I'm going to
他们说我要创业。
wake you up at the ideal moment in your
在最理想的时刻叫醒你
90minute cycle so that this thing that
90分钟循环，所以这件事
sits on my bedside I tap it when I'm the
它放在我的床头柜上，我睡觉时会敲敲它。
lights go out and then it's going to go
灯灭了，然后它就要走了
on its 90minut cycle and it's going to
它按90分钟的循环运行，然后……
figure out the perfect moment to wake
找到最佳的起床时间
you up. It's nonsense because my sleep
你起来。这简直是​​胡说八道，因为我的睡眠
cycle may be 75 minutes. Yours may be
周期可能为75分钟。你的可能是
105 minutes. It's got no idea because
105分钟。它一无所知，因为
it's using a hard-coded 90minute cycle.
它采用的是固定的90分钟循环周期。
It's it's in some ways nonsense. But we
从某种程度上来说，这简直是无稽之谈。但是我们
go down into nonREM sleep and up into
进入非快速眼动睡眠，然后进入……
REM sleep every 90 minutes. What changes
每90分钟进入快速眼动睡眠期。哪些变化
however is the ratio of non-REM to REM
然而，非快速眼动睡眠与快速眼动睡眠的比例是多少？
within those 90inut cycles as you move
在您移动的这 90 牛顿周期内
across the night such that in the first
整个晚上，在第一阶段
half of the night the majority of those
半夜里，大多数人
90-minute cycles are comprised of lots
90分钟的循环由许多部分组成。
of deep non-REM sleep and very little
深度非快速眼动睡眠和极少
REM sleep. But as you push through to
快速眼动睡眠。但当你坚持下去时
the second half of the night, now that
夜幕降临后的下半场，现在
seesaw balance shifts over and you spend
跷跷板的平衡发生了变化，你花费了
much more of your time in REM sleep in
你在快速眼动睡眠中的时间会大大增加。
the second half of the night and
当晚的后半段和
particularly just as you said in the
特别是正如你所说……
last 2 hours of the night. Why is this
夜间最后两个小时。为什么会这样？
consequential? Well, just as you said
后果严重吗？正如你所说
and you spoke about for your girlfriend,
你谈到了你的女朋友，
let's say that you know I normally go to
假设你知道我通常会去
bed for argument sake and I'm not saying
为了方便讨论，我姑且把床当作例子，我并不是说
this is the ideal time, but I go to bed
这是最佳时间，但我还是去睡觉了。
at midnight to make the math easy and I
为了方便计算，我在午夜进行了计算。
wake up at 8:00. But tomorrow I've got
早上8点起床。但明天我有
to catch my flight back home. So, I'm
去赶回家的航班。所以，我是
going to wake up two hours early. So,
准备早起两个小时。所以，
I'm going to wake up at 6 rather than 8.
我打算早上6点起床，而不是8点。
I've lost two hours of sleep. So, how
我少睡了两个小时。那么，如何
much total sleep have I lost? Well, I've
我总共损失了多少睡眠时间？嗯，我已经
lost 25% of my total sleep. 2 hours of
我失去了25%的睡眠时间。 2 小时
my 8 hours. 25%. Well, yes and no. I've
我的8小时。 25%。嗯，算是，也不算。我已经
lost 25% of my total sleep, but I may
我失去了25%的睡眠时间，但我可能
have lost 50 60 70% of all of my REM
我失去了50%、60%、70%的快速眼动睡眠。
sleep. Why? Because REM sleep comes in
睡觉。为什么？因为快速眼动睡眠开始了
the second half of them, particularly
后半部分，尤其是
those last couple of hours of sleep. So
最后那几个小时的睡眠。所以
that's why it's not just academic that
所以这不仅仅是学术问题。
you understand the sleep cycle
你了解睡眠周期
relationship, but it's also pragmatic
它既有关系，也很务实。
because it can impact the amount. In
因为它会影响数量。在
fact, the easiest way if people said,
事实上，最简单的说法是，如果人们这样说的话，
"How can I get more REM sleep?" I would
如何才能获得更多快速眼动睡眠？我会
say just sleep 15 minutes later into the
比如说，再睡15分钟。
day than you normally would do and you
比平时多一天，而且你
will disproportionately bias yourself
会不成比例地偏袒自己
towards getting significantly more REM
获得更多快速眼动睡眠
sleep.
睡觉。
&gt;&gt; And why does REM sleep matter?
快速眼动睡眠为什么重要？
REM sleep is a brain state firstly that
快速眼动睡眠首先是一种大脑状态，
is incredibly active in some in fact
事实上，在某些方面非常活跃。
some parts of the brain particularly if
大脑的某些部分，特别是如果
I were to show you these deep emotional
我本想向你展示这些深层的情感。
centers of the brain as I pull this
当我拉动这个时，大脑的各个中心都在运转。
brain apart.
大脑分离。
So we've got these sort of deep
所以我们有一些比较深入的探讨。
emotional centers in the brain that sit
大脑中位于此处的情感中枢
and in fact the sort of they're more
事实上，他们更倾向于那种类型。
just underneath in here tucked in inside
就在下面，藏在里面
just next to your brain stem at the top
就在你脑干上方。
of it. And these emotional centers are
它的。这些情感中心是
called the amygdala. And you have one on
被称为杏仁核。你身上也有一件。
the left and one on the right side of
左侧和右侧各一个
your brain. That part of the brain
你的大脑。大脑的那个部分
together with a memory structure that
以及一个记忆结构
runs alongside it called the
与它并排运行的叫做
hippocampus. Those two parts of the
海马体。这两个部分
brain form what we call the limbic
大脑形成我们所说的边缘系统。
system. And you may have heard of the
系统。你可能听说过……
limbic system, the emotional centers of
边缘系统，即情绪中枢
the brain. Those can be up to 40% more
大脑。这些可能高达 40% 以上
active when you're in dream sleep than
比在做梦睡眠时更活跃
when you're awake.
当你醒着的时候。
&gt;&gt; Dream sleep.
做梦入睡。
&gt;&gt; Dream sleep is rapid eye movement sleep.
做梦睡眠是快速眼动睡眠。
&gt;&gt; REM sleep.
快速眼动睡眠。
&gt;&gt; So REM sleep is the stage. Now it
所以快速眼动睡眠是睡眠阶段。现在是
depends on how you define dreaming. If
这取决于你如何定义做梦。如果
you define dreaming as any mental
你把做梦定义为任何精神活动
activity reported upon awakening, then
醒来后报告的活动，然后
you dream in all stages of sleep. Light
在睡眠的各个阶段你都会做梦。光
non-REM sleep, deep REM sleep. So what
非快速眼动睡眠，深度快速眼动睡眠。所以呢
would what would that sound like? Well,
那听起来会是什么样子？出色地，
if I woke you up and said, Stephen, just
如果我把你叫醒，然后说：“斯蒂芬，就……”
tell me what was going through your head
告诉我你当时在想什么
and you said, "Well, I was just thinking
然后你说：“嗯，我刚才在想……”
about the next time you're going to come
关于你下次什么时候来
in and wake me up." That's just a dream
进来叫醒我。”那只是个梦
thought. What the most people think of
想法。大多数人想到的
dreams as the dreams that we have from
梦境，也就是我们所做的梦
REM sleep, from rapid eye movement
快速眼动睡眠，简称 REM 睡眠
sleep. That's why we call it dream
睡觉。这就是为什么我们称之为梦想。
sleep. Dreams from rapid eye movement
睡觉。快速眼动睡眠的梦境
sleep are flid the narrative. In fact,
睡眠是叙事的转折点。实际上，
last night when you fell asleep and you
昨晚你睡着的时候，你
went into dream sleep, you became
进入梦乡，你变成了
incredibly psychotic.
精神极度错乱。
&gt;&gt; Excuse me.
打扰一下。
&gt;&gt; Now, before you reject my diagnosis of
现在，在你否定我的诊断之前……
your nighttime psychosis, let me give
你的夜间精神病，让我来告诉你
you five good reasons. When you went
你列举了五个充分的理由。你去的时候
into dream sleep last night, you started
昨晚你进入梦乡时，你开始……
to see things which were not there. So,
看到原本不存在的事物。所以，
you were hallucinating. Second, you
你当时出现了幻觉。其次，你
believe things that couldn't possibly be
相信那些根本不可能发生的事情
true. So you were delusional. Third, you
真的。所以你是在妄想。第三，你
became confused about time, place, and
对时间、地点和方面感到困惑
person. So in psychiatry, we call that
人。所以在精神病学中，我们称之为
being disorientated.
感到迷失方向。
Fourth, you had wildly fluctuating
第四，你的波动非常剧烈
emotions. Something that we call being
情绪。我们称之为存在的东西
emotionally labile. You're all over the
情绪不稳定。你无处不在
place. And then how wonderful, you and
地方。然后，多么美好啊，你和
I, cuz I'll include myself now as being
我，因为我现在也要把自己算在内了。
psychotic. You and I, we both woke up
精神病患者。你和我，我们都醒了。
this morning and we forgot most if not
今天早上，我们几乎忘记了所有的事情。
all of that dream experience. So, we're
所有这些梦幻般的体验。所以，我们是
suffering from amnesia. If you were to
患有失忆症。如果你要
experience any one of those five
体验这五种体验中的任何一种。
symptoms whilst you're awake, you'd be
清醒时出现的症状，你会……
seeking some degree of psychological
寻求某种程度的心理
help. But for reasons that we're only
帮助。但出于我们仅……的原因
now understanding, it seems to be a
现在明白了，这似乎是一个
normal biological and psychological
正常的生理和心理
process. So, what are the reasons? Why
过程。那么，原因是什么呢？为什么
do we dream? We dream for at least two
我们会做梦吗？我们至少梦想两个
different reasons. The first reason is
原因各不相同。第一个原因是
emotional first aid.
情绪急救。
REM sleep is what I've defined as
我把快速眼动睡眠定义为：
overnight therapy and it's during dream
夜间治疗，而且是在梦中进行的
sleep where your brain takes difficult
睡眠时，大脑很难放松。
painful emotional experiences and it
痛苦的情感经历及其
acts like a nocturnal soothing balm and
它就像夜间舒缓膏一样发挥作用。
it just takes the sharp edges off those
它只是把那些尖锐的边缘磨平了。
difficult painful experiences so that
经历艰难痛苦的经历，因此
you come back the next day and you have
你第二天回来，然后你就……
a memory of an emotional event but it's
一段关于情感事件的记忆，但它是
no longer emotional. you don't have that
不再有情绪波动。你没有那个
same visceral regurgitation of of that
同样的内脏反流
same emotional charge.
同样强烈的情感冲击。
Why is REM sleep able to do this
为什么快速眼动睡眠能够做到这一点
overnight therapy, this deepotentiation?
这种夜间治疗，即去势作用？
Why is REM sleep able to sort of strip
为什么快速眼动睡眠能够起到某种剥离作用？
the bitter emotional rind from
苦涩的情感外壳
theformational orange as it were? The
就像是形成橙色一样？这
reason is the following. Dream sleep,
原因如下。做梦入睡，
REM sleep is the only time during the
快速眼动睡眠是整个睡眠过程中唯一的时期
24-hour period where the brain shuts off
大脑关闭的24小时周期
a stress related neurochemical called
一种与压力相关的神经化学物质
noradrenaline.
去甲肾上腺素。
Now, you've heard of the sister chemical
现在，你已经听说过这种姊妹化学物质了。
downstairs in your body called
你身体下方的那个地方叫做
adrenaline. Well, upstairs in the brain,
肾上腺素。嗯，在大脑的上层，
we don't have adrenaline. We have
我们没有肾上腺素。我们有
noradrenaline. REM sleep is the only
去甲肾上腺素。快速眼动睡眠是唯一的睡眠阶段。
time where it's completely shut off. And
完全关闭的时间。和
what we put forward is a theory called
我们提出的理论叫做
overnight therapy where your brain has,
一夜疗程，让你的大脑……
as I told you, these emotional centers
正如我之前告诉你的，这些情感中心
and these memory centers. The emotional
以及这些记忆中心。情绪
centers, the amydala, the memory
中枢、杏仁核、记忆
centers, the hippocampus. You reactivate
中枢，海马体。您重新激活
those structures when you go into dream
当你进入梦境时，那些结构
sleep. So your brain gets the chance to
睡觉。所以你的大脑就有机会
reactivate and replay and reprocess
重新激活、重放和重新处理
emotional experiences. However, it's
情感体验。然而，它是
doing it in a quote unquote safe
在所谓的“安全”环境下进行。
neurochemical environment because that
因为神经化学环境是这样的。
stress chemical of neuradrenaline is
神经肾上腺素是一种应激化学物质。
completely shut off. So, it's the ideal
完全关闭。所以，这是理想的
neurochemical therapy for stripping the
神经化学疗法用于剥离
emotion from the memory. And we put
回忆带来的情感。我们把
forward a theory that perhaps the
提出一种理论，或许
quintessential disorder where this fails
典型的紊乱症，而这种紊乱症却失败了。
is PTSD.
是创伤后应激障碍（PTSD）。
Because when you speak to those
因为当你和那些人交谈时
patients, not only do we see that their
我们不仅看到患者们
REM sleep is disrupted,
快速眼动睡眠受到干扰，
when you speak to those patients, they
当你和这些病人交谈时，他们
will say, "Look, I just can't quote
会说：“你看，我就是没法引用……”
unquote get over the event." What they
“放下这件事吧。”他们
mean by that is the war veteran who is
意思是说，那位退伍老兵
now going to the supermarket and they
现在要去超市了，他们
come outside and they're in the car park
出来一看，他们都在停车场里。
and the car backfires and they instantly
汽车突然发出爆燃声，他们瞬间
have the flashback to the the sort of
回想起那种……
detonation on the military field. And
军事领域内的爆炸。和
what's happening there is that the brain
那里发生的事情是，大脑
has not stripped the emotion from the
并未剥离其中的情感。
memory. So every time they relive the
记忆。所以每次他们重温……
memory, they regurgitate that same
记忆，他们会重复同样的内容。
emotional reaction.
情绪反应。
&gt;&gt; So no wonder we proposed that the brain
所以，我们提出大脑
then comes back the following night and
然后第二天晚上又回来了，
says, "Look, I'm sorry, sleep. I've
他说：“听着，对不起，睡觉。我……”
still got this trauma memory. Can you do
这段创伤记忆依然挥之不去。你能做到吗？
your trick of stripping the emotion from
你剥离情感的伎俩
the memory?" And it fails again. So the
内存呢？”它又失败了。所以
next night it comes back and says, "I'm
第二天晚上它又出现了，说：“我是……”
sorry to bother you, but I've still got
不好意思打扰您，但我还有一些事要处理。
this emotionally charged memory. Please
这段充满情感的回忆。请
do your trick of stripping the emotion
施展你那剥离情感的绝招
from memory." It fails again. This
凭记忆。”它又失败了。这
sounds like the broken record of
听起来像是老调重弹。
repetitive nightmares that we see in
我们在《
PTSD.
创伤后应激障碍。
Why could this be happening? Levels of
为什么会发生这种情况？级别
noradrenaline in the brain in patients
患者大脑中的去甲肾上腺素
with PTSD are too high. And I was at a
患有创伤后应激障碍的比例太高了。当时我在……
conference some years ago where I was
几年前的一次会议上，我……
presenting this theory. We just
提出这一理论。我们只是
presented this theory. It was a theory
提出了这一理论。那是一种理论
and it was in search of data. And it
它当时正在寻找数据。而且它
turns out at the same conference, it was
原来在同一次会议上，还有……
one of those incredible moments. You get
那是令人难以置信的时刻之一。你得到
hairs on the back of your neck. There
后颈上的汗毛。那里
was a psychiatrist from Puget Sound,
他是一位来自普吉特海湾的精神科医生，
which is just outside of Seattle on the
它就在西雅图郊外。
west coast of America. And he had been
美国西海岸。他曾是
treating his war veterans in the
他治疗退伍军人的方式
Veterans Administration with a blood
退伍军人事务部与血液
pressure medication called Preszicin.
降压药，名为普瑞斯汀（Preszicin）。
Now, it turns out that prescineric
现在，事实证明，prescineric
drug because it's the Veterans
因为这是退伍军人的药物
Administration, so it's cheap and it
管理方面，所以成本低廉，而且
crosses the bloodb brain barrier. When
能够穿过血脑屏障。什么时候
prescin brain, one of the things that it
大脑，这是它所做的事情之一
does is shut down levels of
这样做会降低……
noradrenaline. Why was this interesting?
去甲肾上腺素。为什么这件事很有趣？
What he was perplexed by is that he was
他感到困惑的是，他
saying, "I'm giving this blood pressure
他说：“我正在测量血压。”
medication to my war veterans with PTSD.
给患有创伤后应激障碍的退伍军人提供药物治疗。
It's not helping too much with their
这对他们来说帮助不大。
blood pressure, but they're all coming
血压，但他们都来了
back saying, "All of those repetitive
回来后说：“所有这些重复的
nightmares, they're starting to go away
噩梦开始消失了。
and I'm sleeping better and I'm feeling
我睡得更好了，感觉也更好了。
better." What he had done was
更好。”他所做的是
inadvertently treated their high levels
无意中处理了他们的高水平
of noradrenaline which were preventing
去甲肾上腺素能够阻止这种情况发生
the brain from kind of stop dropping
大脑停止下降
those levels of noradrenaline down and
去甲肾上腺素水平下降
processing the emotion from the memory.
处理记忆中的情绪。
It was too high in those PTSD PTSD
那些患有创伤后应激障碍（PTSD）的人的PTSD患病率太高了。
patients. But by treating them with this
患者。但通过这种方式对待他们
drug, he'd inadvertently brought the
他无意中带来了毒品
levels of noradrenaline down during REM
快速眼动睡眠期间去甲肾上腺素水平下降
sleep. And then it ultimately became one
睡觉。然后它最终变成了一个
of the only prescribed medications in
唯一处方药物
the Veterans Administration for
退伍军人事务部
repetitive nightmares because why? The
为什么会反复做噩梦？这
brain had finally got down into a quote
大脑终于陷入了引用之中
unquote safe chemical state because
因为处于安全的化学状态
neuradrenaline was too high. But he
神经肾上腺素水平过高。但他
treated them with this drug. So he had
用这种药物治疗他们。所以他有
data that was in search of a theory. I
寻找理论的数据。我
had a theory that was in search of
有一个理论，旨在寻找
clinical data. And so I raced to him
临床数据。于是我赶紧跑向他。
after he gave us a presentation. I said,
他给我们做了报告之后。我说，
"I think I know why you're finding what
“我想我知道你为什么会发现什么
you're finding." I flew him down to
你发现的。”我把他接了过来
Berkeley. We spent all day together. We
伯克利。我们一整天都待在一起。我们
went out for a dinner together. And as I
一起出去吃了顿饭。而当我
said, ultimately he went on to do
他说，最终他还是继续做了
clinical trials. And it it's not a cure
临床试验。但这并非治愈方法。
all for everyone, by the way. It doesn't
顺便说一句，这一切都是为了大家。它不
work for everyone.
为所有人服务。
But and I would say that there is now a
但是，我想说，现在已经存在……
better treatment for nightmares if
如果能更好地治疗噩梦就好了
you're suffering from nightmares and
你正遭受噩梦的困扰，
it's called image rehearsal therapy or
它被称为意象排练疗法或
IRT
红外热成像
and it works through an incredible
它通过一种不可思议的方式运作。
mechanism of memory that we actually had
我们实际上拥有的记忆机制
discovered about gosh 20 years ago now
20年前发现了gosh
called memory reconsolidation.
称为记忆重组。
So when you learn information, it would
所以当你学习信息时，它会
be or let's take a word document.
或者，我们来看一个 Word 文档。
Wouldn't it be staffed if you opened up
如果开门营业，难道不会有工作人员吗？
a word document, you started typing in,
你开始在Word文档中输入内容，
you know, all this information, you hit
你知道，所有这些信息，你都击中了
save, and then you come back tomorrow
保存，明天再回来。
and you double click on the document and
然后你双击文档，
word has shut you out, you can't edit
Word 已将你排除在外，你无法编辑。
the document. That's a really bad
文件。那真是太糟糕了
information storage system. It's a bad
信息存储系统。这是个坏消息
idea. Your human memories are just like
主意。你的人类记忆就像……
this. You form new memories, then you
这。你形成新的记忆，然后你
sleep, and you save them. But when you
睡觉，你就能拯救他们。但是当你
come back and you reactivate that memory
回来后，你重新激活了那段记忆。
when you recall a memory, you bring it
当你回忆起一段记忆时，你会把它带回来。
back into this opened up state, it's
回到这种开放状态，它是
like double clicking on the memory and
就像双击内存一样
the memory becomes fragile and malleable
记忆变得脆弱且易变
once again. So you can update and edit
再次。这样你就可以更新和编辑了
that memory. And then the next night you
那段记忆。然后第二天晚上你
resave it. It's called reconsolidation.
重新保存。这叫做重新整合。
So the first night I save it. That's
所以第一晚我就把它存了起来。那是
consolidation. Then I reactivate it. I
合并。然后我重新激活它。我
modify it and then the next night I
修改它，然后第二天晚上我
reconsolidate it. So coming back to
重新整合它。所以回到……
nightmares, it turns out that you can do
噩梦，原来你可以……
this with trauma patients who have
这种情况也适用于创伤患者。
nightmares caused by trauma. For
由创伤引起的噩梦。为了
example, let's say that you got into a
例如，假设你进入了一个
horrific road accident and you went
可怕的交通事故，然后你就去了
through your brakes failed, you went
即使刹车失灵，你还是走了。
through the red light, you got t-boned,
你闯红灯时被侧面撞击了。
it was just traumatic, was all
那简直太可怕了，仅此而已。
traumatic.
创伤性的。
And what you do with the therapist
以及你和治疗师一起做的事情
because you're having these repetitive
因为你一直在重复这些
nightmares of reliving that same car
噩梦重现那辆车
crash every night, you work with them
你每晚都和他们一起工作，他们也经常撞车。
and you tell them the dream. You recall
然后你把梦境告诉他们。你还记得
the dream actively out loud. But then
将梦境大声说出来。但是后来
working with a therapist, what you do is
与治疗师合作时，你需要做的是：
you modify the outcome. So instead of me
你改变了结果。所以，不是我。
saying the brakes failed, now in the new
他说刹车失灵了，现在在新的
scenario with your therapist, you say,
你说，想象一下你和治疗师的对话场景。
"Well, you look down and there's a
“嗯，你往下看，就会发现……”
manual handbrake in the car." So you
车里的手动手刹。”所以你
realize that you can actually just
意识到你其实可以只是
gradually start applying the handbrake
逐渐开始拉起手刹
and you bring the car to a safe halt and
然后你安全地把车停了下来。
you go to the side of the road and
你走到路边，
there's no accident. And what you're
没有发生意外。而你是什么
doing is you're reopening back up that
你现在做的就是重新打开它。
trauma memory and you're rewriting the
创伤记忆，而你正在改写它
narrative and then you sleep and you
叙述，然后你睡觉，然后你
update that memory. And by recalling and
更新该内存。通过回忆和
rewriting the memory each and every
每次都重写内存
waking day, you end up dissipating the
醒来后，你最终会消散……
severity of your trauma nightmare every
你的创伤噩梦的严重程度
single night. And it's called image
一晚。它被称为图像
rehearsal therapy for nightmares. It's
噩梦排练疗法。它是
incredibly powerful. It's probably more
威力无比。可能更多
powerful than the presin drug that I
比我服用的那种普瑞辛药物效力更强。
spoke about.
谈到。
&gt;&gt; And I'm guessing people don't sleep and
我猜人们都不睡觉，
also have nightmares for a variety of
也经常做各种各样的噩梦
reasons relating to trauma generally.
与创伤相关的普遍原因。
Ah, it's a good question perhaps which
啊，这或许是个好问题，哪个？
is in some ways what's the difference
从某种意义上说，区别是什么？
between a bad dream and a nightmare
介于噩梦和坏梦之间
[clears throat]
[清嗓子]
&gt;&gt; because all of us will have bad dreams.
因为我们都会做噩梦。
Bad dreams are usually things that
噩梦通常是……
happen infrequently. Maybe you have them
发生频率不高。也许你也有它们
once every month, every couple of
每月一次，每隔一段时间
months.
几个月。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; The definition of nightmare disorder is
噩梦障碍的定义是：
that you have to have these dreams
你必须拥有这些梦想
frequently, maybe at least twice a week.
经常，可能至少每周两次。
They have to wake you up
他们得叫醒你。
out of your sleep and you have vivid
你从睡梦中惊醒，脑海中浮现出清晰的画面。
recall.
记起。
Plus, it has to cause you some kind of
此外，它还必须给你造成某种……
daytime distress where you're not
白天感到焦虑，而你却不在
feeling good about the day. It's causing
今天感觉不错。它造成
you mental anguish. And furthermore, if
你的精神痛苦。而且，如果
it starts to lead to hopelessness or a
它开始导致绝望或
sense that your life is not worth
感觉自己的生命毫无价值
living, you absolutely need to go and
活着，你绝对需要去……
see someone. And here's what we've
见某人。这就是我们所拥有的
discovered about nightmares.
发现了关于噩梦的真相。
Short sleep duration, not getting enough
睡眠时间短，睡眠不足
sleep, sleeping less than six hours
睡眠不足，睡眠时间少于六小时
predicts by about 100 to 150% higher
预测值高出约 100% 至 150%。
percentage chance of you having suicidal
你出现自杀倾向的概率是多少？
thoughts, attempting suicide or
有自杀念头，试图自杀或
tragically suicide completion. That's
悲剧的是，自杀身亡。那是
bad sleep.
睡眠质量差。
It turns out that nightmares, so if
原来噩梦就是这样，所以如果
short sleep has a 150% higher likelihood
睡眠不足的患病几率高出150%。
of suicidality,
自杀倾向
having nightmares has an 800%
做噩梦的概率高达 800%。
higher likelihood of suicidal tendencies
自杀倾向的可能性更高
associated with it. Now, we don't think
与之相关。现在，我们并不认为
that nightmares are causing suicidal
噩梦会导致自杀倾向
tendencies. That's not what we believe.
倾向。我们不这么认为。
We believe, however, nightmares much
然而，我们相信，噩梦很大程度上……
more than disrupted sleep. Nightmares
不仅仅是睡眠紊乱。噩梦
seem to be the canary in the coal mine.
就像煤矿里的金丝雀一样，预示着危险的到来。
Nightmares are this distress beacon that
噩梦就像一个求救信号，
leaks from our electrical static of
我们静电泄漏
sleep at night and it is incredibly
晚上睡得很好，这真是太棒了
sensitive to your suicidal tendencies,
对你的自杀倾向很敏感，
your suicidal attempts and as I said
你的自杀企图，正如我所说
suicide completion as well. Nightmares
自杀也已完成。噩梦
are a biomarker. If you are having
是一种生物标志物。如果您有
distressing nightmares that are waking
令人痛苦的噩梦会醒来
you up, you need to go and speak to
你起来，你需要去和……谈谈
someone about it. It's absolutely
有人知道这件事。绝对是
paramount because there are good
至关重要，因为有很多好的
effective ways that you can dissipate
你可以采取的有效方法来消除
those nightmares.
那些噩梦。
&gt;&gt; I was trying to understand whether it's
我试图弄明白这是否是
a a malfunction or it's a signal. I
是故障还是信号？我
guess it might be both.
我觉得可能是两者兼有。
&gt;&gt; It's a very good question which is is it
这是一个很好的问题，那就是它到底是什么？
adaptive or is it maladaptive? Is it a
它是适应性的还是不适应性的？它是
good thing to have a nightmare or is it
做噩梦是件好事吗？还是说……
a bad thing to have a nightmare? We
做噩梦是件坏事吗？我们
don't quite have the answer to that. But
我不太清楚答案。但
let me come back to I told you there
让我回到我之前跟你说过的事情。
were two functions of dream sleep and
梦境睡眠有两个功能：
we're still in the first one which is
我们目前仍处于第一阶段，即
emotional first aid and it turns out
情绪急救，结果证明
that your thinking is incredibly astute.
你的想法非常精辟。
We believe that at least normative
我们认为至少在规范方面
dreams not nightmares nightmares may be
梦境而非噩梦，噩梦可能是
the system failing just as I spoke about
正如我刚才所说，系统就崩溃了。
in PTSD with repetitive nightmares and
患有创伤后应激障碍并伴有反复噩梦
in fact repetitive nightmares are so
事实上，反复出现的噩梦是如此令人痛苦。
consistent in PTSD that you can't
创伤后应激障碍的一致性是，你无法……
receive a diagnosis of PTSD without
未经诊断就被诊断为创伤后应激障碍
having repetitive nightmares. That's how
反复做噩梦。就是这样
sort of diagnostic they are. But
它们具有一定的诊断价值。但
dreaming, normative dreaming, even if
做梦，规范的梦，即使
they're bad dreams, is beneficial. How
它们是噩梦，但对身体有益。如何
could I make that claim? There was a
我可以提出这样的主张吗？曾有一个
study done by a late sleep scientist, a
一项由已故睡眠科学家进行的研究表明
woman called Rosaline Cartwright, and
一个名叫罗莎琳·卡特赖特的女人，
she was studying people who had gone
她正在研究那些已经离世的人。
through a difficult period, let's say
比如说，经历一段艰难时期
bereiement or very bitter divorce. And
丧亲或非常痛苦的离婚。和
they had become depressed because of
他们因为这个原因变得抑郁了。
that experience. And around the time of
那段经历。大约在……时期
the experience, she was seeing them as a
这段经历，她把他们视为一种
therapist and she was having them do
治疗师，她让他们这样做
dream recall. So she was having them
梦境回忆。所以她当时正在吃它们
create dream diaries every single night.
每晚都写梦日记。
And then she tracked these patients for
然后她追踪了这些患者……
a year. And it turned out about roughly
一年。结果大约是
half of them by 12 months later had
12个月后，其中一半人已经
remitted from their depression. They'd
抑郁症缓解了。他们会
got better. They'd got past their
情况好转了。他们已经度过了难关
depression. The other half were still
沮丧。另一半人仍然
depressed. So then she took that data
郁闷。于是她就收集了这些数据。
and she went back with those two groups
她和那两拨人一起回去了。
and she said, "Is there anything
她问道：“有什么事吗？”
different about their dreams and it
他们对梦想的看法各不相同，而且
turned out that there was both of those
结果发现这两种情况都存在。
groups of people whether they cut free
人群是否切断自由
of their depression or they stayed in
他们要么沉浸在抑郁中，要么就待在家里。
their depression. Both of them were
他们的抑郁症。他们俩都是
dreaming at the time. Both of them were
当时正在做梦。他们俩都是
having REM sleep, both of them were
他们俩都处于快速眼动睡眠期。
dreaming. What was the difference then?
做梦。那么区别在哪里呢？
Those individuals that went on to gain
那些后来获得成就的人
remission to their depression and get
缓解他们的抑郁症并获得
get better, those people were dreaming
好起来吧，那些人只是在做梦。
of the events itself at the time that
事件本身在当时的情况是
they were happening. Whereas those other
它们正在发生。而其他那些
people who didn't go on to gain clinical
那些没有继续获得临床资格的人
remission, they were dreaming. They just
缓解？他们只是在做梦。他们只是
weren't dreaming of the experiences
并非梦见这些经历
itself. In other words, it's not just
本身。换句话说，这不仅仅是
sufficient to have REM sleep. It's not
足以进入快速眼动睡眠。它不是
just sufficient to have REM sleep and be
刚好足以进行快速眼动睡眠，并且
dreaming. You need to be dreaming of the
做梦。你需要梦想着
difficult, painful experience that
一段艰难而痛苦的经历
you're going through to gain that
你正在经历这一切以获得那个
clinical resolution.
临床症状缓解。
&gt;&gt; Damn. So, if I have something going on
该死。所以，如果我有什么事要办的话
in my life, I need to think about it
在我的生活中，我需要好好想想这件事。
before I go to bed.
在我睡觉之前。
&gt;&gt; Yes and [laughter] no.
是，也不是。（笑）
What you have to realize is that it's
你必须意识到，这是
taken us, depending on who you believe,
带走了我们，这取决于你相信谁。
3.4 million years of evolution to
经过340万年的进化
develop this thing called homminid sleep
发展出一种叫做人科睡眠的东西
and dreaming and REM sleep.
以及做梦和快速眼动睡眠。
I think that that evolutionary millions
我认为那是数百万年的进化史。
of years probably understands what the
多年的经验可能明白……
correct blueprint playlist of dream
梦境的正确蓝图播放列表
experience is and should be for me at
经验对我来说是，也应该是……
night. And therefore, I don't need to
夜晚。因此，我不需要
worry about it. I shouldn't try to force
别担心。我不应该强求。
anything. That's the first function of
任何事物。这是第一个功能
dream sleep is that it's emotional first
做梦的本质是情绪性的。
aid. And we've got good data for that.
援助。我们掌握了这方面的可靠数据。
But there's a second completely
但还有第二种完全不同的
independent benefit of dreaming.
做梦的独立益处。
Dreaming is a form offormational
做梦是一种信息形式
alchemy. Dreaming is creativity.
炼金术。梦想即创造力。
Now I told you that during deep non-REM
我刚才跟你说过，在深度非快速眼动睡眠期间。
sleep, we take new memories that we've
睡眠中，我们会带走新的记忆。
learned and we fixate them like Amber
我们学会了，然后像琥珀一样把它们固定住。
sort of setting a fossil in and we do
就像把化石放进去一样，我们确实这么做了。
that during deep sleep. That saves the
在深度睡眠期间。这样就省钱了。
individual pieces of the new stuff. Then
新东西的各个部件。然后
comes along REM sleep which happens
快速眼动睡眠随之而来，这种情况
after deep sleep. And the second phase
深度睡眠后。第二阶段
of memory processing happens. That's
内存处理过程发生。那是
where REM sleep starts to fuse all of
快速眼动睡眠开始融合所有
the things that you've recently been
你最近做的事情
learning with this entire back catalog
利用这套完整的过往曲目进行学习
of information. And so you wake up with
信息。于是你醒来时……
a revised mindwide web of associations
一个经过修订的、覆盖整个大脑的联想网络
that is capable of diving solutions to
能够提供潜水解决方案
previously impenetrable problems. So,
以前难以解决的问题。所以，
you know, it's almost you, it's like
你知道吗，这几乎就是你，就像
group therapy for memories that REM
针对快速眼动睡眠记忆的团体治疗
sleep gathers in all of the information
睡眠会收集所有信息
that you've learned during the day and
你当天学到的东西
everyone gets a name badge. But unlike
每个人都会拿到一个姓名牌。但与此不同的是
the waking logical connections that you
你清醒时的逻辑联系
make already, REM sleep is like a Google
已经做好了，快速眼动睡眠就像谷歌
search gone wrong that you insert, let's
搜索出错，您输入的内容，我们来看一下。
say, diary of a CEO, and it takes you to
比如说，《CEO日记》，它会带你到
page 20. This is dream sleep.
第20页。这是梦境睡眠。
&gt;&gt; Mhm.
嗯。
&gt;&gt; And it's about some field hockey game in
故事是关于一场曲棍球比赛的。
Utah. And you think, hang on a second,
犹他州。然后你会想，等等，
but how on earth is that? Well, there
但这怎么可能呢？嗯，就是这样。
was someone who had, you know, they had
是那种……你知道，他们曾经……
found a diary that had been lost, you
你找到了一本遗失的日记。
know, a long time ago. And the guy who'
很久以前就知道了。还有那个人
found it was a famous CEO in the town of
发现他是该镇一位著名的首席执行官
this sort of, you know, Utah as he was
你知道，犹他州就是这样的地方。
watching. So, it's a distant,
正在观看。所以，这是一个遥远的……
non-obvious connection. But it turns out
不明显的联系。但事实证明
that that's what dreaming is all about.
这就是梦的本质。
It's [snorts] almost as though we go to
简直就像我们去……
sleep with the pieces of the jigsaw, but
抱着拼图碎片睡觉，但是
by way of dreaming, we wake up with the
通过做梦，我们醒来时……
puzzle complete. And when you start to
拼图完成。当你开始
fuse things that shouldn't should not
不应该融合的东西不应该融合
normally go together, but when they do
通常情况下它们会一起出现，但当它们……
every now and again cause a marked
时不时地会引起明显的
advance in evolutionary fitness, that is
进化适应性方面的进步，即
the biological basis of creativity. It's
创造力的生物学基础。它是
the reason that no one has ever told
没人告诉过的原因
you, "Look, Stephen, you should stay
你，“听着，斯蒂芬，你应该留下来。”
awake on a problem." They don't. They
醒来就发现问题了。”他们不会。他们
tell you to sleep on a problem. And in
告诉你先冷静思考一下问题。并且
every language that I've inquired about
我询问过的每一种语言
to date from, you know, from French to
追溯到，你知道，从法国到
Swahili, that term sleeping on a problem
斯瓦希里语中，那个词指的是对问题视而不见。
or something like it exists. My point
或者说，类似的东西确实存在。我的观点
being is the benefit, the creative
存在即益处，创造力
benefit of sleep transcends cultural
睡眠的益处超越文化范畴
boundaries. It's a common experience of
边界。这是很常见的经历
homo sapiens.
智人。
&gt;&gt; There is an invisible tax on salespeople
销售人员面临着一种隐形税。
that no one really talks about enough.
很少有人真正谈论这个问题。
the mental load of remembering
记忆的心理负担
everything like meeting notes,
会议记录之类的所有东西
timelines, and everything in between
时间线，以及介于两者之间的一切
until we started using our sponsors
直到我们开始使用赞助商的服务
product called Pipe Drive, one of the
名为 Pipe Drive 的产品，是其中之一
best CRM tools for small and
适用于小型企业的最佳 CRM 工具
medium-sized business owners. The idea
中型企业主。这个想法
here was that it might alleviate some of
这样做或许能缓解一些问题。
the unnecessary cognitive overload that
不必要的认知负荷
my team was carrying so that they could
我的团队正在努力，以便他们能够
spend less time in the weeds of admin
减少在繁琐的行政事务上花费的时间
and more time with clients, in-person
以及更多与客户面对面交流的时间。
meetings, and building relationships.
会议和建立关系。
Pipe Drive has enabled this to happen.
Pipe Drive 使这一切成为可能。
It's such a simple but effective CRM
它是一款简单却高效的客户关系管理系统。
that automates the tedious, repetitive,
它可以自动执行繁琐、重复性的工作，
and timeconuming parts of the sales
以及销售过程中耗时的部分。
process. And now our team can nurture
过程。现在我们的团队可以培养
those leads and still have bandwidth to
这些线索，而且还有余力
focus on the higher priority tasks that
专注于优先级更高的任务
actually get the deal over the line.
最终促成交易。
Over a 100,000 companies across 170
超过10万家公司，遍布170个国家
countries already use Pipe Drive to grow
各国已经利用管道驱动技术来发展
their business, and I've been using it
他们的生意，我一直在用它
for almost a decade now. Try it free for
已经持续近十年了。免费试用
30 days. No credit card needed, no
30天。无需信用卡，
payment needed. Just use my link
需要付款。直接用我的链接就行了。
pipederive.com/ceo
pipederive.com/ceo
to get started today. That's
今天就开始吧。那是
piperive.com/ceo.
piperive.com/ceo。
Just give me 15 seconds to explain how
请给我15秒钟时间解释一下。
you can build a viable business online.
你可以在网上建立一个可行的企业。
The people I see winning in life don't
我所看到的那些在生活中取得成功的人，并没有
have a perfect plan. They just take the
制定一个完美的计划。他们就拿走了
first step and then the next and then
第一步，然后是下一步，然后
they keep going. They stay obsessed and
他们继续前进。他们一直很痴迷，
they stay consistent. And Stand, a
他们始终保持一致。而 Stand，
platform I co-own and one of our
我共同拥有的平台，也是我们其中之一
sponsors, is the best first step to help
赞助商是帮助他人的最佳第一步。
turn your knowledge into income. It only
将你的知识转化为收入。它只是
takes a couple of minutes to launch your
启动需要几分钟时间
business and start selling digital
开展业务并开始销售数字产品
products, coaching, memberships, or
产品、辅导、会员资格或
communities online without any tech
无需任何技术的在线社区
headaches or endless setup. Thousands of
令人头疼的问题或无休止的设置。数千
entrepreneurs, creators, and risk-takers
企业家、创造者和冒险家
use Stan to take control of their
利用斯坦来控制他们
future. Because Stan is for
未来。因为斯坦是为
entrepreneurs, for those willing to put
对于那些愿意付出的人来说，企业家们
in the work and bet on themselves. If
在工作中，他们相信自己。如果
you're ready to start building, join us.
准备好开始建设了吗？加入我们吧！
Launch your business today with a free
立即免费开启您的创业之旅
14-day trial at
14天试用期
stephvenbartlet.stan.store.
stephvenbartlet.stan.store。
What is the uh most important thing we
最重要的事情是什么？
haven't talked about as it relates to
还没有谈到它与……的关系
the personas of those people that are
那些人的性格
probably listening right now and for the
可能现在正在收听，并且是为了
reasons why they might have clicked? You
他们点击的原因是什么？你
know that they're probably looking
要知道他们可能正在查看
again. We have the optimizers, we have
再次。我们有优化器，我们有
those that have bad sleep habits and
那些睡眠习惯不良的人
then we have those that have real sleep
然后还有一些人真正睡得好。
disorders. What is the most important
疾病。最重要的是什么？
thing we haven't talked about that we
我们还没谈到的一件事是……
should have talked about for them?
我应该替他们谈谈吗？
&gt;&gt; It may be the dystopian future.
这或许就是反乌托邦式的未来。
&gt;&gt; Let's talk about the dystopian future
我们来谈谈反乌托邦的未来吧。
then. [laughter]
然后。 [笑声]
What is a podcast if it does not
如果播客不具备以下特点，那它还算什么播客呢？
contain, at least in this day and age, a
至少在当今时代，它包含着
dystopian future?
反乌托邦的未来？
&gt;&gt; What is the dystopian future?
反乌托邦的未来是什么样的？
&gt;&gt; Probably the most spectacular discovery
或许是最惊人的发现
that has happened since you and I last
自从你我上次……以来，就发生了这样的事。
spoke is the discovery of what we call
辐条是对我们所说的发现
the genetic short sleepers.
天生睡眠时间短的人。
These are individuals who by way of a
这些人通过以下方式
genetic mutation can survive on as
基因突变可以存活下来
little as 6.25 hours of sleep. In other
睡眠时间仅6.25小时。在其他方面
words, 6 hours and 15 minutes of sleep.
字数，6 小时 15 分钟睡眠。
and they show zero impairment in their
他们的各项能力均未受损。
brain or their body, they can do just
大脑或身体，它们可以做到。
fine on six hours of sleep.
睡六个小时就没事了。
&gt;&gt; I know where this is going.
我知道事情会如何发展。
&gt;&gt; And we have four genes that we've
我们有四个基因
identified now. The first two genes. The
已确认。前两个基因。这
first one identified was called the DEC
第一个被发现的被称为DEC
2 gene, DEC2 gene. The second was called
2 基因，DEC2 基因。第二个被称作
the ADRB1 gene, which I granted I know
ADRB1基因，我承认我知道它。
it sounds like the next Radio Head
听起来像是下一个电台司令乐队。
album, but it's it's not the next Radio
这张专辑，但它不是下一张《Radio》。
Head album. Um, and these genes allow
专辑封面。嗯，这些基因允许
these individuals
这些人
to get away with an amount of sleep that
为了逃避睡眠不足的问题，
normally would cause predictive disease
通常会导致预测性疾病
and sickness just as we've spoken about.
就像我们之前谈到的那样，还有疾病。
So, at this point, probably some people
所以，在这一点上，可能有些人
listening are thinking,
听着，你在思考，
I think I'm one of those people. Just to
我觉得我就是那种人。只是为了
put it in context, your the probability
结合上下文来看，这就是概率。
that you will be struck by lightning in
你会被闪电击中
your lifetime is 0.00. 00064
你的寿命为 0.00。 00064
highly unlikely the chances of you
你出现这种情况的可能性极低。
having the ADRB1 gene is 0.004
携带 ADRB1 基因的概率为 0.004
&gt;&gt; and the DBR1 gene is the short sleeper
DBR1基因是短睡眠基因。
gene
基因
&gt;&gt; is one of the short sleeping genes. So
是短睡眠基因之一。所以
in other words you are statistically
换句话说，从统计学角度来看，你是……
more likely to be struck by lightning in
更容易被闪电击中
your lifetime than you are to have that
你一生中拥有的比你拥有的还要多。
short sleeping gene. So the probability
短睡眠基因。所以概率
is is is low by the way.
顺便说一句，这个值很低。
Why is this the case? Why do they get
为什么会这样？他们为什么会得到
away with this? And we've discovered now
摆脱它？而我们现在发现
by using sort of um genetic
通过使用某种基因
manipulations, we understand why. First
我们明白这是为什么。第一的
thing is that they have a much stronger
问题在于他们拥有更强大的力量。
wake drive during the day. So you and I
白天进行唤醒驾驶。所以你和我
and all the rest of our mere mortals
以及我们所有其他凡人
will have these kind of like
会有这些类似的东西
oscillations in our consciousness
我们意识中的波动
throughout the day where we'll have dips
一整天我们都会进行一些小动作
where we feel a bit sleepy and we're
我们感到有点困，而且我们
dragging and then we'll kind of get they
拖着，然后我们就能得到他们
don't have that. They have it's like a
我没有那个。他们有，就像……
light switch, like a dimmer switch. You
类似调光开关的灯开关。你
and I, we may sort of go up to like 80%
而我，我们可能会达到80%左右。
brightness when we're awake and then
我们清醒时光线明亮，然后
sometimes it will flicker and then we'll
有时它会闪烁，然后我们就会
go down and we'll have pretty solid
下去之后，我们就能稳稳地控制局面了。
sleep, maybe sort of, you know, down to
睡觉，也许有点像，你知道，到
20% but the lights are not quite off,
20%，但灯还没完全关掉。
you know, where sleep is is good but not
你知道，睡眠在哪里是好的，但不是
amazing. These people have an all or
惊人的。这些人全部或
nothing phenomenon. They are all 100%
无现象。它们都是100%
bright light throughout the day and then
白天光线充足，然后
and they can maintain 17 18 hours of
它们可以维持17到18个小时。
wakefulness, no problem.
保持清醒没问题。
And then when they sleep, they sleep
然后当他们睡觉时，他们就睡着了。
hard. They have much more efficient
难的。它们的效率要高得多。
sleep. Remember we spoke about sleep
睡觉。还记得我们之前聊过睡眠吗？
efficiency and I want it 85% or above.
效率方面，我希望达到 85% 或更高。
Almost all of their time at night spent
他们几乎所有的夜间时间都用来
in solid, stable, sound sleep. And the
处于稳定、良好的睡眠状态。以及
depth of their sleep they have is
他们睡眠的深度是
greater. So they're awake more
更大。所以他们更清醒一些。
throughout the day. They build up a
全天都是如此。他们建立起一个
stronger wakefulness drive which is
更强的觉醒驱动力，即
called adenosine which means that when
称为腺苷，这意味着当
they sleep they sleep harder throughout
他们睡得很沉，整晚都睡得很沉。
the night which means that they can then
夜晚意味着他们可以
be awake for more powerful stints during
在工作期间保持清醒，以便进行更高强度的训练。
the day. Second they don't suffer from
那天。其次，他们不会遭受……
jet lag.
时差反应。
&gt;&gt; What the what do you mean they don't
什么？什么意思？他们不……
suffer from jet lag?
你是否饱受时差困扰？
&gt;&gt; Because of their strength of wakefulness
因为他们清醒的程度
drive when they are circadium misaligned
当它们的昼夜节律错位时，它们会驱动它们。
it's as though they haven't traveled
就好像他们从未旅行过一样。
between time zones. They can just stay
不同时区之间。他们可以留下来。
awake. They have a strong drive for
醒。他们有着强烈的进取心
wakefulness. Who are these people?
清醒。这些人是谁？
&gt;&gt; They are these genetic short sleepers.
他们是天生的短睡眠者。
&gt;&gt; And do they pass these genes onto their
他们会将这些基因遗传给下一代吗？
children?
孩子们？
&gt;&gt; Yes, they do.
是的，他们确实会这样做。
&gt;&gt; And so their children have the same
因此，他们的孩子也拥有同样的特质。
&gt;&gt; they're heritable.
它们是可遗传的。
&gt;&gt; Can I have
我可以要吗？
&gt;&gt; Well, firstly, let's take a step back
首先，让我们退一步想想。
before I get to the dystopian. This
在我谈到反乌托邦之前。这
tells us something above and beyond
这告诉我们一些超越寻常的事情。
biological fascination. It says there is
对生物学的着迷。它说有
a profound statement in evolution.
这是进化论中一个意义深远的论断。
Mother nature has figured out a way
大自然母亲已经找到了解决办法
genetically to zip file sleep.
从基因层面来说，睡眠就像一个压缩文件。
&gt;&gt; Zip file. You can compress eight down
压缩文件。你可以把八块压缩成小块
into six. You know on your computer how
分成六份。你知道在你的电脑上如何
you can get a collection of files, you
你可以获得一系列文件，你
group them all together and then you say
把它们全部放在一起，然后你说
compress these files and you compress
压缩这些文件，然后你就可以压缩它们了。
them and you zip them into a single file
将它们压缩成一个文件
and it's dense, it's packed and it takes
它很密实，很拥挤，而且需要
up less amount of volume.
增加的体积较少。
&gt;&gt; Do they have the same life expectancy?
他们的预期寿命相同吗？
&gt;&gt; They seem to from everything we can
从我们所能了解到的所有信息来看，他们似乎都是如此。
tell.
告诉。
So somewhere along the way through
所以，在某个时候
genetics, evolution has figured out how
遗传学和进化已经解决了这个问题。
to go from eight and compress it down to
从八进制压缩到
six. Where's the dystopia? Well, we've
六。反乌托邦在哪里？嗯，我们已经
all heard of crisper, which is this
大家都听说过crisper，就是这个。
genetic editing manipulation tool that a
基因编辑操作工具
lab next door to mine at UC Berkeley
我在加州大学伯克利分校的实验室就在隔壁。
discovered, Jennifer Downer. She won a
发现者是詹妮弗·唐纳。她赢得了
Nobel Prize for it. Is there some
因这项成就获得诺贝尔奖。是否有一些
future,
未来，
and I hope not. Is there some future
我希望不会。未来会怎样？
where we start to genetically engineer
我们开始进行基因工程的地方
people from a need of 7 to n hours down
需要7到n小时的人们
to a need of six? Imagine the reduction
需要六个吗？想象一下这种减少
in health care burden cost because right
医疗保健负担成本，因为这是权利
now the burden of insufficient sleep is
现在睡眠不足的负担是
vast.
广阔的。
Insufficient sleep will cost most
睡眠不足会付出最大的代价
nations about 2% of their GDP. Here in
各国约占其GDP的2%。在此处
America it's $411 billion of cost caused
美国为此付出了4110亿美元的代价。
by insufficient sleep. In the United
睡眠不足。在美国
Kingdom it's about $40 billion. In
王国规模约为400亿美元。在
Japan, it's $50 billion.
日本，是500亿美元。
Solve the sleep loss epidemic, which
解决睡眠不足的流行问题，
I've been trying to do by saying, you
我一直试图通过说“你”来做到这一点。
know, sleep enough. And you could, you
要知道，要保证充足的睡眠。而且你也可以，你
know, cause massive financial disruption
知道，这会造成巨大的金融混乱
in the good way. But here, if you start
往好的方向发展。但是在这里，如果你开始
to genetically engineer people, could
对人类进行基因改造，可能会
you reduce the burden that is caused by
你减轻了由此造成的负担
people currently who need 7 to9 and take
目前需要7到9个人的人
that burden away because they no longer
因为他们不再有那个负担，所以那个负担也随之消失了。
need 7 to9?
需要7到9个吗？
&gt;&gt; Why did you say I hope not? Well, I hope
你为什么说我希望不是？我希望如此。
not because I think here's the following
并非因为我认为以下情况属实
that happens. It's not that I'm against
这种情况确实会发生。我并非反对
that idea. I would love for the burden
那个想法。我愿意承担这份负担。
of disease and sickness to be reduced
减少疾病和患病
and people not to suffer from that. And
让人们免受这种痛苦。和
if I could find a way to do it
如果我能找到办法的话
genetically, I would. And you could
从基因上来说，我会的。而且你还可以
think about people arguing, well,
想想人们争论的情景，嗯，
imagine the productivity benefits. I
想象一下这将带来的生产力提升。我
mean, huge upsides of that. You know,
这意味着巨大的好处。你知道，
people are being more productive and
人们的生产力提高了，
they're probably spending more. So from
他们的支出可能更多了。所以从
a capitalistic society, it's the perfect
在一个资本主义社会里，它是完美的。
it's the adman's dream because when when
这是广告人的梦想，因为当……
you're asleep, it's antithetical to a
你睡着了，这与……背道而驰
capitalistic society. Why? Because
资本主义社会。为什么？因为
you're neither producing nor consuming.
你既不生产也不消费。
That's very cynical and I don't buy into
这太愤世嫉俗了，我不认同。
that. But nevertheless, so all of these
那。但是，尽管如此，所有这些
things would be marketkedly better,
市场情况会好转，
would they not be, if we genetically
如果我们从基因上看，难道它们不会是吗？
engineered this way. Why do I fear it? I
就是这样设计的。我为什么会害怕它？我
know for a fact that as soon as six
确切知道，早在六岁时
becomes the new eight, everyone starts
成为新的八，每个人都开始
sleeping four.
睡四个人。
And now I'm just back into the same
现在我又回到了原点。
battle again because six is the minimum
因为六人是最低要求，所以还要再打一场。
that you need. And they say, "Well, if
你需要的。他们说：“嗯，如果
that's the minimum, then I'll sleep
这是最低要求，然后我就睡觉。
four." And when I find the next gene
四个。”当我找到下一个基因时
that allows you to get away with four
这样你就可以逃脱四次惩罚了。
hours of sleep, then they say, "Well,
睡了几个小时后，他们说：“好吧，
that's great. So then I can go down to
那太棒了。所以然后我就可以下去了
two." And it's a form of almost this
二。”而且它几乎是一种这样的形式
sleep currency, you know, inflation that
睡眠货币，你知道，通货膨胀。
I'm always fighting a battle and at some
我总是在战斗，而且有时
point I'll always be on the wrong side
我的意思是，我永远都会站在错误的一边。
of that battle.
那场战役。
&gt;&gt; Crazy. These people with this gene can
疯狂的。拥有这种基因的人可以
thrive on four to six hours sleep
每天睡四到六小时才能精神饱满
without any negative effects that most
几乎没有任何负面影响
of us would experience.
我们中的许多人都会经历这一切。
[clears throat and cough]
[清嗓子，咳嗽]
&gt;&gt; Correct. It's
正确的。它是
&gt;&gt; so you know what is going on there and
这样你就知道那里发生了什么事了。
what we're seeing is this this
我们看到的是这个
incredible density of sleep and this
睡眠密度惊人，而且
epic drive for wakefulness. They are
对清醒状态的强烈追求。他们是
more efficient sleepers. They can get
睡眠效率更高。他们可以得到
done what you and I take eight hours to
完成了你我花费八小时才能完成的事情
do. They can do it in six. And I guess
做。他们六分钟就能完成。我想
you is there a way to easily test this?
有没有什么简单的方法可以测试这个？
I guess go into a lab and get
我想应该去实验室弄到
&gt;&gt; Yeah. So if you've ever done, you know,
是的。所以如果你曾经这样做过，你就知道，
I think um you know all of those genetic
我想，嗯，你知道所有这些基因
testing kits out there where and a lot
市面上有很多检测试剂盒，而且很多都存在这个问题。
of them will allow you to download your
其中一些将允许您下载您的
raw data. All you need to do is download
原始数据。你只需要下载即可。
your raw raw data and then there's a
你的原始数据，然后还有
company I think it's called Prometheus.
我想这家公司叫普罗米修斯。
Again, I have no affiliation with them.
再次声明，我与他们没有任何关联。
I don't know how valid they are, but
我不知道这些说法是否属实，但是
then you upload your raw genetic data
然后您上传您的原始基因数据
into their model and then it will list
将其输入他们的模型，然后它会列出
and it will rip it apart. So normally
它会把它撕成碎片。所以通常情况下
those genetic services they give you a
他们提供的那些基因检测服务
nice PDF and it's kind of like maybe 15
不错的PDF文件，大概有15个左右。
pages of all of the the main stuff and
所有主要内容的页面和
it's this Prometheus is kind of like the
普罗米修斯有点像……
you know the old school kind of
你知道，那种老派的
scientist nerdy. They will just give you
科学家书呆子。他们只会给你
this kind of raw just kind of janky you
这种未经加工的，有点粗糙。
know 50page report. The interface is
知道一份50页的报告。界面是
terrible, but you can go in there and
很糟糕，但你可以进去。
you can search to see, you know, what
你可以搜索一下，看看，你知道，什么
form of the deck 2 gene do I have or
我拥有哪种类型的2号基因？
what form of the ADRB1 gene do I have?
我携带的是哪种类型的ADRB1基因？
And it will tell you, are you a genetic
它会告诉你，你是不是基因型
short sleeper or are you not and you can
你是睡眠短的人，还是睡眠不短的人，你可以
find out.
查出。
&gt;&gt; I've been thinking a lot lately about um
我最近一直在想……
about certain diet states as well and
关于某些饮食状况也存在类似情况。
whether they have an impact on sleep.
它们是否对睡眠有影响。
We're talking about circadian rhythms
我们正在讨论的是昼夜节律。
there. I was thinking about fasting a
那里。我当时在考虑禁食。
lot and also I think me myself and Jack
很多，而且我觉得我自己和杰克
over there are in ketosis right now. I
那边的人现在都处于酮症状态。我
was wondering if you
我想知道你是否
&gt;&gt; when you think about brain performance
当你思考大脑功能时
and sleep and different sort of states
以及睡眠和各种不同的状态
do you think much about fasting or
你经常考虑禁食吗？
&gt;&gt; about ketosis or
关于酮症或
&gt;&gt; Yeah, it's a mixed bag if you look at
是的，如果你仔细观察的话，情况就比较复杂了。
it. Certainly what you eat will change
它。当然，你的饮食习惯会发生变化。
how you sleep. But perhaps more
你的睡眠质量如何？但或许更多
powerfully is how you sleep dramatically
强大的睡眠方式是戏剧性的
changes how you eat and how you dispose
改变你的饮食方式和排泄方式
of those calories and what happens
这些卡路里会产生什么影响？
inside of your body when you are
当你……的时候，在你体内
underslept.
睡眠不足。
&gt;&gt; But
但
&gt;&gt; so I have lots of cravings when I've
所以当我……的时候，我就会有很多想吃的东西。
short slept.
睡眠不足。
&gt;&gt; Yes, you have. And there's a reason why
是的，你已经有了。这其中是有原因的。
is firstly two appetite hormones called
首先是两种食欲激素，它们分别是
leptin and ghrein will go in opposite
瘦素和胃饥饿素会相反
directions. So they sound like hobbits,
方向。所以他们听起来像霍比特人。
I And I've got some Lord of the Rings
我还有一些《指环王》
thing here, but leptin is the signal
这里有个问题，但瘦素是信号。
that says to your brain, you're full.
这会向你的大脑发出信号：你已经吃饱了。
&gt;&gt; Yeah,
是的，
&gt;&gt; you're you're satiated. Don't eat
你已经吃饱了。不要吃
anymore. Ghrein is the opposite. It kind
不再是了。格林则恰恰相反。它那种
of makes your tum stom tummy growl and
它会让你的肚子咕噜咕噜叫个不停。
it says you're hungry. You're not full.
它说你饿了。你还没吃饱。
You need to eat more. When you are
你需要多吃点。当你
underslept, leptin, which says you're
睡眠不足，瘦素水平升高，这表明你……
full, stop eating. That hormone is
吃饱了，停止进食。那种激素是
impaired. It drops away. So you lose the
受损。它掉了下去。所以你输了
I'm full signal. and worse still the
信号满格。更糟糕的是
ghrelin signal which says I'm hungry
饥饿素信号表明我饿了
that increases
增加
and so now you have about a 30 to 40%
所以现在大概有30%到40%的份额。
increased hunger drive and the final
饥饿感增强以及最终
part of this is that when you are
部分原因是当你
underslept and taking on board calories
睡眠不足，摄入过多卡路里
the way that you dispose of that energy
你如何处理这些能量
is different your body has a higher
情况有所不同，你的身体有更高的
prediliction when you are sleepdeprived
睡眠不足时的偏好
to disposing of calories as fat rather
把卡路里转化为脂肪排出体外
than storing it for example as glycogen
而不是将其以糖原等形式储存起来。
in the muscles.
在肌肉中。
&gt;&gt; Oh, so when I'm under slept, um that's
哦，所以当我睡眠不足的时候，嗯，那就是
why you know you're more likely to get
为什么你知道你更有可能获得
belly fat.
腹部脂肪。
&gt;&gt; Correct. And what's worse is that there
正确的。更糟糕的是，还有
was a great study where they looked at
这是一项很棒的研究，他们考察了……
people who were dieting and either
那些正在节食的人，要么
getting sufficient sleep or not getting
睡眠不足或睡眠不足
sufficient sleep. What was fascinating
充足的睡眠。最引人入胜的是……
is that both of those groups, whether
这两个群体，无论
you were well-slept or not wellslept,
你睡得好还是睡得不好？
you both lost weight. In fact, you lost
你们俩都瘦了。事实上，你输了。
about the same amount of weight. So
重量大致相同。所以
you'd think, okay, so that's fine. The
你会想，好吧，那没问题。这
problem was if you looked at what you
问题是，如果你看看你……
were losing, there was an issue. Those
我们输了，肯定出了问题。那些
people who were dieting but not getting
那些节食但没有减肥的人
sufficient sleep, 70% of all the weight
充足的睡眠占所有体重的70%。
that they lost came from lean muscle
他们失去的肌肉来自瘦肌肉。
mass and not fat. In other words, when
肌肉量，而不是脂肪量。换句话说，当
you're not getting sufficient sleep, you
你睡眠不足，你
keep what you want to lose, which is
保留你想失去的东西，那就是
fat, and you lose what you want to keep,
脂肪堆积，让你失去想要保留的部位。
which is muscle.
那就是肌肉。
&gt;&gt; Oh gosh. Damn. It's important, isn't it?
我的天哪。该死。这很重要，不是吗？
The sleep stuff.
睡眠方面的问题。
&gt;&gt; But coming back to ketosis, by the way,
不过，再说回生酮状态吧。
I would say when people go into a fasted
我想说的是，当人们进入禁食状态时
state, usually what we see is that their
通常情况下，我们看到的是他们的
sleep gets shorter.
睡眠时间变短。
&gt;&gt; And they'll say, "I sleep almost more
他们会说：“我睡得几乎更多了。”
efficiently. I'll sleep for maybe just
高效地。我可能就睡一会儿
four or five hours, but I feel more
四五个小时，但我感觉更久
alert and more awake."
精神更集中，更加清醒。
Now, some of that has to do with the
现在，其中一些与……有关
ketosis. When you are calorically
酮症。当你摄入大量卡路里时
deprived,
被剥夺的，
the brain starts to realize that
大脑开始意识到这一点
something is wrong because you are
出问题了，因为你
lacking calories. You're going into
缺乏热量。你即将进入
starvation. So, it drives on a chemical
饥饿。所以，它是靠化学物质驱动的。
called ereexin. Ereexin is a
称为ereexin。 Ereexin 是一种
wakeomotmoting chemical and it forces
唤醒运动化学物质及其作用
your brain to release much more of this
你的大脑会释放出更多这种物质。
wakefulness chemical called ereexin. So
一种名为ereexin的促醒化学物质。所以
now when you're fasting, it's easier to
现在当你禁食的时候，就更容易……
stay awake for longer and your brain
保持清醒的时间越长，你的大脑就越容易清醒。
will deliberately stop you from sleeping
会故意阻止你入睡
as much.
差不多。
&gt;&gt; It's not because it wants you to sleep
这并不是因为它想让你睡觉。
less. It's because the only time during
较少的。这是因为只有在那段时间里
our evolutionary past that we
我们进化的过去
unexperienced short sleep was when we
缺乏经验的短睡眠是指我们
were in a caloric deficit. And the
处于热量不足状态。以及
reason came comes back again to this
原因又回到了这一点。
idea that you have to stay awake longer
你需要保持清醒更长时间的想法
because you're not finding food. Now,
因为你找不到食物。现在，
your brain doesn't know you've
你的大脑并不知道你已经
deliberately decided to fast, which is a
特意决定禁食，这是一种
good thing in lots of ways. But that's
从很多方面来说都是件好事。但那是
one of the reasons that when people are
人们之所以会这样做，其中一个原因是
fasting, they'll say, "My sleep goes to
他们会说，禁食期间，“我的睡眠会受到影响”。
&gt;&gt; peck in a hand basket." You know,
用手篮啄食。”你知道，
&gt;&gt; mine goes really really short. So, when
我的那款真的非常非常短。所以，当
I'm I'm in ketosis now and I'm like in
我现在处于酮症状态，感觉就像……
on my way in and my sleep will reduce to
我正要进去，我的睡眠时间将会减少。
about five five six hours, my Whoop
大约五、六小时后，我的 Whoop
scores plummet.
分数暴跌。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; Until I kind of come out the other end,
直到我最终走出困境，
which might take a couple of weeks and
这可能需要几周时间，
then my sleep scores seem to stabilize
之后我的睡眠评分似乎就稳定下来了。
again. But that initial transition
再次。但最初的转变
period, it looks like it's having a
句号，看起来它正在经历一个
physiological shock.
生理性休克。
&gt;&gt; It is. And the shock is this chemical
这是。而这种冲击就是这种化学物质
ereexin, which is this wakering chemical
ereexin，这是一种唤醒化学物质。
which will force you to stay awake in a
这将迫使你保持清醒。
very solid fashion. By the way, case in
非常经典的款式。顺便说一下，案件在
point, people with narcolepsy,
重点是，患有嗜睡症的人，
this sleep disorder where they
这种睡眠障碍
inadvertently and uncontrollably fall
不经意间不受控制地跌倒
asleep during the day. They have the
白天睡觉。他们拥有
opposite. I just telling I was just
对面的。我只是说我刚才
telling you that when you are fasting,
告诉你，当你斋戒时，
your brain dumps out this chemical
你的大脑会释放这种化学物质
erection to force you awake and you're
勃起会让你醒来，而你
wide awake. People with narcolepsy when
清醒。患有嗜睡症的人
we've studied their brains, they have a
我们研究过他们的大脑，他们有一个
deficiency of this brain chemical
这种脑化学物质的缺乏
arexin. So they can't stay awake in a
艾瑞辛。所以他们无法保持清醒
stable fashion. They have the opposite
稳定的时尚。他们的情况正好相反。
of your fasting problem. You're wide
你的禁食问题。你很宽广。
awake because you've got too much
你醒着是因为你拥有太多了
erection. They've got too little Rexin
勃起。他们拥有的雷克辛太少了。
and they therefore they can't sustain
因此，他们无法维持下去。
stable wakefulness during the day. So
白天保持稳定的清醒状态。所以
they're constantly falling asleep. M
他们总是打瞌睡。 M
&gt;&gt; this story of ereexin has led to the
这段关于ereexin的故事导致了
invention of the first new class of
发明了第一类新型
sleeping medication that I actually
我确实服用过安眠药
favor and most people are not aware of
偏爱，但大多数人并不了解。
it. It's a new class of we're on to
它。这是我们正在学习的一门新课程
essentially web 3.0 of sleep medication.
本质上是睡眠药物领域的 Web 3.0 版本。
Web 1.0 were the benzoazipines things
Web 1.0 就是苯二氮卓类药物。
like Xanax and Valium not great for
像 Xanax 和 Valium 这样的药物效果不太好
sleep. The second wave the web 2.0 those
睡觉。第二波浪潮，即Web 2.0
were things like ambient lanesta sonata.
比如氛围音乐小夜曲奏鸣曲之类的。
Both of those drugs worked in a very
这两种药物都非常有效。
similar way where they go up to your
类似地，他们会走到你身边。
cortex and they tickle a receptor called
它们刺激大脑皮层，并刺激一种叫做……的受体。
the GABA receptor, GABA, GABA. And it's
GABA受体，GABA，GABA。而且是
the major neuroinhibitory transmitter of
主要的神经抑制性递质
the brain. So when these drugs flood
大脑。所以当这些药物泛滥时
your brain, they just hit the red light
你的大脑，它们刚刚触碰到了红灯
and they stop neural firing of the
它们会阻止神经元放电。
cortex. Essentially, they sedate you.
皮层。实际上，它们会让你昏昏欲睡。
And sedation is not sleep. But when you
镇静剂并不等于睡眠。但是当你
take an ambient, you mistake sedation
服用环境麻醉剂，你误以为是镇静剂
for sleep.
为了睡觉。
&gt;&gt; It's not quite the same. It's not
不太一样。它不是
naturalistic sleep.
自然睡眠。
&gt;&gt; But after we realized by way of the
但当我们通过以下方式意识到
story of narcolepsy that narcopsy
嗜睡症的故事
patients, they don't have this chemical
患者体内没有这种化学物质
erection and they're falling asleep
勃起，然后他们就睡着了
inappropriately during the day. Well,
白天不恰当地。出色地，
think about what insomnia is at night.
晚上想想失眠是什么感觉。
Insomnia is almost the opposite of
失眠几乎与……相反
narcopsy, which is that narcolepsy
嗜睡症，也就是嗜睡症
patients, they're falling asleep during
病人在治疗过程中睡着了。
the day when they want to be awake.
他们想保持清醒的那天。
Insomnia patients are awake at night
失眠患者夜间无法入睡。
when they want to be asleep. So what
当他们想睡觉的时候。所以呢
they realized is that what we can do if
他们意识到，如果我们能做什么，
this chemical ereexin, this wakefulness
这种化学物质ereexin，这种觉醒
volume button in the brain is a problem
大脑中的音量按钮是个问题
in insomnia patients. What if we were to
失眠患者。如果我们……
just develop a drug that doesn't sedate
只需研发一种不会引起镇静作用的药物即可。
the cortex like ambient? Instead, it
皮层就像环境一样？相反，它
goes down into the brain stem where the
向下进入脑干，在那里
center for erection is. And these new
勃起中心是。以及这些新的
drugs and they're called the Doras
毒品，它们被称为多拉斯
drugs, D A small s. And it's a class of
药物，D A 小 s。这是一类
drugs. There are three FDA approved and
毒品。目前有三种获得FDA批准的
I'll try and spell them out for you.
我尽量把它们解释清楚。
They're called suvaxent, lumberexent,
它们分别叫做苏瓦森特（Suvaxent）和伦伯雷森特（Lumberexent）。
and daredexent.
和 daredexent。
Exactly. Why my sinapses are filled with
确切地。为什么我的神经末梢充满了
things like those names, but there you
诸如此类的名字，但就是这样。
go. They're three FDA approved drugs.
去。这三种药物均已获得美国食品药品监督管理局（FDA）批准。
And what they do is they act like a
他们的做法就像……
clever set of chemical fingers. They go
一双灵巧的化学手指。他们走了
down into the brain stem where this sort
向下延伸到脑干，在那里这种
of erection is being released and they
勃起正在释放，他们
just dial down the volume on wakefulness
把清醒时的音量调低一些
and then they take a step back and they
然后他们后退一步，然后
allow the antithesis of wakefulness to
允许清醒状态的反面
come in its place which is this thing
取而代之的是这个东西
called naturalistic sleep. Now if you
称为自然睡眠。现在，如果你
look at that those clinical data they
看看那些临床数据
absolutely make you sleep for uh not
绝对让你睡不着觉，呃，不是。
necessarily a longer period of time but
不一定需要更长的时间，但
you're awake a lot less. So you've got
你醒着的时间少了很多。所以你已经有了
nice sleep efficiency, more continuity.
睡眠效率高，睡眠更连贯。
But I as a scientist could be very
但我作为一名科学家，可能会非常
skeptical and I could come along and
我持怀疑态度，但我可以一起去。
say, "Okay, so this new drug, it
比如说，“好的，这种新药，它
increases your total sleep time,
增加你的总睡眠时间，
improves your sleep efficiency, but I
提高睡眠效率，但我
have four words. Yes. And so what? Just
四个字。是的。那又怎样？只是
because I've added sleep to your night,
因为我让你的夜晚多了些睡眠，
how do I know that that's functional
我怎么知道它是有效的
sleep? How do I know that that's useful
睡觉？我怎么知道那有用呢？
sleep? Couldn't it just be like junk
睡觉？难道它就不能只是垃圾吗？
DNA? It could be just junk sleep. Well,
脱氧核糖核酸？可能只是睡眠质量差。出色地，
they did a study where they looked at
他们做了一项研究，研究了……
what we call the glimpmphatic system in
我们称之为顿悟系统的
your brain. There's a cleansing system
你的大脑。这里有一个清洁系统
in your brain that kicks into high gear
你的大脑瞬间高速运转起来。
during deep non-REM sleep. And it
在深度非快速眼动睡眠期间。而且它
flushes the brain of all of the
把大脑里所有的
metabolic toxins, two of which are
代谢毒素，其中两种是：
things called beta amalloid and ta
被称为β-淀粉样蛋白和ta的物质
protein, which are the culprits of
蛋白质是罪魁祸首
Alzheimer's. And that's why we know that
阿尔茨海默病。这就是我们知道这一点的原因。
sleep is so important because at night,
睡眠非常重要，因为在夜晚，
it's a good night sleep clean. It's a
一夜好眠，干净清爽。这是一个
power cleanse that washes away the
强力清洁，洗去……
Alzheimer's toxins. So they did a study.
阿尔茨海默病毒素。所以他们做了一项研究。
Heavens knows how they got these people
天知道他们是怎么找到这些人的。
to participate. But they brought them
参与。但他们带来了他们
in. They were 50 years or older and in
他们年龄都在50岁以上。
the morning and the night before they
早晨和前一天晚上
had a lumbar spinal puncture and they
他们接受了腰椎穿刺术。
siphoned off cerebral spinal fluid. So
抽取脑脊液。所以
they could measure how much of the
他们可以测量有多少
metabolic detritis was in the brain
脑部存在代谢性碎屑。
before sleep and in the brain after
睡前和睡后大脑中
sleep including
睡眠包括
&gt;&gt; the metabolic waste product sort of
代谢废物之类的
including beta amalloid and and tow
包括β-淀粉样蛋白和拖
protein
蛋白质
&gt;&gt; and they either had one of these drugs
他们要么服用了这些药物中的一种，要么服用了其中一种。
the Doras drugs or they had a placebo
多拉的药物，或者他们服用的是安慰剂。
and fair enough when they took the this
当他们采取这一行动时，这无可厚非。
new class of medication the web 3.0 to
新型药物网络 3.0
the Dora drug, their sleep got better.
服用朵拉药后，他们的睡眠质量有所改善。
But what they also found is that not
但他们还发现，并非如此。
only did their sleep get better, but
他们的睡眠质量确实有所改善，但是
they had cleansed the brain the next
他们第二天就清洗了大脑。
morning of more beta amaloid and ta
早上摄入更多β-淀粉样蛋白和ta
protein than the placebo group. In other
与安慰剂组相比，蛋白质组患者蛋白质水平更高。在其他方面
words, it wasn't just epifenomenal junk
文字，不仅仅是附带的垃圾
sleep. It was beneficial sleep. It was
睡觉。睡眠很有益。那是
adaptive useful sleep because that drug
适应性有益睡眠，因为那种药物
induced sleep had washed away more of
催眠已经冲刷掉了更多的
the Alzheimer's proteins. And it was the
阿尔茨海默病蛋白。而这正是
first demonstration and they've now
首次演示，他们现在
replicated it in animal models that this
在动物模型中也重复了这一现象。
is a sleeping pill that isn't
是一种并非安眠药的药
disadvantageous
不利
which we know to be the case for things
我们知道这种情况适用于很多事物。
like ambient. In fact, ambient there was
像环境音一样。事实上，那里的环境是
a recent study that showed that it
最近一项研究表明，
decreases the cleansing pulsing fluid by
减少清洁脉冲液
about 30 to 40% at night. But this is a
夜间约占30%至40%。但这是一个
new class of medications that does the
一类新型药物，其作用是
opposite.
对面的。
&gt;&gt; And this is new.
这是新情况。
&gt;&gt; And this is new. The Doras drugs D O R A
这是新情况。多拉的毒品 D O R A
small s. problem is that a lot of
小 s。问题在于很多
insurance companies here in the United
美国保险公司
States currently do not reimburse. Some
各州目前不予报销。一些
do and I believe that it's some of these
是的，而且我相信是其中的一些原因。
of the three doors drugs, not all of
三扇门毒品，并非全部
them are available in Europe or in the
它们在欧洲或其他地方均有销售。
UK.
英国。
&gt;&gt; Probably about right
大概差不多吧
&gt;&gt; and because they're just so expensive
而且因为它们价格太贵了。
and if you pay out of pocket, it can be
如果你自掏腰包支付，那可能……
up to $400 a month for these
这些每月最高可达 400 美元。
medications. Now, some insomnia patients
药物。现在，一些失眠患者
when I go to them and say, "At the end
当我走到他们跟前说：“最后……”
of a shockingly bad month of sleep, if I
如果我经历了一个月糟糕透顶的睡眠，那我
went to them and said, "Look, if you
我走到他们跟前说：“听着，如果你们……​​”
gave me $400 now, could I I could wave a
现在给我400美元，我可以挥舞一下吗？
magic wand and eradicate all of that bad
用魔法棒消灭所有坏东西
sleep over the previous month, would you
你会把上个月的睡眠时间补上吗？
like to give me $400?" Most of them
愿意给我400美元吗？”他们中的大多数人
would say, "Absolutely, take my money."
会说：“当然可以，拿走我的钱吧。”
But still, people are being priced out
但即便如此，人们仍然因为房价过高而买不起房。
at this stage, but the Doris drugs,
现阶段，但多丽丝的药物，
please look into them if you're
如果您是，请调查一下。
struggling with insomnia as well as
饱受失眠困扰
CBTI. I didn't realize there was so much
CBTI。我没想到会有这么多。
new science and research that had been
新的科学和研究已经
discovered on how to sleep well, what's
发现了如何睡得好的方法，是什么
going on in the brain, and also some of
大脑中正在发生的事情，以及一些
the lifestyle factors that have made
生活方式因素造成了这种情况
sleeping so hard for so many people. And
很多人睡得很沉。和
with that in mind, I want to do
考虑到这一点，我想这样做
something that I've never done before,
这是我以前从未做过的事。
which is a world first for the Diary of
这是《日记》杂志的世界首创。
a SEO. Is I'm going to put a link below
一名搜索引擎优化专家。我打算在下面放一个链接。
because I think this is a particular
因为我认为这是一种特殊的
episode where if you share this
如果你分享这一集，就会看到这一集
conversation with some of your friends
和你的一些朋友聊天
who particularly struggle with sleep or
那些睡眠特别困难的人
sleep optimizers or who have sleep
睡眠优化者或睡眠
disorders, they'll get a ton of benefit
患有疾病的人会从中受益匪浅。
from it. So, what I'm going to do is in
从中。所以，我接下来要做的就是……
the description of wherever you're
你所在位置的描述
listening to this podcast right now,
我正在听这个播客，
there is a link. And if you click on
两者之间存在联系。如果你点击
that link, um you'll see that you've got
点击那个链接，你会看到你已经有了
your own personalized link to share this
您专属的分享链接
episode. And those of you that share
插曲。以及那些分享的人
this episode, whether it's on your
这一集，无论是在你的
story, on social media or in a WhatsApp
在社交媒体或WhatsApp上讲述故事
group or wherever, on email with your
群组或其他任何地方，通过电子邮件与您的
friends, you will collect points for
朋友们，你们将获得积分
every person that listens and I will
每个听的人，我都会
reward those. Um, you'll see as you
奖励那些人。嗯，你很快就会明白的。
click on the link who have shared it the
点击分享此链接的人
most. In part, I say this because so
最多。部分原因是，我这么说……
many of you come up to me in the street
你们很多人会在街上走过来和我打招呼。
and they came up to me after our last
在我们最后一次之后，他们走过来和我说话。
conversation and they said, um, that
对话中，他们说，嗯，
conversation you did with Matt Walker
你和马特·沃克的对话
was so amazing. I sent it to my aunt and
太棒了。我把它寄给了我的姑姑。
she now d she did this and she's changed
她现在承认她做了这件事，她变了。
this and blah blah blah blah and she's
这个，还有巴拉巴拉巴拉，她
now sleeping well. And then all the
现在睡得很好。然后所有的
downstream impacts of that have been
下游影响已经显现
profound. So
深刻的。所以
&gt;&gt; I'm going to create this little system
我打算创建一个小系统
to encourage all of you to share it with
鼓励大家与他人分享
someone that um is struggling at the
有人在……方面遇到了困难
moment with sleep because I do believe I
短暂的睡眠，因为我相信我
do believe that sleep is upstream from
我相信睡眠是上游
so many of the downstream symptoms that
许多下游症状
ruin our lives whether it's relationship
毁掉我们的生活，无论是人际关系还是其他方面。
issues whether it's libido issues or
无论是性欲问题还是其他问题
whether it's creativity issues. I mean,
无论是创造力方面的问题。我是说，
I was reading through your work and I
我正在阅读你的作品，我
saw your conversation with Rogan not so
没看到你和罗根的对话
long ago where you talked about the fact
很久以前，你谈到过这件事
that a sleep-d deprived person has their
睡眠不足的人会……
genes fundamentally working differently.
基因的运作方式从根本上来说就不同。
You talked about 700 genes working
你提到了700个基因协同作用
differently.
不一样。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. 711 genes are distorted in their
是的。 711个基因发生畸变
activity caused by a lack of sleep. Some
睡眠不足引起的活动。一些
genes that are overexpressed that are
过度表达的基因
related to cardiovascular disease or
与心血管疾病有关或
stress or inflammation and other genes
压力或炎症以及其他基因
that are impaired which are associated
受损的，与……相关
with your immune system. So you become
利用你的免疫系统。所以你变成了
immune deficient
免疫缺陷
&gt;&gt; and it can be a downward compounding
而且这可能是一种向下复利效应。
spiral if you're such a person that's
如果你是这样的人，那就陷入恶性循环吧。
really continually strugg struggling
真的一直在苦苦挣扎
with sleep and building up some of that
通过睡眠和积累一些
sleep debt. So that link is below. Check
睡眠不足。链接如下。查看
it out. And we have a closing tradition
把它拿出来。我们还有一个结束仪式的传统。
on this podcast where the last leaves a
在这个播客中，最后留下了一个……
question for the next. The question left
下一个问题。剩下的问题
for you is what did success bring you
对你而言，成功带来了什么？
that you never could have dreamed of?
你做梦都想不到的事？
It brought me two things.
它给我带来了两样东西。
one beneficial one less. So
少了一个有益的。所以
beneficial is that I have now the chance
好处在于我现在有机会
and have gifted the chance to
并给予了他们这个机会
fly around the world and tried to speak
飞遍世界各地，并试图说话
the word of sleep because the physiology
睡眠一词与生理学有关
of it is so silent. And I used to lament
这里如此寂静。我过去常常为此感到惋惜
why me because there are so many other
为什么是我？因为还有很多其他人。
much better sleep scientists in the
睡眠质量大幅提升，科学家们……
world than me. And a friend after I was
世界比我更伟大。后来我的朋友
saying like I don't understand why me
就好像我不明白为什么是我
imposter syndrome and he just told me to
冒名顶替综合症，他刚才告诉我
shut up and accept that it's you and
闭嘴，接受现实吧，那就是你。
instead asked the question what are you
相反，他问的是：你是什么人？
going to do with it and I changed how I
我打算如何处理它，并且我改变了我的方式
embraced that. So I've been so fortunate
欣然接受了这一点。所以我真是太幸运了。
that my life after publishing the book
出版这本书之后我的生活。
that you're holding
你拿着
changed forever and almost all for the
一切都彻底改变了，几乎全部都是为了
better. And I'm so fortunate. I have
更好的。我真是太幸运了。我有
lived a life of such fortune by way of
他过着如此幸运的生活……
the sleep mission. I would say though
睡眠任务。不过我想说的是……
that there is
存在
also, and I suspect you may experience
另外，我怀疑你可能也会经历
some of this too, when you raise your
当你提高你的……时，其中也包括一些其他方面。
head above the public parapit,
头顶高于公共平台，
don't be surprised if shots are fired.
如果发生枪击事件，不要感到惊讶。
And if you're someone who has even the
如果你是那种即使拥有……
vaguest
最模糊
hint of insecurity, [laughter]
一丝不安全感，[笑声]
comments will do you a lovely
评论会给你带来美好的
disservice. And so I think there's a
失职。所以我认为存在一个
degree of kind of vulnerability and
脆弱性的程度和
insecurity that you can develop by way
你可能通过以下方式产生的不安全感
of becoming um someone who is in the eye
成为……嗯，那个在众目睽睽之下的人
of the public that had I not been in the
如果我不在场，公众会怎么想？
eye of the public I probably wouldn't
在公众的注视下，我可能不会
have been you know as self-conscious
你是否曾经有过那种不自信的性格？
about whether it's you know your
关于你是否了解你的
intellect or your voice or your you know
智力、你的声音，或者你的……你知道
disastrous you know boyband haircut
你知道，男孩乐队的发型简直是灾难。
whatever it is um I would say that's the
不管是什么，嗯，我会说那就是……
only slight downside overall I am the
唯一的小缺点是，我就是……
most fortunate human that I know. I am
我认识的最幸运的人。我是
so gifted by way of this thing called
如此天赋异禀，乃是通过这件叫做……的东西。
sleep. It's a love affair that's lasted
睡觉。这是一段持续很久的恋情。
me almost 25 years and I believe it's
我差不多25年了，我相信是
the most beguiling topic in all of
最引人入胜的话题
science and it has treated me so well.
科学对我很好。
&gt;&gt; You happy?
你开心吗？
&gt;&gt; More than you could imagine at this
比你想象的还要多
moment in my life. I am the happiest
我生命中的一个时刻。我是最幸福的
I've been.
我一直都在。
&gt;&gt; Why? I have a a piece that I found in
为什么？我有一块我在……找到的碎片
life
生活
for reasons that I can share or not
至于原因，我或许可以透露，或许不能透露。
share. And
分享。和
&gt;&gt; go ahead and share them. I'd love in my
请随意分享。我爱我的
life.
生活。
&gt;&gt; You know, I found my person
你知道吗，我找到了我的另一半
&gt;&gt; and and she is she
她就是她
appeared like lightning from a clear
如同闪电般从晴朗的天空中闪现。
blue sky. Never saw her coming.
蓝天。完全没想到她会来。
And
和
it's interesting that
有趣的是
I've never been able to be more myself,
我从未如此自在地做自己。
even with myself,
即使是对自己，
than I have with her.
比我跟她在一起的时光还要多。
Every day she makes me want to be a
她每天都让我想要成为一个
better person.
更好的人。
And
和
I have found peace that I have never had
我找到了从未有过的平静。
before.
前。
&gt;&gt; That you've never had before?
你以前从未有过的经历？
&gt;&gt; No.
不。
&gt;&gt; Did you have peace last time we spoke?
上次我们通话时，你过得平静吗？
I wouldn't say I was without peace. I
我不会说我内心毫无平静。我
didn't know this type of peace
以前从未体验过这种和平。
and I never believed in this notion of
我从来不相信这种说法。
the one. You know, I was a scientist.
就是那个。你知道吗，我以前是科学家。
I'm a hard-nosed empirical kind of guy
我是一个务实、注重实证的人。
and I just did not imagine it would be
我完全没想到会是这样。
such
这样的
uh I didn't think there was such a one.
呃，我没想到还有这样的事。
I would have told you if you'd told me
如果你告诉我，我也会告诉你。
that two years ago, you'd given me your
两年前，你给了我你的
love story of certainty. I would have
一段充满确定性的爱情故事。我会
thought you're misguided and that, you
我觉得你被误导了，而且，你
know, you just need to put down whatever
你知道，你只需要放下任何东西
substances you're using because you're
你正在使用的物质，因为你
delusional because there isn't such a
这是妄想，因为根本不存在这样的事。
thing.
事物。
&gt;&gt; Um,
嗯，
she's a gift
她是个宝藏
and I hope I never take her for granted.
我希望我永远不会把她给予我的一切都视为理所当然。
I doubt it. There's a an incredibly sad
我对此表示怀疑。有一个令人无比悲伤的故事
story
故事
of a gentleman called Clive Wearing. And
一位名叫克莱夫·韦林的先生。和
Clive is a famous individual in the
克莱夫是位名人。
neuroscience world. And Clive was the
神经科学界。而克莱夫是
man who the movie Momento
电影《记忆碎片》中的男人
was based on, which is a movie where a
改编自一部电影，其中……
man has brain damage and he has profound
男子脑部受损，并患有严重的疾病。
amnesia. And from that moment forward,
健忘症。从那一刻起，
he can never make any new memories
他永远无法创造任何新的记忆
whatsoever. He's densely amnesic.
任何。他患有严重的失忆症。
And he was a real life individual. He
他是一个真实存在的人。他
contracted a virus that destroyed his
他感染了一种病毒，这种病毒摧毁了他的身体。
memory centers. And from that point
记忆中心。从那以后
forward, he could no longer make any new
向前，他再也无法做出任何新的决定了。
memories. And he lived in just 2 or 3
回忆。他只住过两三个地方。
seconds of time. And that spotlight of
几秒钟的时间。而那束聚光灯
consciousness just moved forward in
意识就这样向前推进了。
time. He had no recollection of the
时间。他完全不记得这件事了。
past. He had no anticipation of the
过去的。他丝毫没有预料到……
future. And the only thing, the only
未来。唯一一件事，唯一
person that he remembered and he would
他记得的那个人，他会
recognize is his wife. So he could have
他认出那是他的妻子。所以他可能
spent this whole three hours speaking to
花了整整三个小时跟人聊天
you. And then you would walk out the
你。然后你就会走出去。
room for five minutes and you would walk
房间待五分钟，然后你就可以走了
back in and you'd say, "Hi Clive, nice
回去之后你会说：“嗨，克莱夫，真不错。”
to meet you." and he'd say, "Hi, what's
很高兴见到你。”他会说，“你好，你好吗？”
your name?" Had no recollection. The
你的名字？” 我完全不记得了。
only person that he remembered was his
他唯一记得的人就是他自己
wife. But the problem was he never
妻子。但问题是他从未
remembered how long it's been since he
他想起了自己有多久没来了。
last saw his wife. And so every time
他最后一次见到妻子。所以每次
that she would walk into the room after
她会随后走进房间。
being out of it for 5 minutes, he would
他昏迷了5分钟后，就会
jump out of his chair and he had this
他猛地从椅子上跳起来，然后他就……
incredible elation and he would run and
他欣喜若狂，然后跑了起来。
he would hug her and kiss her. And I
他会拥抱她，亲吻她。我
think sometimes we take our partners for
有时候我们会把伴侣当成……
granted
的确
and the only time we realize how
而我们唯一意识到这一点的时候
precious they are is when they're gone.
失去之后，才懂得珍惜。
And I often think about that that
我经常会想到这一点。
complacency can be one of the greatest
自满可能是最大的弊端之一。
negative forces in a relationship. And I
关系中的负面因素。我
always think about Clive Weiring even on
即使在……也总是想起克莱夫·韦林
the days where I'm having a bad day or
当我心情不好的时候，或者
I'm in a bad mood and I'm not myself or
我心情很差，感觉不像我自己。
I just don't want to be around someone.
我就是不想和任何人待在一起。
I always try to remember his reaction.
我总是努力记住他的反应。
And when my wife walks back in from work
当我的妻子下班回家时
or I see her, you know, first thing, I
或者我见到她，你知道，第一件事就是，我
try to remember how his reaction was and
试着回忆一下他的反应。
how I truly feel at the time despite the
尽管当时我的真实感受是……
blanket of negative stress trying to
试图营造一种负面压力的氛围
drown that feeling out.
用酒精麻痹自己，驱散这种感觉。
&gt;&gt; It's a beautiful thing. I think about
这是一件美好的事。我想到……
that a lot as well.
那方面也很多。
&gt;&gt; In what way? just the part of I'm way
以什么方式？只是我方式的一部分
more cognizant now on a frequent basis
现在更频繁地意识到这一点
almost on a weekly basis of how I'm
几乎每周我都会谈到我的近况。
going to feel
感觉
when my time is up as it relates to rel
当我的时间到了，就关系而言，
my romantic relationship like I think
我的恋爱关系就像我想的那样
even like mid argument I will now think
即使在争论进行到一半的时候，我现在也会这样想
and this actually happened like a couple
这件事实际上就像一对情侣那样发生了。
of days ago it wasn't really an argument
几天前，这根本算不上什么争论。
we're disagreeing about something I
我们在某件事上意见不合，我
literally said mid mid uh dispute that
字面上说的是中途争论。
we were having I said we're going to
我们正在……我说我们要……
regret this so much and what I meant was
我对此深感后悔，我的意思是……
when I when that When that phone call
当我接到那个电话时
rings and someone gives me bad news that
电话铃声响起，有人告诉我一个坏消息。
either I'm going or you're going, I'm
要么我走，要么你走，我
going to regret that this 30 minutes was
我会后悔这30分钟的。
wasted doing this.
这样做纯属浪费时间。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; I'm really going to regret it.
我肯定会后悔的。
&gt;&gt; How much would you give to have that 30
你愿意付出多少来拥有那30
minutes?
分钟？
&gt;&gt; Exactly. And it's like, you know, we're
确切地。你知道，我们就像……
arguing about, I don't know,
他妈的争论什么，我也不知道，
some whatever it might be, some trivial
不管是什么，一些琐碎的事情
thing. It's actually really helped me
事物。它真的帮了我很大的忙。
because in the midst of those storms,
因为在那些风暴之中，
um, thinking through to that moment when
嗯，回想那一刻，
you get that phone call and like you're
你接到那个电话，感觉就像……
ill or I'm ill and some we're not going
生病了，或者我生病了，所以我们有些人不去了。
to be around much longer.
能够存在更长时间。
um it liberates you from the pettiness
嗯，它让你摆脱了琐碎的烦恼。
that a sense of immortality can create
永生感可以创造
and that pettiness results in the
而这种斤斤计较导致了……
complacency that you're describing that
你所描述的那种自满情绪
like I I took you for granted.
就像我以前把你当成理所当然一样。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; So it's a nice little mechanism now for
所以现在它成了一个很不错的机制。
me to go is this an important thing? Is
让我去，这很重要吗？是
this really important? And I have to
这真的很重要吗？我必须
provide nuance there which is this
这里需要提供细微差别，那就是
doesn't mean don't address things
但这并不意味着不要处理问题。
&gt;&gt; correctly. I was just about to say
正确。我正要说
conflict is critical. You've got to
冲突至关重要。你必须
fight well,
好好战斗！
&gt;&gt; but let it be me versus you and the
但就让我和你对抗吧
problem. Like me and you versus the
问题。就像你和我对抗
problem versus me just going at you.
问题是，我只是想找你麻烦。
&gt;&gt; Yes. You have to be fighting for each
是的。你必须为每一件事而战。
other,
其他，
&gt;&gt; not fighting against each other.
他们之间没有互相争斗。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Exactly.
是的。确切地。
&gt;&gt; And that you have to try to then in that
所以你必须尝试这样做。
context of Clive wearing
克莱夫穿着的背景
&gt;&gt; don't shy away from conflict if you need
如果需要，不要回避冲突。
to have the conversation. Often it's
进行对话。通常是
like the gym. If you do it well, you
就像健身房一样。如果你做得好，你
even on the days when you kind of go
即使在那些你有点想离开的日子里
into the gym, you think, I I don't want
走进健身房，你心想，我不想……
to do this or I just I don't feel good,
做这件事，或者我只是感觉不舒服。
you always come out feeling better than
你总是感觉比别人好。
you did before. And with conflict, if
你以前做过。而如果发生冲突的话
you do it well, you typically, it may
如果你做得好，通常情况下，它可能
not be the hour after or even the day
不是之后的一个小时，甚至不是当天。
after, but if you do it well, you
之后，但如果你做得很好，你
typically are better as a couple after
通常情况下，夫妻关系会更好
than you were before the conflict as
比冲突前更甚
long as you do it well. So, I'm not
只要你做得好就行。所以，我不是
saying don't have conflict. What I'm
说不要发生冲突。我是什么
saying is Clive Wearing's story to me of
克莱夫·韦林向我讲述的故事是……
how he loved his wife with an intent
他全心全意地爱着他的妻子。
that I'd never experienced before until
那是我以前从未经历过的，直到
I met my much better half
我遇到了我更好的另一半
prevented me from resentment.
它让我不再心生怨恨。
Resentment is the barrier that will keep
怨恨是阻碍我们前进的障碍。
you from reparation and a future of I
你免于赔偿和我的未来
think equinimity.
保持内心的平静。
Because when you resent someone, it
因为当你怨恨某人时，
means that you haven't processed, you
这意味着你还没有处理，你
haven't moved forward. And resentment
尚未取得进展。以及怨恨
usually comes by way of I think a poor
通常是通过我认为一个贫穷的人来发生的
choice of things such as did I win the
选择诸如我是否获胜之类的事情
argument? Did you win the argument? It's
争论？你赢了这场争论吗？它是
not about point scoring at least. And
至少与得分无关。和
I've done that before. I've been guilty
我以前做过这件事。我曾有罪。
of all of that behavior. But now with
所有这些行为。但现在
this person that I cherish most, you
我最珍视的这个人，就是你。
know, I think of his lessons. It's not
我知道，我会想起他的教诲。它不是
that we don't have conflict. We do. It's
我们没有冲突。是的。它是
just that I value the person far beyond
只是我对这个人非常珍视。
the conflict afterwards. And I'll always
随后的冲突。我将永远
want to reach out with an olive branch
想伸出橄榄枝。
because it's not worth it. Just as you
因为不值得。就像你一样
said, when that call comes,
他说，当那个电话响起时，
you know, I I think of that sometimes
你知道，我有时会想到这件事。
when I have a bad day. Let's say
当我心情不好的时候。比如说
someone, you know, I come back to my car
你知道，我回到车里的时候，有人……
and my car is being rearended when it's
我的车在行驶过程中被追尾了。
been parked or, you know, I was coming
已经停好车了，或者，你知道，我正要过来。
here to fly out and we were 4 hours on
我们来这里准备乘飞机离开，结果等了4个小时。
the tarmac waiting and there's a guy in
停机坪上有人在等着，那里有个家伙
front of me who's getting all agitated
我前面那个人情绪激动起来了
and giving the the ground staff all
并给予地勤人员所有
sorts of vitriol.
各种各样的尖刻言辞。
And I was thinking, look, when you're on
我当时在想，你看，当你……
your deathbed, my good fellow, are you
我的朋友，你已濒临死亡了吗？
going to look back at this day and
将来我会回顾这一天
think, gosh, you know, I remember that
想想，哎呀，你知道，我记得那件事
one day when I was on that flight coming
有一天，我乘坐那趟航班抵达
out to LA and it was 4 hours delayed.
飞往洛杉矶的航班延误了4个小时。
No, of course you're not. So, if you're
不，你当然不是。所以，如果你是
not stressing about it when you're
当你……的时候不要为此感到压力
dying, why are you stressing about it
都快死了，你还担心什么？
now?
现在？
&gt;&gt; It's just not worth it.
根本不值得。
&gt;&gt; Live. Thank you. Thank you so much. I
居住。谢谢。太感谢了。我
mean, I can't thank you enough for the
我的意思是，我无法用言语表达我对你的感激之情。
profound impact you've had on so many
你对许多人产生了深远的影响。
millions of people. Um, being the the
数百万人。嗯，作为
chief torchbearer of the subject of
该主题的主要倡导者
sleep and creating a movement around
睡眠和周围环境的移动
sleep, but also a heightened awareness
睡眠，以及高度的意识
of ourselves and our struggles. And that
我们自己和我们的奋斗。而那
is something that you'll never
是你永远不会拥有的东西
understand. Like, you'll never
理解。比如，你永远不会
understand the full magnitude of the
充分理解
many millions of people you've
你已经影响了数以百万计的人。
positively impacted. Um, but I mean even
产生了积极影响。嗯，但我的意思是即使
though you'll never get to meet them all
虽然你永远不可能见到他们所有人。
and you'll never get to hear all of
你永远也听不到全部内容。
their thank yous, they are very very
他们的感谢，他们非常非常
real people and they are that the them
真实的人，他们就是他们
themselves are these little ripples
它们本身就是这些细小的涟漪。
through the ocean where their children
穿过海洋，他们的孩子
and then the generations to come get to
然后后代就会……
sleep better and enjoy their lives and
睡得更好，生活更美好
live a happier healthier life because of
因为……而过上更幸福、更健康的生活
the work that you do. So it's um
你所做的工作。所以，嗯……
incredibly important work, Matthew,
马修，这项工作极其重要。
&gt;&gt; and I hope you long continue it and I
我希望你能一直坚持下去，我
long continue being the conduit of this
长期以来，它一直扮演着这一角色的传播者的角色。
very important information to people
对人们来说非常重要的信息
like me and my audience. Couldn't
就像我和我的观众一样。无法
appreciate you more. Thank you so much
更加感激你。太感谢了
for saying that. I can't lay claim to
因为你说了那句话。我不能声称拥有
any such um uh affirmations, but I would
任何此类嗯嗯嗯的肯定，但我会
say that I stand on the shoulders of
可以说我站在……的肩膀上
giants and that um I am simply relaying
巨人，嗯，我只是转述一下。
all of the incredible work of all of my
我的所有同事们所做的所有令人难以置信的工作
colleagues in the field and all of those
该领域的同事以及所有那些
who came before me. Um I'm just the
在我之前的人。嗯，我只是……
mouthpiece and not a particularly good
吹嘴，而且质量也不太好。
one at that and for all of their work.
就凭这一点，就为了他们所有的努力。
It's really the appreciation that I give
我真正表达的是一种感激之情。
to them. So, thank you for giving me the
对他们来说。所以，谢谢你给我
opportunity to say that.
有机会说这句话。
[music]
[音乐]
Make sure you keep what I'm about to say
请务必记住我接下来要说的话。
to yourself. I'm inviting 10,000 of you
对自己说。我邀请你们中的10000人。
to come even deeper into the dire of a
进一步陷入困境
CEO. Welcome to my inner circle. This is
首席执行官。欢迎来到我的核心圈子。这是
a brand new private community that I'm
一个全新的私人社区，我
launching to the world. We have so many
面向全球发布。我们有太多了
incredible things that happen that you
发生的那些不可思议的事情
are never shown. We have the briefs that
从未展示过。我们有以下简报：
are on my iPad when I'm recording the
录音时，我的iPad上都有这些内容。
conversation. We have clips we've never
对话。我们有一些从未播放过的片段
released. We have behindthe-scenes
已发布。我们有幕后花絮
conversations with the guests and also
与客人的交谈以及
the episodes that we've never ever
我们从未见过的那些剧集
released. and so much more. In the
已发布。还有更多。在
circle, you'll have direct access to me.
圈内人可以直接联系到我。
You can tell us what you want this show
你可以告诉我们你希望这个节目呈现什么内容
to be, who you want us to interview, and
你想让我们采访谁？
the types of conversations you would
你会进行的对话类型
love us to have. But remember, for now,
爱我们拥有。但请记住，就目前而言，
we're only inviting the first 10,000
我们只邀请前10000名。
people that join before it closes. So,
在截止日期前加入的人。所以，
if you want to join our private closed
如果你想加入我们的私人封闭式组织
community, head to the link in the
社区中，请点击链接。
description below or go to
下方有详细说明，或前往
daccircle.com.
daccircle.com。
I will speak to you then.
到时候我再跟你谈。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Oh,
哦，
hey.
嘿。
[music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[歌唱]